[
  {
    "Question": "In a startup company's business plan, it has a sales goal for the first year of $250,000, a sales goal increase of\n10% the second year, and increase of 15% for the third year. What is the sales goal amount for the third year?",
    "A": "$265,250",
    "B": "$316,250",
    "C": "$302,000",
    "D": "$275,000",
    "answer": "B: $316,250",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For marketing research data to be useful, they must",
    "A": "describe the target market.",
    "B": "contain researchers' bias.",
    "C": "be interpreted properly.",
    "D": "come from multiple sources.",
    "answer": "C: be interpreted properly.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Landon wants to start a home-based T-shirt printing business. Which of the following are the most critical\nequipment and supplies that Landon will need to get his business up and running:",
    "A": "Printing machine, display cases, and T-shirts",
    "B": "T-shirts, printing machine, and artwork",
    "C": "Artwork, T-shirts, and thread",
    "D": "T-shirts, thread, and display cases",
    "answer": "B: T-shirts, printing machine, and artwork",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Al is thinking about moving his company's headquarters to another city, which would be expensive but would\nbring the company closer to the raw materials needed for manufacturing. The benefit of moving is",
    "A": "feasibility.",
    "B": "independence.",
    "C": "demand.",
    "D": "proximity.",
    "answer": "D: proximity.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A new customer moving into your area is a(n)",
    "A": "weakness.",
    "B": "strength.",
    "C": "threat.",
    "D": "opportunity.",
    "answer": "D: opportunity.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A reason that the government requires some businesses to have licenses is that the businesses",
    "A": "could affect the public welfare.",
    "B": "are owned by several people.",
    "C": "have more than 20 employees.",
    "D": "are located in metropolitan areas.",
    "answer": "A: could affect the public welfare.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sari's restaurant is hosting a family fun night with food specials, carnival games, and face painting. She wants to get the word out about the event to the general public, but she's not sure how. Which of the following public relations tools would be most appropriate:",
    "A": "Newsletter",
    "B": "Email to current customers",
    "C": "Press conference",
    "D": "Press release",
    "answer": "D: Press release",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Most business analysis techniques focus on identifying organizational __________ and possibilities for __________.",
    "A": "locations; expansion",
    "B": "goals; improvement",
    "C": "projects; partnerships",
    "D": "capital; fundraising",
    "answer": "B: goals; improvement",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following best describes problem-solving with appreciative inquiry:?",
    "A": "Digging deeper to find underlying causes",
    "B": "Framing an issue in a positive way",
    "C": "Thinking of things that could make the issue worse",
    "D": "Working out issues subconsciously",
    "answer": "B: Framing an issue in a positive way",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A disadvantage of commercial finance companies as a main source of credit for businesses is that they are often",
    "A": "expensive.",
    "B": "conservative.",
    "C": "cautious.",
    "D": "independent.",
    "answer": "A: expensive.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should a business manager do to effectively handle an employee's complaint?",
    "A": "Consider several solutions",
    "B": "Listen to the complaint",
    "C": "Explain business procedures",
    "D": "Send the employee to counseling",
    "answer": "A: Consider several solutions",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The entrepreneurial discovery process requires knowledge and the recognition of a(n)",
    "A": "preventable accident.",
    "B": "market need.",
    "C": "economic crisis.",
    "D": "creative observation.",
    "answer": "B: market need.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A customer's experiences with a business are affected by the customer's perceptions and",
    "A": "expectations.",
    "B": "encouragement.",
    "C": "appearance.",
    "D": "leadership.",
    "answer": "A: expectations.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step in entrepreneurial discovery?",
    "A": "Analyzing the feasibility of an idea",
    "B": "Screening the product ideas",
    "C": "Determining the risks and rewards",
    "D": "Identifying an unmet want or need",
    "answer": "D: Identifying an unmet want or need",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following best describes what it means to have a vision:?",
    "A": "Having a mental picture of the ideal future",
    "B": "Encouraging others to achieve their dreams",
    "C": "Setting clear objectives that you want to achieve",
    "D": "Being clear-minded and focused at all times",
    "answer": "A: Having a mental picture of the ideal future",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When total sales equal total expenses, the business?",
    "A": "must cut its operating costs.",
    "B": "has successfully created economies of scale.",
    "C": "has reached its break-even point.",
    "D": "will increase its price markups.",
    "answer": "C: has reached its break-even point.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "TRISM Co. sets an organizational goal to gain 100 new clients. To do so, each sales rep must contact five prospects per week. This is an example of",
    "A": "establishing performance standards.",
    "B": "designing an organizational structure.",
    "C": "aligning personal goals with company goals.",
    "D": "generating new product ideas.",
    "answer": "A: establishing performance standards.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do businesses often analyze when making decisions about how to improve the company?",
    "A": "Training methods",
    "B": "Privacy factors",
    "C": "Information skills",
    "D": "Statistical findings",
    "answer": "D: Statistical findings",
    "topic": "Market research & marketing information"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a prediction:?",
    "A": "Sales will be up 4% next quarter.",
    "B": "Sales were up 4% last quarter.",
    "C": "The business owes $200,000 in taxes.",
    "D": "About half of the business's customers are female.",
    "answer": "A: Sales will be up 4% next quarter.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Increasing membership by 25% during the next year might be one of the __________ of a health club.",
    "A": "goals",
    "B": "principles",
    "C": "strategies",
    "D": "tactics",
    "answer": "A: goals",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following financial records would you use to identify discrepancies within the general accountin g\nledger:?",
    "A": "Statement of cash flow",
    "B": "Income statement",
    "C": "Balance sheet",
    "D": "Owner's equity statement",
    "answer": "C: Balance sheet",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After being fired from his job, Jack wrote blog posts in which he criticized his former company and all its\nemployees. He made many negative comments, most of which were untrue. What tort is Jack committing?",
    "A": "Invasion of privacy",
    "B": "Battery",
    "C": "Negligence",
    "D": "Defamation",
    "answer": "D: Defamation",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Changes in accounts receivable are reflected in",
    "A": "cash from operations.",
    "B": "financing.",
    "C": "investing.",
    "D": "net income.",
    "answer": "A: cash from operations.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because their advertisements last only as long as they are on the air, broadcast media are considered\n__________ media.",
    "A": "space",
    "B": "affordable",
    "C": "time",
    "D": "short-term",
    "answer": "C: time",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of insurance protects a company from losses incurred when one of its customers is unable to repay a\ndebt because the customer's business was destroyed by a tornado?",
    "A": "Credit",
    "B": "Property",
    "C": "Health",
    "D": "Life",
    "answer": "A: Credit",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The form of discipline that is used to maintain discipline on a day-to-day basis is",
    "A": "time out.",
    "B": "constructive criticism.",
    "C": "group counseling.",
    "D": "peer pressure.",
    "answer": "B: constructive criticism.",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business has decided to talk to several customers individually to understand their preferences and experiences with the business's products. What form of research is the business doing?",
    "A": "Research panels",
    "B": "A case study",
    "C": "Focus groups",
    "D": "Interviews",
    "answer": "D: Interviews",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Organizational costs, revenue, and profitability are of limited use in measuring supply chain performance because these measures",
    "A": "tend to work best in certain industries.",
    "B": "are not changed by managerial decision-making.",
    "C": "tend to focus on specific units or departments.",
    "D": "can reflect conditions unrelated to performance.",
    "answer": "D: can reflect conditions unrelated to performance.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding risk and business objectives is true:?",
    "A": "Risk management should not be considered when planning corporate strategy.",
    "B": "Businesses that have good corporate objectives do not need to plan for risks.",
    "C": "Businesses should focus primarily on mitigating risks rather than meeting goals.",
    "D": "Good business plans aim to meet corporate goals while mitigating risks.",
    "answer": "D: Good business plans aim to meet corporate goals while mitigating risks.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do businesses often negotiate with banks during the process of obtaining a loan?",
    "A": "Personal equity",
    "B": "Interest rate",
    "C": "Stock value",
    "D": "Accounts payable",
    "answer": "B: Interest rate",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a business budgeted $245,250 in sales with 60% of that amount for expenses but actual sales were $280,500 with 65% of that amount spent on expenses, by what amount did the business's monthly income increase or decrease from the amount budgeted?",
    "A": "$25 decrease",
    "B": "$50 increase",
    "C": "$65 decrease",
    "D": "$75 increase",
    "answer": "D: $75 increase",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When is the use of email an effective direct-advertising strategy?",
    "A": "A business wants to be sure people read the message.",
    "B": "The message appeals only to people who have computers.",
    "C": "The message is too long to be posted on the company's social media account.",
    "D": "The message appeals to a small audience interested in a specific product.",
    "answer": "D: The message appeals to a small audience interested in a specific product.",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When the owner of a small company conducts an organizational SWOT analysis, it is important for them to?",
    "A": "define the business's mission.",
    "B": "develop strategies for improvement.",
    "C": "obtain input from employees.",
    "D": "focus on the threats.",
    "answer": "C: obtain input from employees.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is important that businesses stay on top of their governance reports to ensure compliance because __________ can change frequently.",
    "A": "personnel",
    "B": "the economy",
    "C": "regulations",
    "D": "technology",
    "answer": "C: regulations",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a reason for dismissing an employee that might be considered illegal:?",
    "A": "Employee is a temporary worker.",
    "B": "Employee is a consultant.",
    "C": "Employee's specialized job no longer exists.",
    "D": "Employee develops a physical disability.",
    "answer": "D: Employee develops a physical disability.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To prevent others from making or selling Evan's invention without permission, he should seek legal protection by applying for a",
    "A": "patent.",
    "B": "trademark.",
    "C": "copyright.",
    "D": "permit.",
    "answer": "A: patent.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an advantage of the corporation as a form of business ownership:?",
    "A": "Tax advantages",
    "B": "Separate owners and managers",
    "C": "Limited liability",
    "D": "Less complex requirements",
    "answer": "C: Limited liability",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following public relations communication tools should include all the information a journalist might need to feature a company or product in a news story:?",
    "A": "Website collection",
    "B": "Sponsorship",
    "C": "Press kit",
    "D": "Petition",
    "answer": "C: Press kit",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way that managers can promote ethical behavior on the part of everyone in the business is by encouraging employees to",
    "A": "develop a code of ethics.",
    "B": "be thoughtful of others.",
    "C": "report unethical actions.",
    "D": "avoid social situations.",
    "answer": "C: report unethical actions.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Current profits for a business are high. An appropriate course of action for this business would be to",
    "A": "reduce its staff.",
    "B": "watch its competitors.",
    "C": "raise its prices.",
    "D": "increase its advertising.",
    "answer": "B: watch its competitors.",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business using sales-oriented pricing might achieve which of the following benefits:",
    "A": "Creating an image for the business",
    "B": "Maximizing profits",
    "C": "Decreasing market share",
    "D": "Earning a return on investment",
    "answer": "A: Creating an image for the business",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do businesses expect to make when they set prices on goods and services?",
    "A": "Profits",
    "B": "Quotas",
    "C": "Payments",
    "D": "Salaries",
    "answer": "A: Profits",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the most important characteristics of a quality good is",
    "A": "responsiveness.",
    "B": "reliability.",
    "C": "empathy.",
    "D": "tangibles.",
    "answer": "B: reliability.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for marketing research to be objective?",
    "A": "So that researchers can guide consumers' responses",
    "B": "So that the data gathered are not influenced by researchers' opinions",
    "C": "So that researchers can express their own opinions",
    "D": "So that the data gathered can be analyzed using statistical software",
    "answer": "B: So that the data gathered are not influenced by researchers' opinions",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following must occur for supply chain management to be successful:?",
    "A": "Emphasis should be placed on internal activities.",
    "B": "Few people should be involved in operations.",
    "C": "Producers should be in contact with final customers.",
    "D": "Goods and communication should flow both ways.",
    "answer": "D: Goods and communication should flow both ways.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of contingency plan describes strategies to deal with the loss of intellectual property?",
    "A": "Crisis management plan",
    "B": "Asset security plan",
    "C": "Continuity plan",
    "D": "Safety plan",
    "answer": "B: Asset security plan",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following has an important impact on a business's willingness to adjust prices:?",
    "A": "State of the economy",
    "B": "Condition of the facility",
    "C": "Opinions of the competition",
    "D": "Policies of the company",
    "answer": "A: State of the economy",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An operating expense incurred by a business when it fails to collect its receivables is called __________ expense.",
    "A": "bad debt",
    "B": "interest",
    "C": "advertising",
    "D": "administrative",
    "answer": "A: bad debt",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does the manufacturing stage of product development entail?",
    "A": "Distributing the product and providing customer service",
    "B": "Investing in equipment, labor, and infrastructure",
    "C": "Determining if the product has market demand and how long it will take to reach the market",
    "D": "Developing a prototype to determine the product's capabilities and efficiency",
    "answer": "B: Investing in equipment, labor, and infrastructure",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason why businesses screen job applications before conducting interviews is to determine if the applicants",
    "A": "have the proper attitudes.",
    "B": "meet the minimum requirements.",
    "C": "attended well-known educational institutions.",
    "D": "earned adequate yearly incomes.",
    "answer": "B: meet the minimum requirements.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Carson has an exciting idea for a new product and needs to acquire funding to start building a prototype. He does not have strong credit, but he does have a wide circle of acquaintances and contacts. What method is best suited for Carson to obtain financial resources?",
    "A": "Angel investors",
    "B": "Small-business loan",
    "C": "Crowdfunding",
    "D": "Credit card",
    "answer": "C: Crowdfunding",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Vera Cruz Company management has identified changes to make to increase sales revenue and improve overall profitability. The management team has given information to all appropriate stakeholders. What should the management team do next?",
    "A": "Inform vendors of the changes",
    "B": "Advertise the changes to customers",
    "C": "Implement the changes immediately",
    "D": "Create a change management plan",
    "answer": "D: Create a change management plan",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business should avoid purchasing long-term service contracts for equipment that is",
    "A": "out of warranty.",
    "B": "highly reliable.",
    "C": "prone to breakdowns.",
    "D": "very expensive.",
    "answer": "B: highly reliable.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is particularly challenging for companies to assess external business risks because such risks are",
    "A": "often the result of poor corporate governance.",
    "B": "primarily due to factors within the company itself.",
    "C": "generally unpredictable and out of the companies' control.",
    "D": "usually predictable and in the companies' control.",
    "answer": "C: generally unpredictable and out of the companies' control.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about selecting employees:?",
    "A": "Businesses must determine job applicants' age, education, and job experience.",
    "B": "Testing the job skills of applicants during the selection process is illegal.",
    "C": "The employee-selection process does not affect employees' success on the job.",
    "D": "The selection process is controlled by strict legal guidelines.",
    "answer": "D: The selection process is controlled by strict legal guidelines.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which section of his business plan will Paulo discuss each key manager's skills?",
    "A": "Executive summary",
    "B": "Company description",
    "C": "Market analysis",
    "D": "Management plan",
    "answer": "D: Management plan",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A common way that companies protect their digital assets is by",
    "A": "giving all employees full access to digital assets.",
    "B": "hesitating to update software and applications.",
    "C": "educating all employees on cybersecurity.",
    "D": "avoiding two-factor authentication when logging in.",
    "answer": "C: educating all employees on cybersecurity.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When bottlenecks in business processes develop that cause a company to miss deadlines and wast e\nresources, an effective manager would most likely choose to?",
    "A": "implement an employee incentive program.",
    "B": "redesign the business processes.",
    "C": "invest in quality control.",
    "D": "speed up production.",
    "answer": "B: redesign the business processes.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following employees would most likely be described as \"innovative\" by their supervisor:?",
    "A": "Anthony, because he is usually quiet during brainstorming sessions",
    "B": "Elizabeth, because she gets frustrated when she needs to learn new skills",
    "C": "Jake, because he is always willing to adapt to changes during a project",
    "D": "Madison, because she prefers to stick to traditional ideas and processes",
    "answer": "C: Jake, because he is always willing to adapt to changes during a project",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "All of a firm's activities and how they function in relation to one another are known as",
    "A": "desired outputs.",
    "B": "efficiency standards.",
    "C": "communication goals.",
    "D": "business operations.",
    "answer": "D: business operations.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a global trend that might encourage an entrepreneur to consider international business opportunities:?",
    "A": "Flexible currency rates",
    "B": "Higher allowances",
    "C": "Lower tariffs",
    "D": "Enforceable trade agreements",
    "answer": "C: Lower tariffs",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of a legally binding contract:?",
    "A": "The contract must be written and signed.",
    "B": "The contract must include an expiration date.",
    "C": "Something of value must be exchanged.",
    "D": "One of the parties must be in agreement.",
    "answer": "C: Something of value must be exchanged.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a specification that a business might establish for selecting spreadsheet software programs:?",
    "A": "Digitally produce marketing data",
    "B": "Graphically display financial information",
    "C": "Regularly organize customer information",
    "D": "Electronically communicate data",
    "answer": "B: Graphically display financial information",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A sportswear company sells its products through only a couple sporting goods retailers in a specific region. This is an example of __________ distribution.",
    "A": "selective",
    "B": "intensive",
    "C": "multiple",
    "D": "exclusive",
    "answer": "A: selective",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Identifying market segments helps a business to develop appropriate",
    "A": "economic forecasts.",
    "B": "marketing strategies.",
    "C": "organizational records.",
    "D": "leadership styles.",
    "answer": "B: marketing strategies.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a company reduces the number of products in its product mix, the company is implementing a(n) __________ strategy.?",
    "A": "expansion",
    "B": "contraction",
    "C": "alteration",
    "D": "positioning",
    "answer": "B: contraction",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a technique that some businesses use to identify a target market for their products:?",
    "A": "Analyzing attitudes",
    "B": "Developing tests",
    "C": "Forecasting sales",
    "D": "Conducting surveys",
    "answer": "D: Conducting surveys",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an inexpensive method for entrepreneurs to collect information during concept\ndevelopment:?",
    "A": "Researching similar products",
    "B": "Introducing the product to a test market",
    "C": "Creating a product prototype",
    "D": "Conducting an observational study",
    "answer": "A: Researching similar products",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A market in which businesses sell products that are basically identical is an example of",
    "A": "perfect competition.",
    "B": "limited socialism.",
    "C": "free enterprise.",
    "D": "monopolistic competition.",
    "answer": "A: perfect competition.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An example of selling an intangible item to the ultimate consumer is the sale of",
    "A": "food to retailers by a food wholesaler.",
    "B": "a house by a housing producer.",
    "C": "health insurance by an insurance company.",
    "D": "jeans by a department store.",
    "answer": "C: health insurance by an insurance company.",
    "topic": "Risk management & insurance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The use of intermediaries enables producers to make larger profits because intermediaries",
    "A": "increase the number of retailer-to-producer contacts.",
    "B": "help reduce the per-unit costs of goods.",
    "C": "may sell more than the producer could sell on its own.",
    "D": "enable producers to use direct distribution.",
    "answer": "C: may sell more than the producer could sell on its own.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of ratio is used to measure the ability of a company to turn assets into cash?",
    "A": "Liquidity",
    "B": "Liability",
    "C": "Profitability",
    "D": "Activity",
    "answer": "A: Liquidity",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a customer engaging in habitual buying behavior:?",
    "A": "Lynnette buys paper for her computer printer at the local office-supply store.",
    "B": "Mike goes to three car dealerships and test-drives different vehicles to determine the one he likes best.",
    "C": "Porter conducts online research to evaluate several brands of computers and decides to purchase a Dell\nlaptop.",
    "D": "Gabriella tells her realtor that she wants to look at three-bedroom ranch homes on the northwest side of",
    "answer": "A: Lynnette buys paper for her computer printer at the local office-supply store.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The first step in developing a budget for a department/company is to",
    "A": "use the budget.",
    "B": "evaluate and revise the budget as necessary.",
    "C": "gather relevant data.",
    "D": "choose/create a budget format.",
    "answer": "D: choose/create a budget format.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The marketing objectives that a business develops for its marketing plan should lead to a(n)",
    "A": "decrease in taxes.",
    "B": "increase in prices.",
    "C": "decrease in costs.",
    "D": "increase in sales.",
    "answer": "D: increase in sales.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A primary reason for providing customer service is to increase",
    "A": "sales volume.",
    "B": "employee responsibility.",
    "C": "the number of salespeople.",
    "D": "the use of facilities.",
    "answer": "A: sales volume.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following results from an effective business exit strategy:?",
    "A": "A drop in the overall value of the business",
    "B": "A decrease in the future worth and stature of the business",
    "C": "Higher taxes on the owner's estate, spouse, or family",
    "D": "A smooth transition for management and stakeholders",
    "answer": "D: A smooth transition for management and stakeholders",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the best way to describe enterprise risk management:?",
    "A": "Firmwide strategy",
    "B": "Bottom-up approach",
    "C": "Divisive approach",
    "D": "Traditional strategy",
    "answer": "A: Firmwide strategy",
    "topic": "Risk management & insurance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one disadvantage of word-of-mouth advertising?",
    "A": "Low risk",
    "B": "High costs",
    "C": "Limited control",
    "D": "Extensive input",
    "answer": "C: Limited control",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A role model manager is someone who",
    "A": "forgets about mistakes.",
    "B": "leads by example.",
    "C": "follows their own rules.",
    "D": "takes all the credit.",
    "answer": "B: leads by example.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Matt has developed a new app. Before he launches it, he should",
    "A": "sell it to a larger company.",
    "B": "make sure it has no issues.",
    "C": "test it with a focus group.",
    "D": "generate new ideas.",
    "answer": "C: test it with a focus group.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Many business professionals say that the ability to sell your ideas",
    "A": "can lead to greater competition at work.",
    "B": "makes you an unattractive job candidate.",
    "C": "is not very important in today's workplace.",
    "D": "is one of the most critical skills for employees.",
    "answer": "D: is one of the most critical skills for employees.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When it comes to building a strategic relationship, it is important to?",
    "A": "be open to learning from others.",
    "B": "focus more on yourself and your needs.",
    "C": "avoid asking questions.",
    "D": "keep your ideas to yourself.",
    "answer": "A: be open to learning from others.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about feasibility studies:?",
    "A": "They are not useful for nonprofit organizations.",
    "B": "They are used by businesses in every industry.",
    "C": "They are especially important for government projects.",
    "D": "They are inexpensive to conduct.",
    "answer": "B: They are used by businesses in every industry.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jana noticed a problem while reviewing her company's monthly income statement. She verified that the total\nrevenue was $4,590 and the total expenses were $1,452. However, the income statement showed a net income total of $1,383. Which of the following reflects the correc t net income:",
    "A": "$3,138",
    "B": "$5,973",
    "C": "$3,381",
    "D": "$1,833",
    "answer": "A: $3,138",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a retailer is trying to clear its inventory of a particular product, which of the following would be the most\neffective type of sales promotion:",
    "A": "A sweepstakes for a new car",
    "B": "A booth at a trade show",
    "C": "A buy-one-get-one-free coupon",
    "D": "A contest that rewards the 100th customer",
    "answer": "C: A buy-one-get-one-free coupon",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a source of cash that businesses include in a cash flow statement:?",
    "A": "Assets",
    "B": "Expenses",
    "C": "Loans",
    "D": "Payables",
    "answer": "C: Loans",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The overall goal of promotion for most businesses is to",
    "A": "be factual.",
    "B": "be relevant.",
    "C": "inform salespeople.",
    "D": "increase sales.",
    "answer": "D: increase sales.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A company that wants to attract a different market segment by offering products that are similar to its cor e\nproduct line should consider a",
    "A": "shallow-variation mix.",
    "B": "product-mix extension.",
    "C": "product-line deletion.",
    "D": "wide-retention strategy.",
    "answer": "B: product-mix extension.",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses that develop and implement procedures for employees to follow to expedite task completion ar e\ntrying to establish efficient",
    "A": "supervision.",
    "B": "workflows.",
    "C": "production processes.",
    "D": "management techniques.",
    "answer": "B: workflows.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If an organization launched a business process redesign to reduce costs, what might result?",
    "A": "Increased spending",
    "B": "Improved efficiency",
    "C": "Opening more offices",
    "D": "Fewer layoffs",
    "answer": "B: Improved efficiency",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What requirement of a legally enforceable contract requires that both of the parties who are en tering into the contract are sane, sober, and of legal age?",
    "A": "Genuineness of assent",
    "B": "Consideration",
    "C": "Capacity",
    "D": "Legality of purpose",
    "answer": "C: Capacity",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The owner receives all of the profits of the business and can act quickly in making busin ess decisions when the form of business ownership is a",
    "A": "corporation.",
    "B": "partnership.",
    "C": "joint venture.",
    "D": "sole proprietorship.",
    "answer": "D: sole proprietorship.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the type of tax that businesses are required to collect from customers when they purchase certain goods or services:?",
    "A": "Estate",
    "B": "Income",
    "C": "Sales",
    "D": "Corporate",
    "answer": "C: Sales",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a condition that must exist for channels to be effective:?",
    "A": "Channel members must not share tasks.",
    "B": "They must have at least five members.",
    "C": "Channel members must have varying goals.",
    "D": "They must be properly managed.",
    "answer": "D: They must be properly managed.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a marketing function that can be performed by channel intermed iaries:?",
    "A": "Promoting products",
    "B": "Monitoring union activities",
    "C": "Training employees",
    "D": "Recruiting workers",
    "answer": "A: Promoting products",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A manufacturer of dishwashing soap has just invented a new type of soap that cleans better. The manufacturer should choose to distribute the soap through __________ distribution.",
    "A": "intensive",
    "B": "exclusive",
    "C": "inclusive",
    "D": "selective",
    "answer": "A: intensive",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of information does a well-written proposal include?",
    "A": "Vague goals",
    "B": "Specific benefits",
    "C": "Previous trends",
    "D": "Contingency data",
    "answer": "B: Specific benefits",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "There are several auto repair shops in town, but Patricia's stands out. Her auto repair shop does great work, but what really sets her shop apart is the customer service. Every customer is greeted by a friendl y employee, and s/he is given snacks and drinks while s/he waits for the repairs to be completed. The great customer service that people can expect from Patricia's business is considered her",
    "A": "vision.",
    "B": "tagline.",
    "C": "brand promise.",
    "D": "mission statement.",
    "answer": "C: brand promise.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Financial loss from investing time and money to comply with accounting standards i s an example of which strategic risk:",
    "A": "Changing customer needs",
    "B": "Reputation damage",
    "C": "Regulatory and political issues",
    "D": "Obsolescence",
    "answer": "C: Regulatory and political issues",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The government's mandating the use of unleaded gas in new cars is an example of",
    "A": "protecting specific businesses.",
    "B": "protecting the environment.",
    "C": "stabilizing the economy.",
    "D": "providing public goods.",
    "answer": "B: protecting the environment.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of business usually experiences economies of scale due to expanded operatio ns?",
    "A": "Large manufacturing plant",
    "B": "Monopoly",
    "C": "Individual financial planner",
    "D": "Small local retailer",
    "answer": "A: Large manufacturing plant",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesspeople who respect the unique customs and habits of their foreign customers are exhibi ting",
    "A": "communication skills.",
    "B": "stereotypical behavior.",
    "C": "cultural sensitivity.",
    "D": "language differences.",
    "answer": "C: cultural sensitivity.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "\"Yes, you'll save money instantly\" is an example of a statement with",
    "A": "threatening language.",
    "B": "an impersonal message.",
    "C": "persuasive words.",
    "D": "body language.",
    "answer": "C: persuasive words.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of a self-confident leader:?",
    "A": "S/He has the ability to share a vision.",
    "B": "S/He is truly invested in the work team.",
    "C": "S/He is decisive, even in uncertain circumstances.",
    "D": "S/He demonstrates empathy.",
    "answer": "C: S/He is decisive, even in uncertain circumstances.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for team members to feel a sense of \"ownership\" and engagement in the vi sion?",
    "A": "It's the only way they will become committed to it.",
    "B": "Leaders cannot force compliance from them.",
    "C": "They cannot be creative otherwise.",
    "D": "They are responsible for determining the vision.",
    "answer": "A: It's the only way they will become committed to it.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true regarding stakeholder expectations:?",
    "A": "Each group of stakeholders has different needs and expectations.",
    "B": "Stakeholder expectations are always financially driven.",
    "C": "All stakeholders want to exert authority over employees.",
    "D": "Stakeholder expectations always come second to customer needs.",
    "answer": "A: Each group of stakeholders has different needs and expectations.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Julio is starting a new business, and he has formed relationships with several successful local business owners. Which of the following is the best way to leverage these relationships to help his own business succeed:",
    "A": "Gaining inside marketing information",
    "B": "Persistently asking those business owners to invest in his company",
    "C": "Attending trade shows and conferences to make new connections",
    "D": "Sharing those businesses' content on social media",
    "answer": "D: Sharing those businesses' content on social media",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hazel started her own childcare network where she connects families to available babysitt ers at her school. Hazel could be described as a(n)",
    "A": "direct salesperson.",
    "B": "franchiser.",
    "C": "wholesaler.",
    "D": "entrepreneur.",
    "answer": "D: entrepreneur.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An entrepreneurial business owner must",
    "A": "dislike business planning.",
    "B": "be independently wealthy.",
    "C": "desire regular 40-hour work weeks.",
    "D": "have an adventurous spirit.",
    "answer": "D: have an adventurous spirit.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one reason that it is easier than ever for small businesses to engage in international trade?",
    "A": "Decreasing international middle class",
    "B": "Technological advances",
    "C": "Language barriers",
    "D": "Increased regulation",
    "answer": "B: Technological advances",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a global trend that might encourage an entrepreneur to consider i nternational business opportunities:?",
    "A": "Higher allowances",
    "B": "Lower tariffs",
    "C": "Enforceable trade agreements",
    "D": "Flexible currency rates",
    "answer": "B: Lower tariffs",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mara is facilitating a group brainstorming session to generate new product ideas for the company. Which of the following attitudes is important for Mara to demonstrate?",
    "A": "Judgmental",
    "B": "Neutral",
    "C": "Passive",
    "D": "Authoritarian",
    "answer": "B: Neutral",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Landon wants to start a home-based T-shirt printing business. Which of the following are the m ost critical equipment and supplies that Landon will need to get his business up and running?",
    "A": "T-shirts, thread, and display cases",
    "B": "Printing machine, display cases, and T-shirts",
    "C": "Artwork, T-shirts, and thread",
    "D": "T-shirts, printing machine, and artwork",
    "answer": "D: T-shirts, printing machine, and artwork",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A small-business owner might register for trademark protection for the company's",
    "A": "computer software.",
    "B": "invention.",
    "C": "trade secret.",
    "D": "logo.",
    "answer": "D: logo.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Evan does not want the legal obligation of repaying a loan and is willing to sha re profits with others. Which of the following options is Evan most likely to select to fund a new venture:",
    "A": "Private equity",
    "B": "Collateral savings",
    "C": "Trade credit",
    "D": "Community bank",
    "answer": "A: Private equity",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a primary factor that small-business owners should consider when deciding to hi re additional staff members?",
    "A": "Interview techniques",
    "B": "Payroll expenses",
    "C": "Training methods",
    "D": "Product standards",
    "answer": "B: Payroll expenses",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Al is thinking about moving his company's headquarters to another city, which woul d be expensive but closer to the raw materials needed for manufacturing. The benefit in moving is",
    "A": "demand.",
    "B": "proximity.",
    "C": "feasibility.",
    "D": "independence.",
    "answer": "B: proximity.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "All of a firm's activities and how they function in relation to one another are known as",
    "A": "business operations.",
    "B": "efficiency standards.",
    "C": "communication goals.",
    "D": "desired outputs.",
    "answer": "A: business operations.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because the MBC Company has one location that services the eastern part of the country and an other location that services the western part of the country, the company's work flow is organized b y",
    "A": "relationship.",
    "B": "work teams.",
    "C": "authority.",
    "D": "territory.",
    "answer": "D: territory.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Looking at problems from various points of view helps a small-business owner develop",
    "A": "practical arguments.",
    "B": "creative solutions.",
    "C": "unnecessary conflicts.",
    "D": "unpredictable results.",
    "answer": "B: creative solutions.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ellen wants to step back from the day-to-day activities of running her company. She decides to take the company to another level by selling public stock. One way Ellen can stay in volved in the company is by",
    "A": "arranging a tactical acquisition.",
    "B": "appointing a family member as president.",
    "C": "serving on the board of directors.",
    "D": "hiring her successor.",
    "answer": "C: serving on the board of directors.",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following categories of information are found on a balance sheet:?",
    "A": "Income, expenditures, profit",
    "B": "Assets, liabilities, owner's equity",
    "C": "Assets, liabilities, margin",
    "D": "Revenues, expenses, profit",
    "answer": "B: Assets, liabilities, owner's equity",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The balance sheet has a close relationship with the company's",
    "A": "mortgage.",
    "B": "income statement.",
    "C": "fair market value.",
    "D": "statement of financial position.",
    "answer": "B: income statement.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following phrases effectively describes a business's income statement:?",
    "A": "Income preview",
    "B": "Budget estimate",
    "C": "Cash-flow report",
    "D": "Financial picture",
    "answer": "D: Financial picture",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Managerial accounting differs from financial accounting because managerial accounting",
    "A": "helps people within a business rather than outside of the organization.",
    "B": "does not focus on planning and budgeting.",
    "C": "is governed by federal regulation.",
    "D": "has less impact on decision-making.",
    "answer": "A: helps people within a business rather than outside of the organization.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason why banks might be reluctant to lend money to a start-up business is bec ause the business",
    "A": "has a solid business plan.",
    "B": "will not have collateral.",
    "C": "has no record of repaying loans.",
    "D": "must incorporate first.",
    "answer": "C: has no record of repaying loans.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business has been running successfully for several years, what would be a probabl e next financial step?",
    "A": "Purchasing a second location",
    "B": "Acquiring start-up funds",
    "C": "Deciding on financial goals",
    "D": "Determining product prices",
    "answer": "A: Purchasing a second location",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Marginal analysis is a cost/benefit decision process that seeks to determine",
    "A": "the best qualities to look for in potential employees.",
    "B": "how a manager can cut costs.",
    "C": "the likely returns on a new investment.",
    "D": "profit-maximizing quantity of output.",
    "answer": "D: profit-maximizing quantity of output.",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What sales forecasting technique creates accurate forecasts for individual products?",
    "A": "Sales force composite",
    "B": "Delphi",
    "C": "Survey of buyer intentions",
    "D": "Jury of executive opinion",
    "answer": "A: Sales force composite",
    "topic": "Market research & marketing information"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An example of an operating expense that is included in a business's income statement is",
    "A": "inventory.",
    "B": "purchases.",
    "C": "commissions.",
    "D": "allowances.",
    "answer": "C: commissions.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following financial analysis methods is used to show the relationshi p of each component to the total within a single financial statement:?",
    "A": "Fundamental analysis",
    "B": "Horizontal analysis",
    "C": "Industry analysis",
    "D": "Vertical analysis",
    "answer": "D: Vertical analysis",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What staffing activity involves seeking out and attracting qualified potential job can didates?",
    "A": "Training",
    "B": "Recruiting",
    "C": "On-boarding",
    "D": "Interviewing",
    "answer": "B: Recruiting",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To screen job applications and employment r\u00e9sum\u00e9s, a business might use computer software that conducts text searches to scan for",
    "A": "typographical errors.",
    "B": "salary requirements.",
    "C": "numerical ratings.",
    "D": "key words.",
    "answer": "D: key words.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit of hiring the right employee for a job:?",
    "A": "Increased employee turnover",
    "B": "Increased risk of poor job performance",
    "C": "Decreased employee morale",
    "D": "Decreased cost of selection",
    "answer": "D: Decreased cost of selection",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the advantages to businesses of training staff is that it tends to increase",
    "A": "employee satisfaction.",
    "B": "operating expense.",
    "C": "compensation.",
    "D": "feedback.",
    "answer": "A: employee satisfaction.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an employee complaint that is related to a coworker:?",
    "A": "Sam complains to his production manager that the new materials are jamming the equipment.",
    "B": "Kelly advises Joe that a flaw in the computer system is creating inefficiencies in h er department.",
    "C": "Ann tells her boss that Brad talks loudly on the phone and distracts her ability to focus on work.",
    "D": "Mario confides in Paige that he disagrees with the wage freeze that the company ha s instituted.",
    "answer": "C: Ann tells her boss that Brad talks loudly on the phone and distracts her ability to focus on work.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "XYZ Company is interested in developing, producing, and selling a new product. Before it does s o, the company spends six months conducting marketing research. What are the primary advantage s of this course of action?",
    "A": "To delay the production process and increase labor costs",
    "B": "To increase costs and determine consumer dislikes",
    "C": "To predict trends and provide information to customers",
    "D": "To determine customer preferences and minimize losses",
    "answer": "D: To determine customer preferences and minimize losses",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is essential to all marketing research:?",
    "A": "Frequency",
    "B": "Primary data",
    "C": "Accuracy",
    "D": "Secondary data",
    "answer": "C: Accuracy",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The marketing function that helps marketers make decisions about what and to whom to sell i s",
    "A": "marketing-information management.",
    "B": "product/service management.",
    "C": "transportation.",
    "D": "promotion.",
    "answer": "A: marketing-information management.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A neighborhood grocery store has added a bakery. What element of marketing should the store use to attract customers from surrounding areas?",
    "A": "Product",
    "B": "Price",
    "C": "Place",
    "D": "Promotion",
    "answer": "D: Promotion",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In order for a market to exist, consumers must have an unfulfilled desire for a product and",
    "A": "know who makes the product.",
    "B": "know where the product is sold.",
    "C": "have financial resources.",
    "D": "have a specific brand preference.",
    "answer": "C: have financial resources.",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An important criterion to consider when identifying market segments is the __________ of the market.",
    "A": "age",
    "B": "size",
    "C": "gender",
    "D": "occupation",
    "answer": "B: size",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a potential weakness a manager might identify in a SWOT analysis?",
    "A": "High-quality products",
    "B": "Lack of management depth",
    "C": "Competitors failing",
    "D": "Low-cost foreign competition",
    "answer": "B: Lack of management depth",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As part of their marketing plans, what do businesses develop first that are intended to lea d to increased sales and revenue?",
    "A": "Objectives",
    "B": "Strategies",
    "C": "Tactics",
    "D": "Activities",
    "answer": "A: Objectives",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a specification that a business might establish for selecti ng spreadsheet software programs:?",
    "A": "Electronically communicate data",
    "B": "Graphically display financial information",
    "C": "Regularly organize customer information",
    "D": "Digitally produce marketing data",
    "answer": "B: Graphically display financial information",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How long are businesses required to keep their records?",
    "A": "On a seasonal basis",
    "B": "Varies greatly",
    "C": "Indefinitely",
    "D": "One year",
    "answer": "B: Varies greatly",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses often conduct environmental scans to determine if they should",
    "A": "make staffing adjustments.",
    "B": "expand into other markets.",
    "C": "follow government regulations.",
    "D": "improve their computer systems.",
    "answer": "B: expand into other markets.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a benefit to a tour operator who makes business decisions by analyzing stati stical information?",
    "A": "Improved performance",
    "B": "Lower demand",
    "C": "Increased competition",
    "D": "Lower outputs",
    "answer": "A: Improved performance",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because operations managers control so much of a business's money, they must focus on",
    "A": "keeping costs low.",
    "B": "hiring the best employees.",
    "C": "creating effective advertising campaigns.",
    "D": "generating publicity.",
    "answer": "A: keeping costs low.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Obtaining goods that will satisfy the needs and wants of a business's customers is a f unction of",
    "A": "advertising.",
    "B": "selling.",
    "C": "marketing.",
    "D": "purchasing.",
    "answer": "D: purchasing.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for businesses to have efficient production?",
    "A": "To be competitive",
    "B": "To remain flexible",
    "C": "To pay employees",
    "D": "To buy resources",
    "answer": "A: To be competitive",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do managers need to do to develop and maintain the level of quality that customers expec t?",
    "A": "Obtain industry information",
    "B": "Monitor all aspects of the business",
    "C": "Consider the type of competition",
    "D": "Prepare an operating budget",
    "answer": "B: Monitor all aspects of the business",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Expenses such as payroll and rent that are necessary to the running of a business are called __________ expenses.",
    "A": "operating",
    "B": "fixed",
    "C": "variable",
    "D": "liability",
    "answer": "A: operating",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business negotiates a two-year lease on 2,250 square feet of space for $2.60 per square foot wi th an option on a third year at a 5% increase in rent. What will the monthly rent be if the busin ess extends the lease for a third year?",
    "A": "$6,265.50",
    "B": "$5,976.00",
    "C": "$5,850.00",
    "D": "$6,142.50",
    "answer": "D: $6,142.50",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Most company budgets are based on",
    "A": "net profit.",
    "B": "expenses.",
    "C": "sales.",
    "D": "gross profit.",
    "answer": "C: sales.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following situations would supply chain managers encounter during the final stage of supply chain management:?",
    "A": "A customer returns a defective product.",
    "B": "The company finds reliable suppliers.",
    "C": "The business plans to deliver goods to customers.",
    "D": "Managers develop a supply chain strategy.",
    "answer": "A: A customer returns a defective product.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Claire doing when she reviews a report that compares the purchase transactions of the company's four largest customers?",
    "A": "Conducting a sales analysis",
    "B": "Preparing a purchasing forecast",
    "C": "Organizing an inventory report",
    "D": "Analyzing service performance",
    "answer": "A: Conducting a sales analysis",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Business process thinking is meant to help companies",
    "A": "achieve goals and serve customers.",
    "B": "hire employees and fill roles.",
    "C": "process payroll and compensate employees.",
    "D": "enforce safety standards.",
    "answer": "A: achieve goals and serve customers.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When bottlenecks in business processes develop that cause a company to miss deadlines an d waste resources, an effective manager would most likely choose to?",
    "A": "invest in quality control.",
    "B": "redesign the business processes.",
    "C": "implement an employee incentive program.",
    "D": "speed up production.",
    "answer": "B: redesign the business processes.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the main external factors that may cause a firm to change its business processes is",
    "A": "desire for growth.",
    "B": "competition.",
    "C": "low employee morale.",
    "D": "high operating costs.",
    "answer": "B: competition.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sandra is a manager at a distribution plant. Lately, her customers have been complaining abo ut timely deliveries. Which area of the business does Sandra need to focus on to ensure on-time delivery?",
    "A": "The sales force",
    "B": "Inventory control",
    "C": "Supply chain management",
    "D": "Production",
    "answer": "C: Supply chain management",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which step of the decision-making model involves identifying what you want to do?",
    "A": "Gathering the information you need",
    "B": "Establishing decision criteria",
    "C": "Determining what you need to know",
    "D": "Pinpointing your objective",
    "answer": "D: Pinpointing your objective",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit of corporate governance:?",
    "A": "It encourages transparency.",
    "B": "It decreases investor confidence.",
    "C": "It creates a less definable brand.",
    "D": "It maximizes corruption.",
    "answer": "A: It encourages transparency.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Members of a board of directors are",
    "A": "required to be stockholders.",
    "B": "elected by stockholders.",
    "C": "a business's vendors.",
    "D": "not able to make decisions.",
    "answer": "B: elected by stockholders.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following most likely led to a greater emphasis on governance structures in rece nt years:?",
    "A": "New technology in the industry",
    "B": "Competitor saturation",
    "C": "Stock market crash",
    "D": "Accounting fraud",
    "answer": "D: Accounting fraud",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Performances standards should be",
    "A": "informally discussed.",
    "B": "subjective.",
    "C": "measurable.",
    "D": "extremely challenging.",
    "answer": "C: measurable.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Product pricing is affected by transportation costs, which are factors related to the marketing element of",
    "A": "competition.",
    "B": "promotion.",
    "C": "place.",
    "D": "selling.",
    "answer": "C: place.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Companies X, Y, and Z determine the selling price of widgets because these companies are the only ones who market widgets. This is an example of",
    "A": "monopolistic competition.",
    "B": "an oligopolistic market.",
    "C": "pure competition.",
    "D": "a true monopoly.",
    "answer": "B: an oligopolistic market.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When evaluating customers' experiences, a company should keep in mind that customers are most often influenced by their interactions with the company's?",
    "A": "negotiation committee.",
    "B": "suppliers.",
    "C": "labor union.",
    "D": "employees.",
    "answer": "D: employees.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Having a narrow product mix allows a company to",
    "A": "specialize in specific product lines.",
    "B": "mass market its products.",
    "C": "produce less efficiently.",
    "D": "appeal to customers with a variety of needs.",
    "answer": "A: specialize in specific product lines.",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ways that a business's website can provide customer-service support are by offering",
    "A": "chat rooms, account numbers, and financial information.",
    "B": "free delivery, email options, and credit authorizations.",
    "C": "product/service updates, FAQs page, and an online help desk.",
    "D": "online billing, sales reports, and toll-free telephone number.",
    "answer": "C: product/service updates, FAQs page, and an online help desk.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business offers services such as an information desk, child-friendly restroom s, and a lost-and-found department, it is providing customers with __________ services.?",
    "A": "shopping",
    "B": "convenience",
    "C": "community",
    "D": "impulse",
    "answer": "B: convenience",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is one of the main functions of promotion in the advertising industry:?",
    "A": "Marketing",
    "B": "Persuading",
    "C": "Branding",
    "D": "Retailing",
    "answer": "B: Persuading",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following media could increase a business's sales by reaching people who are driv ing home from work:?",
    "A": "Email",
    "B": "Publicity",
    "C": "Advertising",
    "D": "Radio",
    "answer": "D: Radio",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mark doesn't have much money to promote his new restaurant, so he focuses on inviting a few customers in for a special dinner in hopes that they will post favorable reviews online and tel l their family and friends about their great meals. Mark is using __________ marketing.",
    "A": "broadcast",
    "B": "direct mail",
    "C": "grassroots",
    "D": "cause",
    "answer": "C: grassroots",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses often use direct advertising strategies because",
    "A": "the promotional message reaches a larger group of people.",
    "B": "they can select and reach qualified prospects.",
    "C": "direct advertising is less expensive than other forms of promotion.",
    "D": "it reduces the need to include other elements in the promotional mix.",
    "answer": "B: they can select and reach qualified prospects.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Skintastic Cosmetic Company implemented a challenging sales promotion in which its ind ependent sales consultants could earn bonuses, prizes, and vacations. This is an example of a company using __________ as a sales incentive.",
    "A": "sweepstakes",
    "B": "push money",
    "C": "cooperative advertising",
    "D": "loyalty programs",
    "answer": "B: push money",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The use of communications channels in public relations activities is an important part of",
    "A": "advertising an image.",
    "B": "marketing products.",
    "C": "providing information.",
    "D": "targeting customers.",
    "answer": "C: providing information.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Francine likes the auto shop where she takes her car for an oil change because it has a comfortable waiting room with good magazines. This illustrates which important characteristic of qual ity service providers?",
    "A": "Responsiveness",
    "B": "Reliability",
    "C": "Tangibles",
    "D": "Assurance",
    "answer": "C: Tangibles",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding the relationship between risk and busines s objectives:?",
    "A": "Risks help businesses determine objectives.",
    "B": "Objectives should never be modified because of risk.",
    "C": "Effective business objectives are not risky.",
    "D": "The more objectives a business has, the less risk it faces.",
    "answer": "A: Risks help businesses determine objectives.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tyrese and his team are creating a list of their company's critical enterprise-wide ris ks. They are compiling",
    "A": "a risk control.",
    "B": "a risk assessment.",
    "C": "enterprise risk management.",
    "D": "a risk inventory.",
    "answer": "D: a risk inventory.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following situations is most likely to result in long-term, increased sal es for a business:?",
    "A": "Raising the price of its current products",
    "B": "Constantly providing new choices for consumers",
    "C": "Lowering the price of its current products",
    "D": "Eliminating a slow-selling product line",
    "answer": "B: Constantly providing new choices for consumers",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a company objective that might be developed by top\nmanagement:?",
    "A": "To improve the collection process",
    "B": "To maintain or increase market share",
    "C": "To maintain the billing cycle",
    "D": "To hold weekly sales meetings",
    "answer": "B: To maintain or increase market share",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business should consider the impact that changes in the environment will have on the business's\nmarketing mix because",
    "A": "most businesses want to be reactive.",
    "B": "the business can change its marketing mix.",
    "C": "the marketing mix is affected by technology.",
    "D": "government regulations can increase costs.",
    "answer": "B: the business can change its marketing mix.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which component of the business plan requires considerable time and external research?",
    "A": "Market analysis",
    "B": "Executive summary",
    "C": "Strategy and implementation",
    "D": "Appendices",
    "answer": "A: Market analysis",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What company has the highest sales-to-receivables ratio based on the following information: Company A\nhas sales of $250,000 and accounts receivable of $20,000; Company B has sales of $275,000 and\naccounts receivable of $25,000; Company C has sales of $300,000 and accounts receivable of $30,0 00;\nand Company D has sales of $290,000 and accounts receivable of $32,000.?",
    "A": "Company A",
    "B": "Company B",
    "C": "Company C",
    "D": "Company D",
    "answer": "A: Company A",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to track the performance of a business plan?",
    "A": "To establish an operating strategy",
    "B": "To find out if products are selling",
    "C": "To determine its proposed mission",
    "D": "To provide investment information",
    "answer": "B: To find out if products are selling",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For successful innovation to occur, employees must be willing to __________ while de veloping ideas.",
    "A": "learn",
    "B": "teach",
    "C": "avoid results",
    "D": "work alone",
    "answer": "A: learn",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a company wants to ensure that changes are implemented in the best possible way and that th ose\nchanges will lead to long-term benefits, it should use the __________ approach.",
    "A": "change avoidance",
    "B": "problem solving",
    "C": "change management",
    "D": "solution finding",
    "answer": "C: change management",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Basic torts relating to businesses often involve disputes concerning",
    "A": "emotional stress.",
    "B": "assaults.",
    "C": "defamation.",
    "D": "contracts.",
    "answer": "D: contracts.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of a business-format franchise:?",
    "A": "The name of the business is chosen by the franchisee.",
    "B": "Products are bought directly from the supplier.",
    "C": "It is the least popular franchise arrangement.",
    "D": "Continuous assistance is provided by the franchisor.",
    "answer": "D: Continuous assistance is provided by the franchisor.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Limited liability, indefinite length of life, ease of expansion, legal entity, and t ransfer of ownership are considered advantages of a",
    "A": "sole proprietorship.",
    "B": "partnership.",
    "C": "trade union.",
    "D": "corporation.",
    "answer": "D: corporation.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Channels of distribution benefit consumers by",
    "A": "increasing profits for businesses.",
    "B": "lowering the prices of all consumer products.",
    "C": "raising the quality of all consumer products.",
    "D": "making a variety of products available to them.",
    "answer": "D: making a variety of products available to them.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For which of the following markets would producers use a short channel of distribution:",
    "A": "Local consumers",
    "B": "Generation X",
    "C": "Baby boomers",
    "D": "Senior citizens",
    "answer": "A: Local consumers",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a business considers where the consumers are and who they are before selecting a channel of distribution, the business is considering the __________ factor.",
    "A": "human",
    "B": "promotion",
    "C": "market",
    "D": "sales",
    "answer": "C: market",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do business employees often need to do before they are able to write proposals?",
    "A": "Research the problem",
    "B": "Analyze personal biases",
    "C": "Contact the customer",
    "D": "Evaluate technical skills",
    "answer": "A: Research the problem",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a manager developing a policy that impacts custom er relations:?",
    "A": "Increasing use of security devices",
    "B": "Extending business hours on weekends",
    "C": "Revising bookkeeping procedures",
    "D": "Scheduling employees' work hours",
    "answer": "B: Extending business hours on weekends",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should a successful brand promise be able to do?",
    "A": "Customize the product for each customer",
    "B": "Clarify the company's processes",
    "C": "Communicate an appealing benefit",
    "D": "Convey a high-quality image",
    "answer": "C: Communicate an appealing benefit",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is one way that freedom in a private enterprise system is limited b y laws:?",
    "A": "Certain occupations must be licensed.",
    "B": "All workers must take ability tests.",
    "C": "Specific pay scales are regulated.",
    "D": "Employees must register with the state.",
    "answer": "A: Certain occupations must be licensed.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During the month of July, sales at Handy's Shoe Mart totaled $2,500. The cost of the shoes was $1,02 5. The owner paid $866 for supplies, insurance, rent, and utilities during the month. The $609 left over represents the owner's",
    "A": "net profit.",
    "B": "gross profit.",
    "C": "sales income.",
    "D": "operating expenses.",
    "answer": "A: net profit.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Non-corporations are taxed as pass-through entities, meaning that",
    "A": "profits and losses are claimed on owners' personal tax returns.",
    "B": "they do not have to pay payroll taxes.",
    "C": "their income tax rates are lower than those of corporations.",
    "D": "they pay only state and local taxes.",
    "answer": "A: profits and losses are claimed on owners' personal tax returns.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following activities is an example of preparing before attempting to sell an idea:?",
    "A": "Explaining solutions to audience needs",
    "B": "Determining the details of your idea",
    "C": "Overcoming objections from the audience",
    "D": "Affirming the audience's decision to \"buy\"",
    "answer": "B: Determining the details of your idea",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Managers are more likely to be able to persuade employees to follow new procedures if the managers have",
    "A": "organizational skills.",
    "B": "credibility.",
    "C": "enthusiasm.",
    "D": "self-motivation.",
    "answer": "B: credibility.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ali wants to negotiate with her boss to take on more job responsibilities. Before approach ing her boss, Ali needs to determine her boss's position and",
    "A": "abilities.",
    "B": "interests.",
    "C": "standards.",
    "D": "procedures.",
    "answer": "B: interests.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After writing your personal vision, what must you do to achieve it?",
    "A": "Commit to your vision through hard work and dedication.",
    "B": "Put your vision in a safe space and look at it again in five years.",
    "C": "Get the highest-paying job that you can find out of high school.",
    "D": "Spend all of your free time working on self-improvement.",
    "answer": "A: Commit to your vision through hard work and dedication.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ryan keeps a list of his goals to remind himself of what he's working toward. Which tip for s mart goal setting is Ryan following?",
    "A": "Putting goals in writing",
    "B": "Tying goals to a timetable",
    "C": "Making goals specific",
    "D": "Making goals difficult but possible",
    "answer": "A: Putting goals in writing",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The future that you desire to create is known as a",
    "A": "mission statement.",
    "B": "goal.",
    "C": "prediction.",
    "D": "vision.",
    "answer": "D: vision.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The entrepreneurial discovery process that involves finding a way to meet an existing de mand by inventing new products from available resources is based on",
    "A": "science.",
    "B": "medicine.",
    "C": "psychology.",
    "D": "physics.",
    "answer": "A: science.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Dan is in the process of determining the types of computer software and telephone service that will best suit his new business and get it up and running. Dan is considering his business's",
    "A": "financial constraints.",
    "B": "technical needs.",
    "C": "competitive advantage.",
    "D": "staffing requirements.",
    "answer": "B: technical needs.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true about business startup requirements:?",
    "A": "New business owners usually need to register for patent protection.",
    "B": "The financial needs to start a new business depend on the nature of the venture.",
    "C": "Purchasing a franchise is usually easy and inexpensive for startup business owners.",
    "D": "Equipment is the least expensive requirement for a startup business.",
    "answer": "B: The financial needs to start a new business depend on the nature of the venture.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for entrepreneurs to talk with industry experts when developing new business concepts?",
    "A": "The industry experts usually improve your management skills.",
    "B": "The industry experts typically provide useful information.",
    "C": "The industry experts commonly enhance your confidence.",
    "D": "The industry experts frequently offer financial support.",
    "answer": "B: The industry experts typically provide useful information.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If an entrepreneur obtains a commercial bank loan to finance a new venture, s/he is often required t o",
    "A": "provide collateral.",
    "B": "close savings accounts.",
    "C": "relinquish contracts.",
    "D": "charge the prime-interest rate.",
    "answer": "A: provide collateral.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To determine their human resource needs, new business owners often find it helpful to",
    "A": "list all the tasks involved in operating the business.",
    "B": "ask a technical recruiter for advice.",
    "C": "hire consultants or freelancers.",
    "D": "allocate funds for additional payroll taxes.",
    "answer": "A: list all the tasks involved in operating the business.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The type of capital resources that a startup business needs to begin operating usually depends on t he",
    "A": "vendors' lead time.",
    "B": "location.",
    "C": "owner's preferences.",
    "D": "industry.",
    "answer": "D: industry.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true about new venture risk-taking:?",
    "A": "When an entrepreneur seeks a high profit, the risk is usually higher.",
    "B": "When the entrepreneur seeks to limit risk, the reward tends to increase.",
    "C": "An entrepreneur's financial risk is not closely related to rewards.",
    "D": "The entrepreneur who does not care about profit is a high risk-taker.",
    "answer": "A: When an entrepreneur seeks a high profit, the risk is usually higher.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Small-business owners develop and use operating procedures so that everyday tasks are performed in a(n) __________ way.",
    "A": "innovative",
    "B": "imprecise",
    "C": "diverse",
    "D": "standard",
    "answer": "D: standard",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To develop repeat business and customer loyalty, a business owner might",
    "A": "update equipment.",
    "B": "increase prices.",
    "C": "ridicule the competition.",
    "D": "offer a new service.",
    "answer": "D: offer a new service.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "By joining a community organization, such as the local chamber of commerce, an en trepreneur can network with others to",
    "A": "evaluate personal skills and abilities.",
    "B": "obtain selling experience.",
    "C": "identify new venture opportunities.",
    "D": "improve goods and services.",
    "answer": "C: identify new venture opportunities.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determine if the following statement is true or false: When developing an exit strategy for an entrepreneurial venture, the most important consideration is finding a suitable buyer.",
    "A": "False, there are many factors to consider, such as company valuation and personal goals.",
    "B": "True, if the buyer is inexperienced, the business risks monetary losses and long-term failure.",
    "C": "False, the most important factor that an entrepreneur should consider is profitability.",
    "D": "True, the valuation of a business is dependent on the buyer's financial resources.",
    "answer": "A: False, there are many factors to consider, such as company valuation and personal goals.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an intangible asset:?",
    "A": "Equipment",
    "B": "Inventory",
    "C": "Office building",
    "D": "Accounts receivable",
    "answer": "D: Accounts receivable",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of a profit-and-loss statement:?",
    "A": "Is the same as a balance sheet",
    "B": "Summarizes expenses and revenue from sales",
    "C": "Shows the owner's financial position",
    "D": "Lists assets and liabilities",
    "answer": "B: Summarizes expenses and revenue from sales",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In managerial accounting, the number of hours that a business runs its machinery during th e production process is classified as a(n)",
    "A": "production output.",
    "B": "cost driver.",
    "C": "unexpected expense.",
    "D": "inflexible transaction.",
    "answer": "B: cost driver.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses often obtain cash to produce and sell goods by borrowing against their",
    "A": "current liabilities.",
    "B": "accounts receivable.",
    "C": "operating expenses.",
    "D": "promissory notes.",
    "answer": "B: accounts receivable.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When determining financing needs, what factor should businesses consider that will help decide whether they can repay the debt?",
    "A": "Liquidity",
    "B": "Depreciation",
    "C": "Equity",
    "D": "Inventory",
    "answer": "A: Liquidity",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a risk a business might face if it obtains a long-term loan from a financial institution and pays off the loan before it is due:?",
    "A": "Being charged a penalty",
    "B": "Losing interest on the account",
    "C": "Paying a processing fee",
    "D": "Receiving a variable rate",
    "answer": "A: Being charged a penalty",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do lending institutions carefully evaluate how well a business meets certain cri teria before making a loan?",
    "A": "To improve relations",
    "B": "To provide service",
    "C": "To prevent theft",
    "D": "To reduce risk",
    "answer": "D: To reduce risk",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following payback periods in a cost/benefit analysis would businesse s prefer if all other things were equal:?",
    "A": "2 years",
    "B": "1 year",
    "C": "3 years",
    "D": "4 years",
    "answer": "B: 1 year",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An example of an internal change that could affect a business's sales forecast is a change in t he",
    "A": "length of a national recession.",
    "B": "number of competitors in the market.",
    "C": "size of the sales force.",
    "D": "levels of consumer spending.",
    "answer": "C: size of the sales force.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ethan is developing common-size financial statements so that he can compare financi al performance across several different companies. Ethan is conducting __________ analysis.",
    "A": "horizontal",
    "B": "vertical",
    "C": "ratio",
    "D": "trend",
    "answer": "B: vertical",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jana noticed a problem while reviewing her company's monthly income statement. She verified that the total revenue was $4,590 and the total expenses were $1,452. However, the income statement showed a net income total of $1,383. Which of the following reflects the correct net income:",
    "A": "$3,381",
    "B": "$5,973",
    "C": "$3,138",
    "D": "$1,833",
    "answer": "C: $3,138",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do interviewers usually focus on asking questions that are related to a job applicant's p erformance?",
    "A": "To understand complaints",
    "B": "To take remedial action",
    "C": "To determine qualifications",
    "D": "To plan future training",
    "answer": "C: To determine qualifications",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If employees are fired because their conduct is in serious violation of company polici es, they are being terminated for",
    "A": "incompetence.",
    "B": "performance.",
    "C": "resigning.",
    "D": "cause.",
    "answer": "D: cause.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it often necessary to provide employees with additional training?",
    "A": "To increase socialization",
    "B": "To improve performance",
    "C": "To analyze diversity",
    "D": "To identify sensitivity",
    "answer": "B: To improve performance",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a supervisor evaluates an employee's performance, the evaluation should be based o n the __________ standards.?",
    "A": "organization's",
    "B": "supervisor's",
    "C": "competition's",
    "D": "employee's",
    "answer": "A: organization's",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is one way that businesses use marketing information:?",
    "A": "To predict change",
    "B": "To analyze data",
    "C": "To develop surveys",
    "D": "To conduct research",
    "answer": "A: To predict change",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of the data collection step in marketing resear ch:?",
    "A": "The least expensive step in marketing research",
    "B": "The least tedious step in marketing research",
    "C": "The step in which the most mistakes are made",
    "D": "The step that is most interesting to researchers",
    "answer": "C: The step in which the most mistakes are made",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a durable good:?",
    "A": "House",
    "B": "Haircut",
    "C": "Gasoline",
    "D": "Hamburger",
    "answer": "A: House",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Motives, perception, attitude, lifestyle, personality, and abilities are _________ _ factors influencing consumer behavior.",
    "A": "political",
    "B": "social",
    "C": "psychological",
    "D": "economic",
    "answer": "C: psychological",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Business goals are accomplished by means of marketing",
    "A": "salespeople.",
    "B": "budgets.",
    "C": "profit.",
    "D": "strategies.",
    "answer": "D: strategies.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Products that appeal to the majority of customers are often sold through __________ marketing efforts.",
    "A": "segmented",
    "B": "mass",
    "C": "demographic",
    "D": "psychographic",
    "answer": "B: mass",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An important part of a market analysis involves collecting __________ information.",
    "A": "confidential",
    "B": "geographic",
    "C": "employee",
    "D": "property",
    "answer": "B: geographic",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason why it is important to accurately forecast sales for a marketing plan is because t he forecast is the basis of other",
    "A": "business reports.",
    "B": "pricing strategies.",
    "C": "operational activities.",
    "D": "management techniques.",
    "answer": "C: operational activities.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a strategy for linking performance measures to financial outcom es:?",
    "A": "Analyzing click-through rates",
    "B": "Developing advertising budgets",
    "C": "Paying for direct-mail pieces",
    "D": "Maintaining sales receipts",
    "answer": "A: Analyzing click-through rates",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of software do many businesses require be installed on computer systems as a s ecurity feature?",
    "A": "Reality",
    "B": "Firewall",
    "C": "Spider",
    "D": "Media",
    "answer": "B: Firewall",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The FPD Company keeps copies of its brochures, catalogs, and flyers on file for future reference. This is an example of a company that is maintaining __________ records.",
    "A": "inventory",
    "B": "legal",
    "C": "promotional",
    "D": "asset",
    "answer": "C: promotional",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is most likely to be a dynamic element of a business's external envi ronment:?",
    "A": "Decrease in personnel",
    "B": "Increase in competition",
    "C": "Renewed emphasis on training",
    "D": "New quality control measures",
    "answer": "B: Increase in competition",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "James needs to hire a bookkeeper for his growing business. To determine the new employe e's salary, James obtained pay data from five companies in his industry that are similar in size. The res earch indicated the following: Company A pays $31,205; Company B pays $29,995; Compan y C pays $34,800; Company D pays $42,500; and Company E pays $36,500. James decided to set his bookkeeper's sal ary at $35,000. What measure of central tendency did James use to set his new employee's salary?",
    "A": "Mode",
    "B": "Mean",
    "C": "Range",
    "D": "Median",
    "answer": "B: Mean",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hill Industries uses specific criteria to evaluate vendor performance, including on-time delivery rate, return rate, and number of customer complaints. These metrics are also known as",
    "A": "consensus scales.",
    "B": "performance indicators.",
    "C": "economic indicators.",
    "D": "return on capital.",
    "answer": "B: performance indicators.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business converts inputs into outputs through its __________ activities.",
    "A": "accounting",
    "B": "management",
    "C": "marketing",
    "D": "production",
    "answer": "D: production",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is often the role of management in the achievement of quality in a business?",
    "A": "To assign blame",
    "B": "To lead the effort",
    "C": "To judge the staff",
    "D": "To eliminate conflict",
    "answer": "B: To lead the effort",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a fixed operating expense:?",
    "A": "Insurance",
    "B": "Sales commissions",
    "C": "Advertising",
    "D": "Travel expenses",
    "answer": "A: Insurance",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What information does a business always need to have when it conducts a break-even analysi s?",
    "A": "Fixed costs and depreciation rates",
    "B": "Variable costs and fixed costs",
    "C": "Production time and variable costs",
    "D": "Production time and depreciation rates",
    "answer": "B: Variable costs and fixed costs",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following should a business consider when negotiating a service or maintenance contract on a piece of equipment:?",
    "A": "Does the cost of the contract exceed the cost of possible repairs?",
    "B": "Is training and technical assistance available?",
    "C": "How much profit does the seller make on the contract?",
    "D": "Does the equipment require installation?",
    "answer": "A: Does the cost of the contract exceed the cost of possible repairs?",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a situation in which a business could use the budget inf ormation to make operating changes:?",
    "A": "Total revenues exceed projected costs.",
    "B": "Estimated sales exceed actual sales.",
    "C": "Expected profits are increasing.",
    "D": "Accounts receivable are on target.",
    "answer": "B: Estimated sales exceed actual sales.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To effectively manage a supply chain, companies should",
    "A": "introduce frequent changes to the production process.",
    "B": "ignore underperforming suppliers and distributors.",
    "C": "monitor the performance of all supply chain partners.",
    "D": "launch new products through multiple suppliers.",
    "answer": "C: monitor the performance of all supply chain partners.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An employee is comparing income statements from the past three years to evaluate changes and tren ds in the business's revenue. What type of business analysis is the employee conducti ng?",
    "A": "Production",
    "B": "Financial",
    "C": "Information management",
    "D": "Sales",
    "answer": "B: Financial",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before assigning a new project to her employees, Joanna establishes the steps that her staff needs t o take to complete the project. Joanna is utilizing",
    "A": "human resource planning.",
    "B": "business process thinking.",
    "C": "agile project management.",
    "D": "change management.",
    "answer": "B: business process thinking.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A manufacturing company is required by the local government to dispose of its waste in an environmentally safe way. This is an example of how process design can be affected by ____ ______ factors.",
    "A": "human",
    "B": "regulatory",
    "C": "technological",
    "D": "natural",
    "answer": "B: regulatory",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following situations describes a business process changing due to tec hnological factors:?",
    "A": "A manufacturing company purchases a new software program to run its machines.",
    "B": "A small general store offers more discounts to compete with a new shopping mall.",
    "C": "A waste treatment plant changes its disposal method to align with environmental law.",
    "D": "A family-owned restaurant opens a second location in an effort to expand its brand.",
    "answer": "A: A manufacturing company purchases a new software program to run its machines.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding the relationship between a business's supply chain management and its performance:?",
    "A": "Good supply chain management leads to unsustainable business practices.",
    "B": "Good supply chain management leads to decreased value for the customer.",
    "C": "Poor supply chain management can result in customer satisfaction.",
    "D": "Poor supply chain management can result in customer dissatisfaction.",
    "answer": "D: Poor supply chain management can result in customer dissatisfaction.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chad is buying a new car. Although the first car is a great deal and a more practical choice, he just lov es the look of the second car. As a result, he decides to purchase the second car. His decision is based on which of the following internal factors:",
    "A": "Insight or intuition",
    "B": "Experience",
    "C": "Framing",
    "D": "Emotion",
    "answer": "D: Emotion",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Time management helps to reduce stress because it",
    "A": "provides less time for rest and relaxation.",
    "B": "increases feelings of pressure and tension.",
    "C": "encourages procrastination in planning necessary activities.",
    "D": "allows adequate time for personal and professional activities.",
    "answer": "D: allows adequate time for personal and professional activities.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who typically reviews and approves the guidelines for running a corporation, which are als o known as corporate governance policies?",
    "A": "The investors",
    "B": "The shareholders",
    "C": "The management team",
    "D": "The board of directors",
    "answer": "D: The board of directors",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the relationship between shareholders and the board of directors?",
    "A": "The shareholders pay dividends to the board of directors.",
    "B": "The board of directors represents the shareholders.",
    "C": "The shareholders make decisions for the board of directors.",
    "D": "The board of directors holds the shareholders accountable.",
    "answer": "B: The board of directors represents the shareholders.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An organization should include independent members on its board of directors because they",
    "A": "provide an objective perspective.",
    "B": "represent the interests of management.",
    "C": "understand the company's inner workings.",
    "D": "are less likely to act unethically.",
    "answer": "A: provide an objective perspective.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When buyers and sellers have agreed on a value for a product, they have established the?",
    "A": "price policy.",
    "B": "exchange price.",
    "C": "equilibrium price.",
    "D": "price line.",
    "answer": "B: exchange price.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "True or false: In determining the selling price of a good or service, most of the factors to be consi dered by the seller are internal to the business.",
    "A": "True, most factors affecting price are internal to the business.",
    "B": "False, most factors affecting price are not controlled by the firm.",
    "C": "True, most factors affecting price are directly controlled by the business.",
    "D": "False, most factors affecting price are directly controlled by the business.",
    "answer": "B: False, most factors affecting price are not controlled by the firm.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A product idea is feasible if it",
    "A": "meets sales quotas.",
    "B": "creates a competitive advantage.",
    "C": "costs a lot to produce.",
    "D": "is a durable good.",
    "answer": "B: creates a competitive advantage.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Terry, a company buyer, has the job of choosing a particular assortment of products that will meet the market's needs and the company's goals. Terry is responsible for the company's product",
    "A": "mix.",
    "B": "item.",
    "C": "line.",
    "D": "sales.",
    "answer": "A: mix.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business manager who wants to increase the number of items the business offers needs to dec ide whether the new items will be compatible with the business's",
    "A": "level of service.",
    "B": "patronage motives.",
    "C": "current product mix.",
    "D": "advertising objectives.",
    "answer": "C: current product mix.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do many businesses identify and strive to improve in order to attract customers and be competitive?",
    "A": "Commission plans",
    "B": "Service standards",
    "C": "Personal characteristics",
    "D": "Operating quotas",
    "answer": "B: Service standards",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of promotional media is a business using when it sends out a postcard telling customers who recently purchased products that the business is adding a new line of products?",
    "A": "Participative",
    "B": "Sales letter",
    "C": "Persuasive",
    "D": "Direct mail",
    "answer": "D: Direct mail",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ariel, who designs and sells a line of purses and tote bags, recently sent free totes bag to l ocal female news anchors. Ariel's goal is to have others see the local celebrities carrying the tote bags to generate interest in her product. What form of word-of-mouth marketing is Ariel using?",
    "A": "Product seeding",
    "B": "Celebrity testimonial",
    "C": "Cause marketing",
    "D": "Social media applications",
    "answer": "A: Product seeding",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An advantage to using direct marketing to communicate product information is that the business can",
    "A": "expect a majority of recipients to respond to the message.",
    "B": "effectively appeal to a mass audience.",
    "C": "customize the messages.",
    "D": "save money by personalizing offers.",
    "answer": "C: customize the messages.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Samples, premiums, and advertising specialties are examples of __________ used in sales promoti on.",
    "A": "communications channels",
    "B": "publicity strategies",
    "C": "marketing activities",
    "D": "selling techniques",
    "answer": "A: communications channels",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do some businesses sponsor local events?",
    "A": "To obtain publicity",
    "B": "To create news",
    "C": "To generate revenue",
    "D": "To sell products",
    "answer": "A: To obtain publicity",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are public relations activities:?",
    "A": "Writing press releases, distributing company newsletters, and sponsoring events",
    "B": "Holding press conferences, identifying trends, and hiring new staff members",
    "C": "Sponsoring events, developing new products, and distributing company newsletters",
    "D": "Identifying trends, writing press releases, and hiring new staff members",
    "answer": "A: Writing press releases, distributing company newsletters, and sponsoring events",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The cost of employing product inspectors is a(n)",
    "A": "appraisal cost.",
    "B": "prevention cost.",
    "C": "internal failure cost.",
    "D": "external failure cost.",
    "answer": "A: appraisal cost.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because __________ measures of risk can be too general, it is also useful to perform ______ ____ assessment of risk.",
    "A": "quantitative; qualitative",
    "B": "qualitative; quantitative",
    "C": "preventative; responsive",
    "D": "responsive; preventative",
    "answer": "B: qualitative; quantitative",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a potential risk of implementing enterprise risk management (ERM) s oftware:?",
    "A": "Standardization of reporting",
    "B": "More emphasis on risk",
    "C": "Loss of data during the transfer",
    "D": "Less efficient use of resources",
    "answer": "C: Loss of data during the transfer",
    "topic": "Risk management & insurance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Salespersons should have good communication skills, but the sales presentation should not include too many __________ words.",
    "A": "expressive",
    "B": "picturesque",
    "C": "personal",
    "D": "technical",
    "answer": "D: technical",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which management function lays the groundwork for all of the other management functions?",
    "A": "Directing",
    "B": "Organizing",
    "C": "Staffing",
    "D": "Planning",
    "answer": "D: Planning",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way that managers can promote ethical behavior on the part of everyone in the business i s by encouraging employees to",
    "A": "develop a code of ethics.",
    "B": "report unethical actions.",
    "C": "be thoughtful of others.",
    "D": "avoid social situations.",
    "answer": "B: report unethical actions.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The ski shop manager set an objective to increase sales by 10% over the previous year even thou gh the forecast was for a mild and rainy winter. The manager's objective was",
    "A": "reasonable.",
    "B": "practical.",
    "C": "unrealistic.",
    "D": "scientific.",
    "answer": "C: unrealistic.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following pairs of businesses are examples of direct competitors:?",
    "A": "Ryan's Drugstore and Hally's Homemade Cards",
    "B": "Hot n' Spicy Wings and Southern Fried Chicken House",
    "C": "JTE Clothes Boutique and Carla's Hardware",
    "D": "Modern Dry Cleaning and Trotterman Accounting Services",
    "answer": "B: Hot n' Spicy Wings and Southern Fried Chicken House",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the most critical component of a business plan:?",
    "A": "Market analysis",
    "B": "Company description",
    "C": "Executive summary",
    "D": "Financial plan",
    "answer": "C: Executive summary",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following employees w ould most likely be described as \"innovative\" by his/her supervisor:?",
    "A": "Jake, because he is always willing to adapt to changes during a project",
    "B": "Madison, because she prefers to stick to traditional ideas and processes",
    "C": "Elizabeth, because she gets frustrated when she needs to learn new skills",
    "D": "Anthony, because he is usually quiet during brainstorming sessions",
    "answer": "A: Jake, because he is always willing to adapt to changes during a project",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the goals of change management is",
    "A": "to obtain buy-in from stakeholders.",
    "B": "to limit the effects of a change.",
    "C": "to keep the people involved to a minimum.",
    "D": "to reduce the time it takes to make a change.",
    "answer": "A: to obtain buy-in from stakeholders.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "C Trademark. A trademark is a symbol, design, or word used by a business to identify a goo d or service and is registered with the government to prevent its use by others. A trademark is an example of intangible business property. Federal law protects a business's intangible property from bein g used by competitors. A business's inventory, acreage, and equipment are types of tangible propert y. SOURCE: BL:001 SOURCE: World Intellectual Property Organization. (n.d.). What is intellectual property? Retrieved September 17, 2018, from http://www.wipo.int/edocs/pubdocs/en/intproperty/450/wipo_pub_450.pdf 2. D Contracts. Business torts are wrongful actions against a business that cause it harm in some w ay. Disputes concerning contracts are often the basis for businesses suing individuals or other businesses. Many businesses have contractual arrangements with employees or vendors. If these contracts are broken, the business might be harmed and seek compensation through the legal system. Basic torts relating to businesses do not involve disputes concerning assaults, defamation, or emotional stress. SOURCE: BL:069 SOURCE: Legal Match. (2018, May 2). Business torts. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.legalmatch.com/law-library/article/business-torts.html 3. D Continuous assistance is provided by the franchisor. A business-format franchise is a more c omplex and more popular type of franchise arrangement than the product trade-name franchise. It involves a close, continuous working relationship between the franchisor and the franchisee. Examples of the business-format franchise are McDonald's, Holiday Inn, and Jiffy Lube. Products and other materi als usually must be purchased from the franchisor's list of approved vendors. The franchisee must operate under the trade name of the franchisor. SOURCE: BL:003 SOURCE: LAP-BL-001-Own It Your Way (Types of Business Ownership) 4. D Corporation. Corporations are advantageous due to the separate legal body that is created by a state charter. The charter limits individual liability, allows for permanency of existe nce, ease in transferring ownership, and a greater number of resources for financial growth. Both the sole proprietorshi p and partnership have unlimited liability, definitive life spans, difficulty in raisi ng capital, and are not separate legal entities. A trade union is a group that represents people in similar occupational skil l areas. SOURCE: BL:006 SOURCE: LAP-BL-006-Taking Care of Business (Selecting Forms of Business Ownership) 5. D Making a variety of products available to them. Channels of distribution benefit consumers by making a variety of products available to them. Without these channels, consumers could only buy products directly from producers, which would be impractical. Channels may lower some but not all consumer product prices. They may raise the quality of some but not all consumer products. Increased profits for businesses is not a benefit for consumers. SOURCE: CM:001 SOURCE: LAP-CM-002-Chart Your Channels (Channel Management) 6. A Local consumers. A short channel can be used when the potential customers are few and/or located close together. The baby boomer, senior citizen, and Generation X markets have many potential customers who are widely dispersed. SOURCE: CM:003 SOURCE: LAP-CM-003-Channel It (Channels of Distribution) Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 14 7. C Market. Market factors deal with where the consumers are, who they are, the information they require, and the size of their orders. Understanding the market is an important aspect of selecting the best channel of distribution. For example, it is important for businesses to know that most consumers prefer to buy products from retailers. Promotion, human, and sales are not factors that businesses consider whe n selecting a channel of distribution. SOURCE: CM:010 SOURCE: Waksman, K. (2018, June 11). How to choose the right distribution channel for your business. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.thebalancesmb.com/choose-best-distribution-channel-for-your-business-3502272 8. A Research the problem. Proposals are intended to answer questions or provide recommendations to solve problems. Business employees often need to research a particular situation or problem before they are able to write proposals. After employees do research and gather information, they write proposal s that explain the problem and the solutions. The proposal is intended to persuade the business to follo w the recommendations. Employees usually do not need to analyze personal biases, contact the cus tomer, or evaluate technical skills before they are able to write proposals. SOURCE: CO:062 SOURCE: Bidsketch. (2018, June 15). How to write a business proposal. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.bidsketch.com/blog/articles/how-to-write-a-business-proposal/9. B Extending business hours on weekends. Management is responsible for developing polic ies, and many of these policies have an impact on customer relations. An example of a policy that usually im proves customer relations is providing extended business hours on weekends. Many customers work duri ng the week and only have free time in the evenings and on weekends. Businesses that offer extended hours on weekends are making it easy for customers to buy when it is convenient for them. Scheduling employees' work hours, using security devices, and revising bookkeeping procedures are routine business activities that managers perform on a regular basis. SOURCE: CR:008 SOURCE: Reynolds, P. (2016, May 6). Role of senior management in delivering customer service. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.etechgs.com/blog/role-senior-management-delivering-customer-service/10. C Communicate an appealing benefit. A brand promise is a business's agreement (spoken or unspoken) with customers that it will consistently meet their expectations and deliver on its brand c haracteristics and values. Before the business can deliver on its brand promise, it must have a product that offers an appealing benefit-one that persuades the target market to buy. For example, FedEx provides delivery services. The company's brand promise focuses on reliability. Therefore, FedEx promises to get its customers' packages to their destinations in a reliable manner-safely, quickly, and courteously-every time, which is an appealing benefit for most customers. A procedure is the step-by-step process that a person follows when performing a specific task. Customization involves maki ng the product unique for each customer. Customization, a high-quality image, and the process by which the business delivers its products may be elements of a company's brand promise. SOURCE: CR:001 SOURCE: Frederiksen, L. (2018, August 13). Elements of a successful brand 4: Brand promise. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://hingemarketing.com/blog/story/elements-of-a-successful-brand-4-brand-promise1 Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 15 11. A Certain occupations must be licensed. Even though there are many economic freedoms in a private enterprise system, there are certain limits. Economic freedom is limited by laws that have been created to protect everyone. Workers in certain occupations must be licensed to safeguard public health and s afety. Pay scales are not regulated but vary greatly depending on the occupation, area of the country, a nd current economic conditions. The law does not require all workers to take tests, although some businesses require applicants to take and pass ability tests before they are hired. Employ ees are not required to register with the state. SOURCE: EC:009 SOURCE: LAP-EC-015-People Power (The Private Enterprise System) 12. A Net profit. Net profit is the amount of money left over after operating expenses are subtracted from gross profit. Sales income is the total received from the sale of goods or services. Gross profit is the mon ey left over after cost of merchandise is subtracted from sales income. Operating expenses are the daily costs of running a business. SOURCE: EC:010 SOURCE: LAP-EC-002-Risk Rewarded (Factors Affecting Profit) 13. A Profits and losses are claimed on owners' personal tax returns. Non-corporations are taxed as pass-through entities, meaning that profits and losses are claimed on owners' personal tax returns. Non-corporations are still subject to federal taxes as well as state and local taxes. Business i ncome-tax rates are based on how much profit a business makes, not whether it is a corporation or not. Non-corporations pay payroll taxes on employees, just as corporations do. SOURCE: EC:072 SOURCE: LAP-EC-027-Pay Your Share (Business Taxes) 14. B Determining the details of your idea. Before you can \"sell\" your idea to others, you need to solidify the details and specifications of your proposal so that you can fully explain your idea t o your audience. Explaining solutions to audience needs, overcoming objections, and affirming the audien ce's decision to \"buy into\" your idea are all steps in the selling process that come after doing advance prep aration. SOURCE: EI:108 SOURCE: LAP-EI-108-Do They Buy It? (\"Selling\" Ideas to Others) 15. B Credibility. Credibility is believability. If employees believe what managers are say ing, they are more likely to be persuaded to do what the managers want them to do. Managers develop credibility by always being truthful with employees. As a result, employees often like and trust managers who are credib le and, therefore, are willing to follow their instructions. Having organizational skills, enthus iasm, or self-motivation does not necessarily mean that managers will be able to persuade employees. SOURCE: EI:012 SOURCE: LAP-EI-121-Win Them Over (Persuading Others) 16. B Interests. The key to successful negotiation is to focus on interests. Interests are the things that you and the other party want or need. You must consider the other party's interests as well as your ow n. Ability is a skill someone uses to perform a task through knowledge, training, and practice. When negot iating, one party may not necessarily know the other party's skills. Standards are specificati ons or statements that are used as a basis for comparing or judging goods or services. Procedure refers to the step-by-step process someone follows when performing a specific task. SOURCE: EI:062 SOURCE: LAP-EI-062-Make It a Win-Win (Negotiation in Business) Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 16 17. A Commit to your vision through hard work and dedication. Your personal vision will not becom e a reality unless you work hard to achieve your goals. Putting your vision in a safe place and look ing at it again in five years will not help you achieve your vision. Instead, you should place your v ision in a place where you will see it often. Getting the highest-paying job you can find out of high scho ol may help you save money, but it will not necessarily help you achieve your vision. You should be strategic when deciding what career path to pursue, making sure that it aligns with your vision. You do not need to spend all of your free time on self-improvement-you can still have hobbies and spend time doing things that you enjoy while pursuing your personal vision. SOURCE: EI:063 SOURCE: LAP-EI-064-Picture This! (Determining Personal Vision) 18. A Putting goals in writing. By keeping a list, Ryan has put his goals in writing. This makes them seem more solid and real, giving Ryan greater motivation to work toward them. Ryan is not necessarily tying hi s goals to a timetable, making his goals specific, or making his goals difficult b ut possible. SOURCE: EI:027 SOURCE: LAP-EI-027-High Hopes (Developing an Achievement Orientation) 19. D Vision. Vision is the future you desire to create. A goal is an objective or want th at you plan to fulfill. A prediction is a forecast made about the future. A mission statement is a brief summary of what a business owner wants a business to be doing. SOURCE: EI:060 SOURCE: LAP-EI-060-Vision Quest (Enlisting Others in Vision) 20. A Science. Entrepreneurial discovery is the process of detecting and matching product and market opportunities with one another in a manner that satisfies the market and the business. S ometimes there is a market with a demand for something that is not available, and the business invents a produc t to satisfy the demand. For example, a scientist uses existing physical elements to develop a new vaccine to prevent a certain disease for which there is no treatment. Because the vaccine is new, the scient ist (inventor) is observing and applying knowledge in a specific way, or using a scien tific process. Medicine, psychology, and physics are scientific disciplines, or areas of scientific study. SOURCE: EN:002 SOURCE: Smart Specialisation Platform. (2015, December 15). Entrepreneurial discovery process. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from http://s3platform.jrc.ec.europa.eu/entrepreneurial-discovery-edp 21. B Technical needs. Entrepreneurs and startup business owners must consider many factors before they open their ventures. They must consider their financial and staffing needs, as well as thei r technical needs. Their technical needs might include telephone, fax, Internet, computers, software programs, and automated equipment needs. Each business's needs vary, so the technical needs of each business varies, too. The competitive advantage is the edge achieved by businesses that offer something better than their competitors. SOURCE: EN:007 SOURCE: Horvath, B. (2017, July 13). Tech considerations for new business: What you need to know. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://businesstown.com/tech-considerations-new-business-need-know/Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 17 22. B The financial needs to start a new business depend on the nature of the venture. The requirements ( e.g., time, money) that a person needs to start a business differ and usually depend on the nature of the business. For example, a person who starts a home-based consulting business does not requi re as much money for the startup as a restaurant franchisee does. The franchisee needs to lease space or bu ild a facility, purchase kitchen equipment, obtain supplies, hire employees, and pay franchise f ees, which can be very expensive. A patent is legal protection that provides an owner the sole rights to an invention or process for a specific time period. Business owners do not always invent goods or processes, so n ot all of them need to obtain patent protection. SOURCE: EN:009 SOURCE: Beesley, C. (2017, December 29). How to estimate the cost of starting a business from scratch. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.sba.gov/blogs/how-estimate-cost-starting-business-scratch 23. B The industry experts typically provide useful information. Industry experts have in-dept h knowledge about a specific field. Experts often know about the trends, processes, new products, and new technolog y that affect the industry. These experts often provide entrepreneurs with useful information as they develop t he ideas for their new ventures. Talking with industry experts doesn't always improve your management skills or enhance your confidence. Industry experts might know where you can obtain financi al support, but they do not always offer it themselves. SOURCE: EN:012 SOURCE: Katz, J., & Green, R. (2011). Entrepreneurial small business (3rd ed.) [pp. 90, 92-96]. New York, NY: McGraw-Hill/Irwin. 24. A Provide collateral. There are many ways for entrepreneurs to obtain financing for new business v entures. One way is to obtain a loan from a commercial bank. The loan process generally involv es completing a loan application and submitting a business plan to the financial institution. In most situat ions, a bank will require the loan applicant to put up collateral in order to obtain the loan. Collatera l is anything of value (e.g., car, home) belonging to the borrower that is pledged to the lender to guarantee that the loan will be repaid. For example, if a business fails, and the borrower cannot afford to pay back the bank loan, the bank can take the borrower's belongings (collateral) as payment for the outstanding loan. Bank s do not require loan applicants to close their savings accounts, relinquish contracts, or char ge interest. SOURCE: EN:015 SOURCE: Hall,",
    "A": "(2012, October 20). 5 ways of funding a business: How to get your piece of the pie. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanhall/2012/10/20/5-means-of-funding-a-small-business-how-to-get-your-piece-of-the-pie/#621492421cf2 25. A List all the tasks involved in operating the business. Often, it helps business owners to write down every task that the business must perform in order to operate. After listing all tasks, the owners can c ategorize tasks by function (e.g., sales, bookkeeping) and determine in which areas they need the help o r expertise of others. In most situations, asking a technical recruiter for advice, hiring consultants or f reelancers, and allocating fund for payroll taxes do not help business owners determine their human resource nee ds. SOURCE: EN:017 SOURCE: CliffsNotes. (2016). Determining human resource needs. Retrieved September 18, 2018, from https://www.cliffsnotes.com/study-guides/principles-of-management/staffing-and-human-resource-management/determining-human-resource-needs Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 18 26. D Industry. Capital resources are assets, or things of value, that a firm uses on an ongoing basis to mee t its objectives. The capital resources that a business needs to get up and running depends on the t ype of products that the business sells. For example, a snow-ski resort needs ski-lift equipment, while a landscape business needs mowing equipment, mulch, and shrubs to efficiently operate. Location, owner's preferences, and suppliers' lead time are not always primary considerations when selecti ng capital resources. SOURCE: EN:019 SOURCE: Nickolas, S. (2018, February 2). What inputs are considered to be factors of production? Retrieved September 12, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/ask/answers/032715/what-inputs-are-considered-be-factors-production.asp 27. A When an entrepreneur seeks a high profit, the risk is usually higher. Risk is the chanc e of failure or loss. There are many types of risks that business owners face including social, career, psychic, an d financial risks. The amount of risk a business owner takes varies, but financial risk is the ris k that is the easiest to measure. The more money that a person invests in a business (equity or debt finance options), the more financial risk the person is taking because s/he has more money to lose. Risk-taking is often related to potential rewards. Entrepreneurs care about their profits to varying degrees. SOURCE: EN:024 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, July 25). Risk-return tradeoff. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/r/riskreturntradeoff.asp 28. D Standard. Operating procedures are the step-by-step processes that employees follow when performing specific work-related tasks. By developing and implementing operating procedures, th e small-business owner reduces the amount of time that s/he spends answering questions and making decis ions about routine, day-to-day activities. This reduction occurs because the employees have guidelines or a standard way to complete tasks. Conducting activities in a standard way often increases emplo yee productivity and efficiency. Everyday tasks do not always need to be performed in i mprecise, diverse, or innovative ways. SOURCE: EN:026 SOURCE: Rush, M. (2016, October 26). Standard operating procedures for a business. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/standard-operating-procedures-business-3228.html 29. D Offer a new service. Because a business cannot survive if it does not earn a profit, and profits are generated from product sales, business owners often look for ways to improve or develop goods and services to keep the customers coming back. Increasing prices and ridiculing the co mpetition are not activities that would increase repeat business and customer loyalty. Updating equipment does not necessarily facilitate repeat business and customer loyalty. SOURCE: EN:028 SOURCE: Rampton, D. (2017, September 25). Introducing new products and services as a business owner. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://due.com/blog/introduce-new-products-and-services-as-a-business-owner/Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 19 30. C Identify new venture opportunities. An opportunity is a circumstance that presents itsel f as a favorable means to meet an objective. Entrepreneurs look for opportunities to start businesses and if the opportunities are feasible, they act upon them. There are many ways to look for business opportuni ties such as watching trends, attending trade shows, and talking with friends, customers, and busi ness associates. Entrepreneurs might join community organizations or trade associations to network with others with the goal of identifying new venture opportunities. Entrepreneurs do not join communit y organizations to obtain selling experiences, evaluate personal skills and abilities, or improve goods and services. SOURCE: EN:031 SOURCE: Long, J. (2017, March 23). 6 benefits of joining a professional community. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/290983 31. A False, there are many factors to consider, such as company valuation and personal goals. Entrep reneurs often leave their ventures after they achieve their objectives for their businesses. Entrepreneurs c onsider many factors, such as how much the business is worth, and personal considerations, such as retiri ng or starting another venture. There are several ways for an entrepreneur to exit a business, which inc lude selling the business, taking his/her share of the profits and letting partners or others run the business, and closing the business. Thus, exiting a business is often complex and has many factors and o ptions to consider, other than finding a suitable buyer. SOURCE: EN:037 SOURCE: Clark,",
    "B": ", & Commers, J. (2018). Entrepreneurship (2nd ed.) [pp. 498-511]. Tinley Park, IL: The Goodheart-Willcox Company. 32. D Accounts receivable. Accounts receivable are money that is owed to a business. They are an asset to the business, but they do not have a physical presence. Inventory, buildings, and equipment ar e all tangible assets-they have a physical presence. SOURCE: FI:093 SOURCE: LAP-FI-010-The Right Balance (The Nature of Balance Sheets) 33. B Summarizes expenses and revenue from sales. A profit-and-loss statement is a business's financial picture that lists all revenue and expenses for a certain time period. A profit-and-loss statement i s not the same as a balance sheet. Characteristics of a balance sheet include listing assets and liabili ties and showing the owner's financial position. SOURCE: FI:094 SOURCE: LAP-FI-004-Watch Your Bottom Line (Income Statements) 34. B Cost driver. A factor that causes a change in the cost of an activity is called a cost driver. Chang es such as the amount of labor used, the number of machines used, the power used to run the machinery, and the number of hours that the machinery is operated are cost drivers. Increases in these activiti es increase the costs of making outputs (products), while decreases in these activitie s decrease the costs of making the outputs. Cost drivers are not unexpected expenses or inflexible transactions. SOURCE: FI:657 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, July 19). Activity cost driver. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from http://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/activity-cost-driver.asp Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 20 35. B Accounts receivable. Accounts receivable are all the monies owed to a business by its c ustomers. Businesses in need of cash to continue producing and selling goods often use their accou nts receivable as collateral when borrowing from financial institutions. In effect, the busines ses are turning over the proceeds from their receivables to the lenders in exchange for immediate cash to continue operating. A promissory note is a legal form signed by a borrower promising to repay a loan. Liabil ities are debts that the business owes. Operating expenses are all of the expenditures necessary to keep the business running. SOURCE: FI:023 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, May 29). Accounts receivable financing. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/accountsreceivablefinancing.asp 36. A Liquidity. Liquidity refers to a business's current assets, such as income or savings, that c an be used to pay expenses. Assets that are in the form of cash or tangibles that can be sold easily to generate cash add to a company's liquidity. When determining financing needs, businesses usually con sider their liquidity to decide if they have sufficient funds available to repay the debt. For exa mple, if a business was barely covering expenses and had no liquid assets, it probably would decide not to borro w money because it would be difficult to make payments on the loan. Depreciation is a reduction i n value of goods occurring over a period of time. Equity is the value of the business after all expenses and deb ts have been subtracted. Inventory is all the stock a business has on hand. SOURCE: FI:043 SOURCE: Mueller, J. (2018, May 8). Understanding financial liquidity. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/articles/basics/07/liquidity.asp 37. A Being charged a penalty. When businesses obtain long-term loans, they agree to pay a certain am ount of interest to the lending institution over a period of years. If a business pays off the loan be fore it is due, the financial institution does not get the interest it expected to receive. In such cases, the financ ial institution may charge the business a penalty for prepaying the loan. This penalty may be sizeabl e depending on the amount of the loan. A financial institution, rather than a business, loses interest on the account. A business might negotiate a variable rate for a long-term loan and pay a processing fee to originate t he loan. SOURCE: FI:041 SOURCE: Business Filings. (2012, May 24). The real cost of borrowing money. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.bizfilings.com/toolkit/research-topics/finance/business-finance/the-real-cost-of-borrowing-money 38. D To reduce risk. There is a risk involved in making loans because a business may default a nd be unable to repay the bank. To reduce the risk, lending institutions use certain criteria to evaluate if th e business is creditworthy. For example, a bank would run a credit check to find out if the business pays its bills on time. Also, a bank would review the business's financial records to determine if it earned suf ficient income to pay expenses and also repay the loan. By carefully evaluating how well a business meets certain criteria, a bank is able to reduce the risk involved in making a loan. Lending institution s do not evaluate businesses to provide service, prevent theft, or improve relations. SOURCE: FI:034 SOURCE: Business Filings. (2012, May 24). What banks look for when reviewing a loan application. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.bizfilings.com/toolkit/research-topics/finance/business-finance/what-banks-look-for-when-reviewing-a-loan-application 39. B 1 year. Businesses prefer a short payback period. This is the point at which a decision begins to pay for itself. In other words, the payback period is the time it takes for the benefits of a change to repay its costs. Another term for payback period is break-even point. SOURCE: FI:357 SOURCE: LAP-FI-011-Running the Numbers (Cost-Benefit Analysis) Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 21 40. C Size of the sales force. An internal change is one that occurs within the business and is un der the business's control. Increasing or decreasing the number of people on the sales force is an inter nal change that will affect the sales forecast. For example, decreasing the size of the sales force may c ause sales to fall because the remaining staff may not be able to handle as many sales. Changes in the number of competitors in the market, the length of a national recession, and the levels of c onsumer spending are external changes. SOURCE: FI:096 SOURCE: Freelancer. (2015, April 14). Sales forecasting: Factors to consider. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.freelancer.com/community/articles/sales-forecasting-factors-to-consider 41. B Vertical. Three common types of financial statement analysis are vertical analysis, hori zontal analysis, and ratio analysis. When conducting vertical analysis, an individual calculates each i ndividual item on a financial statement as a percentage of the total. After doing so, the analyst can develop com mon-size financial statements that allow him/her to compare performance across several years for a singl e company or across several different companies. Horizontal analysis, which is sometimes kno wn as trend analysis, involves analyzing dollar amounts on financial statements for a single compan y across several years. Horizontal analysis does not involve the development of common-size finan cial statements. Ratio analysis involves the calculation of ratios based on a company's financial data. It allows analysts to compare numbers within a financial statement and determine the relationships among numbe rs on different financial statements. It can also be used to compare the performance of multiple companies. SOURCE: FI:334 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, June 13). Vertical analysis. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/v/vertical_analysis.asp 42. C $3,138. A business's income statement, or profit-and-loss statement, is a financial summary that shows how much money the business has made or has lost over a specific period of time. A typi cal income statement includes revenue, operating expenses, and net income (profit). To determine the net i ncome, subtract the total expenses from the total revenue ($4,590-$1,442 = $3,138). It is important to verify the income statement's accuracy because businesses use the information to make important decisions ab out the business. If the information is incorrect (e.g., transposed numbers) and errors are not corrected, the business may make unwise decisions on the basis of faulty information. SOURCE: FI:335 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, August 9). Net income. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/n/netincome.asp 43. C To determine qualifications. The purpose of an interview is to determine if the appl icant meets the qualifications to perform the job. Therefore, the interview questions should relate directly to th e job in terms of the applicant's education, skills, training, and work history. Businesses often take remedial action with current employees who are not performing well on the job. Applicants usually do not complain during job interviews. Interviewers usually do not plan future training while a sking questions during a job interview. SOURCE: HR:355 SOURCE: Business Filings. (2012, May 24). The dos and don'ts of conducting a job interview. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.bizfilings.com/toolkit/research-topics/office-hr/the-dos-and-donts-of-conducting-a-job-interview 44. D Cause. Termination for cause occurs when an employee's conduct seriously violates company poli cies or jeopardizes the company or other employees. A termination for performance is used when an emplo yee consistently exhibits poor performance compared to established performance criteria, or is inc ompetent. A resignation is a voluntary act by an employee. SOURCE: HR:358 SOURCE: Heathfield, S.M. (2018, August 25). Termination for cause. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.thebalancecareers.com/termination-for-cause-1918274 Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 22 45. B To improve performance. Businesses often provide additional training based on changing needs i n the workplace. As technology and job responsibilities change, it is necessary to trai n employees to perform new tasks or tasks that have been revised. By providing training, businesses are helping em ployees learn new skills and improve their performance. Socialization is part of the orientation proces s. Businesses do not provide additional training to analyze diversity or identify sen sitivity. SOURCE: HR:392 SOURCE: Frost, S. (2018, June 30). The importance of training & development in the workplace. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/importance-training-development-workplace-10321.html 46. A Organization's. Each organization, or business, develops standards for evaluating an emplo yee's performance. When supervisors evaluate employees, they should rate them according to establ ished standards. An employee is more likely to resent a negative evaluation if it is based on the supervisor's standards. Evaluations are not based on the standards set by employees or competitors. SOURCE: HR:368 SOURCE: Noe, R.A., Hollenbeck, J.R., Gerhart, B., & Wright, P.M. (2010). Human resource management: Gaining a competitive advantage (7th ed.) [p. 358]. New York, NY: McGraw-Hill/Irwin. 47. A To predict change. Businesses need a wide variety of information in order to make decisions about how the business will market its goods or services. Businesses gather marketing information about t heir customers, the competition, the economy, and sales trends in order to predict what may occur in the future. The use of marketing information allows businesses to prepare for change and adapt in ord er to remain successful. Businesses often develop surveys and conduct research to obtain the marketing data they need to analyze in order to predict change. SOURCE: IM:012 SOURCE: Churchill, G.A., Brown, T.J., & Suter, T.A. (2010). Basic marketing research (7th ed.) [pp. 3-7]. Mason, OH: South-Western Cengage Learning. 48. C The step in which the most mistakes are made. The reason that the most mistakes are made in this s tep is that data collection can be a tedious chore. When researchers become bored, they may record dat a inaccurately. It is also the most expensive and least interesting step. SOURCE: IM:010 SOURCE: LAP-IM-010-Seek and Find (Marketing Research) 49. A House. A durable good is an item that is intended to last a relatively long time. Most houses would be considered durable goods. Haircuts, gasoline, and hamburger are eventually used up and are, therefore, classified as nondurable goods. SOURCE: MK:001 SOURCE: LAP-MK-004-Have It Your Way! (Nature of Marketing) 50. C Psychological. Consumer behavior encompasses individuals' actions that determine what they buy and sell. Psychological, social, and personal factors all influence consumer behavior. Psyc hological factors include an individual's motives, perception, attitude, lifestyle, personality, abi lities, and knowledge. Consumer behavior is also impacted by social factors such as opinion leaders, a person's fami ly, reference groups, social class, and culture. Personal factors impacting consumer behavior are specific to a particular person and include demographic characteristics such as gender, age, ethnicity, etc. W hile political and economic factors may influence consumer behavior in some instances, moti ves, perception, attitude, lifestyle, personality, and abilities are not political or economic factors. SOURCE: MK:014 SOURCE: LAP-MK-006-Cause and Effect (Buying Behavior) Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 23 51. D Strategies. Marketing strategies are game plans for getting the job done. Budgets and salespeople are factors in a strategy, and profit is a goal of most strategies. SOURCE: MP:001 SOURCE: LAP-MP-002-Pick the Mix (Nature of Marketing Strategies) 52. B Mass. Mass marketing is designing products and directing marketing activities in order to appeal to the whole market. One marketing plan can thus be used to appeal to many types of customers. Demographic characteristics, such as age, income, or occupation, and psychographic characteristics, such as lifestyles and personalities, are used to define or differentiate between segments of a market. SOURCE: MP:003 SOURCE: LAP-MP-003-Have We Met? (Market Identification) 53. B Geographic. When analyzing the market, it is important for businesses to collect several types of geographic information. First, a business considers the geographic location of customer s and potential customers. Businesses need to know where their customers are. Also, a business considers the geographic location of the business. Businesses need to know if they are located in an a rea that has market potential or if there are too many competitors in that area. A market analysis does not involve collecting confidential, employee, or property information. SOURCE: MP:009 SOURCE: Frenz, R. (2017, September 26). Components of marketing analysis. Retrieved September 20, 2018, from https://bizfluent.com/info-7921910-components-market-analysis.html 54. C Operational activities. The sales forecast, the prediction of future sales over a specific per iod of time, is the basis for many other operational activities. The forecast affects decisions about product ion, distribution, purchasing, promotion, etc. Therefore, the sales forecast needs to be as accurate as possible so the business correctly plans the other operational activities. For example, if the forecast is t oo high, a business might produce substantially more product than it will be able to sell. A sal es forecast is not the basis of pricing strategies, business reports, or management techniques. SOURCE: MP:014 SOURCE: Metcalf, T. (2018, April 5). Top 10 reasons why sales forecasting is important. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from http://yourbusiness.azcentral.com/top-10-reasons-sales-forecasting-important-24818.html 55. A Analyzing click-through rates. Businesses develop performance measures to evaluate the effecti veness of marketing activities. Businesses also need to compare the performance measures to financi al outcomes to determine if the activity was worth the cost. The click-through rate for online advertising is a performance measure. By analyzing the click-through rate, businesses can link performan ce to financial outcomes. For example, if 200,000 people viewed a site and 8,000 of them clicked on a banner ad, the click-through rate is 4%. If the goal was to achieve a click-through rate of 2%, the activity outperformed expectations that might lead to an increase in sales, which is the financial outcome the bu siness desires. Developing advertising budgets and paying for direct-mail pieces are promotional activities. Mainta ining sales receipts is a bookkeeping activity. SOURCE: MP:020 SOURCE: WordStream. (n.d.). Click-through rate (CTR): Understanding click-through rate for PPC. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.wordstream.com/click-through-rate Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 24 56. B Firewall. Firewall software is intended to prevent unauthorized access to a computer network. Many businesses require firewall software to be installed on their computer systems because th eir systems are networked, and hackers could destroy or steal valuable data. Firewall software is a sec urity feature that helps protect a business's computer network. Businesses do not install reality, spider, or media soft ware as a security feature. SOURCE: NF:012 SOURCE: Cisco. (2015, July 30). What is a firewall? Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/security/firewalls/what-is-a-firewall.html 57. C Promotional. Promotional records are documents containing information about the various types of communication that businesses use to inform, persuade, or remind customers of their products, images, or ideas. Businesses often keep copies of their promotional materials in case they need to refer to them in the future for some reason (e.g., to answer customer inquiries). Contracts, permits, and leases are examples of records that businesses keep for regulatory and legal purposes. Inventory records contain information about the types and quantities of materials or products the business has available or on order. Asset records contain information about the things that a business owns, such as the equipment and furniture it uses to operate. SOURCE: NF:001 SOURCE: LAP-NF-001-Record It (Business Records) 58. B Increase in competition. A business's external environment is always changing and dynam ic. Elements of the external environment that are likely to impact business decision-making are competition, demographics, society and culture, the economy, the government, and technology. Personnel, training, and quality control measures all represent internal elements of the business's environment. SOURCE: NF:015 SOURCE: LAP-NF-015-Get the 4-1-1 (Conducting an Environmental Scan) 59. B Mean. The mean is a measure of central tendency. Mean is a mathematical average, which involves adding together the raw data and dividing the sum by the number of individual data. In the ex ample, James added together all of the salaries of the companies that he researched ($31,205 + $29,995 + $34,800 +$42,500 + $36,500 = $175,000). Then, Jack divided the sum by the number of indiv idual salaries in the set of data ($175,000/5 = $35,000). The mode of a set of numbers is the value that appears most often in the set. The range is the difference between the largest and the smallest number in the data set. The median is the exact middle of a data set. In the example, $34,800 is the median of the data set. SOURCE: NF:093 SOURCE: Russell, D. (2018, March 11). How to calculate the mean, median, and mode. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.thoughtco.com/the-mean-median-and-mode-2312604 60. B Performance indicators. A performance indicator is a measure of the success of a certain activ ity or entity. Businesses often set performance indicators for their own success, as well as the success and effectiveness of their suppliers. Performance indicators commonly used to evaluate vendor perform ance and effectiveness include on-time delivery rate, return rate, and number of customer complaints. If a vendor does not meet or exceed a particular indicator, the business is apt to discuss the m easure with the vendor and develop a plan of corrective action. A consensus scale is a measure of ea ch group member's feelings toward a proposed decision or solution. Economic indicators are stati stical measures used to assess the health and direction of the economy. Return on capital is a measure of how well a business generates cash flow in relation to the capital it has already invested into itself. SOURCE: OP:162 SOURCE: Brown,",
    "C": "M. (2010, December 30). 7 tips for rating and evaluating your suppliers and vendors. Retrieved September 18, 2018, from http://www.inc.com/guides/2010/12/7-tips-to-rate-and-evaluate-your-suppliers-and-vendors.html Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 25 61. D Production. Production is the process or activity of producing goods and services. For example, a company uses raw materials, equipment, employees, and a building to produce radios for purchase by other businesses for use or for resale. Management is the process of coordinating resources in order to accomplish an organization's goals. Accounting is the process of keeping financial rec ords. Marketing is the process of planning and executing the conception, pricing, promotion, and distribution of idea s, goods, and services to create exchanges that satisfy individual and organizational objectives. SOURCE: OP:017 SOURCE: LAP-OP-017-Can You Make It? (Nature of Production) 62. B To lead the effort. Management sets the tone for quality in a business and leads the effort. If managers do their best to achieve quality and set an example for employees, the employees usually follo w. Managers lead by setting clear goals, by making sure employees understand the goals, by giv ing employees the information and tools they need, and by being supportive. They also lead by behaving the way they expect employees to behave. The role of management in the achievement of quality in a business is not to assign blame or judge the staff. Management should direct and guide. It is n ot possible to eliminate conflict, although management often can control conflict. SOURCE: OP:020 SOURCE: Brown, B. (2017, September 26). The role of managers in Total Quality Management. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://bizfluent.com/info-7743372-role-managers-total-quality-management.html 63. A Insurance. Insurance is a fixed operating co st-it does not increase or decrease with changes in production. Sales commissions, advertising, and travel expenses are all variable-they fluctuate with changes in production. SOURCE: OP:024 SOURCE: LAP-OP-009-Watch Your (Over) Head (Overhead/Operating Costs) 64. B Variable costs and fixed costs. A break-even analysis is a financial assessment that a busines s uses to identify the level of sales it needs to reach the break-even point at various prices. To conduct a break-even analysis, the business must know the fixed costs and variable costs it will encou nter to get the good or service to the end user. Production time might be included as a cost in certain types of busi nesses (e.g., tax preparation, manufacturing). Depreciation rate is the level at which the value of something (e.g., equipment) reduces over time. SOURCE: OP:192 SOURCE: Tatum, M., & Harris, B. (2018, August 23). What is a break-even analysis? Retrieved September 17, 2018, from http://www.wisegeek.com/what-is-a-break-even-analysis.htm 65. A Does the cost of the contract exceed the cost of possible repairs? The business should estimate the costs of the most expensive, possible repairs and calculate if these expenses would be more or less than the cost of the service or maintenance contract. If the cost of the repair would be less than the cost of the contract, it may be wise to forgo the contract. The business would consider the need for installation and the availability of training and technical assistance when purchasing equipment. A bus iness does not consider how much profit the seller will make on the contract. SOURCE: OP:027 SOURCE: Thakur, S. (2011, April 28). Negotiate software maintenance contracts: Tips & strategies. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.brighthubpm.com/monitoring-projects/115813-negotiate-software-maintenance-contracts-tips-and-strategies/Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 26 66. B Estimated sales exceed actual sales. Budgets are only useful if a business compares the budget estimates with actual operating conditions. Businesses use the budget information to make dec isions about how the business will operate and to make changes when necessary. A business knows that it must make operating changes if it compares the level of sales estimated in the budget wit h actual sales figures and finds that actual sales are not keeping up with the estimates. This information indicat es that the business might not make the expected profit or even have a loss if changes are not made. A business probably would not make operating changes if the budget information indicates that tota l revenues exceed projected costs, expected profits are increasing, and accounts receivable are on target. SOURCE: OP:030 SOURCE: Johnston, K. (2016, October 26). How does a budget help management make good decisions? Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/budget-management-make-good-decisions-57917.html 67. C Monitor the performance of all supply chain partners. To ensure the efficient production and distri bution of products, companies should monitor the performance of all supply chain partners on a consistent basis. Companies should not ignore underperforming vendors-they should work with them to resolve the problem(s) or else replace them. Companies must be careful when introducing new innovations or changes to the production process. Introducing change too quickly can overwhelm the supply cha in, resulting in failure to meet production quotas. Companies should stick with a single supplier when launching a new product in order to avoid overcomplicating the process. SOURCE: OP:303 SOURCE: Schiff, J. (2016, February 17). 13 ways to improve your supply chain management. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from http://www.enterpriseappstoday.com/supply-chain-management/slideshows/13-ways-to-improve-your-supply-chain-management.html 68. B Financial. Business analysis is the process of investigating and evaluating a business issue, problem, process, or approach. Analysis helps a business determine if it is achieving its goals or i f it needs to take corrective action, so it can achieve its goals. Financial analysis invol ves evaluating the business's financial health. Because the business needs to make a reasonable profit so it can thrive in mark etplace, it is important to continuously analyze the business's financial status. The operations bu siness function involves the day-to-day activities that the business performs-activities that are required for continued business functioning such as producing goods and services. Information management is the proc ess of coordinating the resources pertaining to business knowledge, facts, or data. Sales is a mark eting activity that involves responding to consumer needs and wants through planned, personalized communi cations intended to influence purchase decisions and ensure satisfaction. SOURCE: OP:327 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, July 9). Financial analysis. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/f/financial-analysis.asp 69. B Business process thinking. Business process thinking is a method of thinking that emphasizes th e importance of processes in business. Managers who use business process thinking would most lik ely establish the necessary steps to complete a project before assigning the project to staff. Human resource planning, agile project management, and change management are also important business practices, b ut they are not described in this example. SOURCE: OP:474 SOURCE: Pitagorsky, G. (2016, August 3). The importance of process thinking. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.projecttimes.com/george-pitagorsky/the-importance-of-process-thinking.html Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 27 70. B Regulatory. Because the manufacturing company is required by local government to dispose of its waste safely, the company must design its waste disposal process to abide by the regulati ons. This is an example of regulatory factors affecting business process design. Human factors affecting process des ign include stress, employee morale, and fatigue. Technological factors that can affect process des ign include the c ost of any equipment or hardware that is necessary for the process. The term \"natural factors\" is not usually used to describe factors affecting process design. SOURCE: OP:475 SOURCE: Taylor, H. (2017, September 26). Factors that affect process design. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://bizfluent.com/list-7444011-factors-affect-process-design.html 71. A A manufacturing company purchases a new software program to run its machines. Technology can cause a business to change its processes, such as when a new technology becomes available or an old technology becomes obsolete. A small general store offering discounts to compete with a new shop ping mall is an example of how competition can cause business processes to change. A waste treatmen t plant changing its disposal method to align with environmental law is an example of how re gulations and governmental factors can cause business processes to change. A family-owned restaurant opening a second location in an effort to expand its brand is an example of how the desire for growth can caus e business processes to change. SOURCE: OP:476 SOURCE: Gleeson, P. (2018, June 30). Factors that may cause change in an organization. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/factors-may-cause-change-organization-203.html 72. D Poor supply chain management can result in customer dissatisfaction. Poor supply chain managem ent would likely lead to many problems for all members of a supply chain, such as order fulfil lment delays and product quality issues. These issues would most likely result in customer dissatisfac tion, not customer satisfaction. Good supply chain management would lead to increased value for customers, since product issues would be less likely. Good supply chain management is likely to result in sustainable business practices, not unsustainable business practices. SOURCE: OP:477 SOURCE: Ingram,",
    "D": "(2016, October 26). How does supply chain management affect manufacturing",
    "answer": "C: M. (2010, December 30). 7 tips for rating and evaluating your suppliers and vendors. Retrieved September 18, 2018, from http://www.inc.com/guides/2010/12/7-tips-to-rate-and-evaluate-your-suppliers-and-vendors.html Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 25 61. D Production. Production is the process or activity of producing goods and services. For example, a company uses raw materials, equipment, employees, and a building to produce radios for purchase by other businesses for use or for resale. Management is the process of coordinating resources in order to accomplish an organization's goals. Accounting is the process of keeping financial rec ords. Marketing is the process of planning and executing the conception, pricing, promotion, and distribution of idea s, goods, and services to create exchanges that satisfy individual and organizational objectives. SOURCE: OP:017 SOURCE: LAP-OP-017-Can You Make It? (Nature of Production) 62. B To lead the effort. Management sets the tone for quality in a business and leads the effort. If managers do their best to achieve quality and set an example for employees, the employees usually follo w. Managers lead by setting clear goals, by making sure employees understand the goals, by giv ing employees the information and tools they need, and by being supportive. They also lead by behaving the way they expect employees to behave. The role of management in the achievement of quality in a business is not to assign blame or judge the staff. Management should direct and guide. It is n ot possible to eliminate conflict, although management often can control conflict. SOURCE: OP:020 SOURCE: Brown, B. (2017, September 26). The role of managers in Total Quality Management. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://bizfluent.com/info-7743372-role-managers-total-quality-management.html 63. A Insurance. Insurance is a fixed operating co st-it does not increase or decrease with changes in production. Sales commissions, advertising, and travel expenses are all variable-they fluctuate with changes in production. SOURCE: OP:024 SOURCE: LAP-OP-009-Watch Your (Over) Head (Overhead/Operating Costs) 64. B Variable costs and fixed costs. A break-even analysis is a financial assessment that a busines s uses to identify the level of sales it needs to reach the break-even point at various prices. To conduct a break-even analysis, the business must know the fixed costs and variable costs it will encou nter to get the good or service to the end user. Production time might be included as a cost in certain types of busi nesses (e.g., tax preparation, manufacturing). Depreciation rate is the level at which the value of something (e.g., equipment) reduces over time. SOURCE: OP:192 SOURCE: Tatum, M., & Harris, B. (2018, August 23). What is a break-even analysis? Retrieved September 17, 2018, from http://www.wisegeek.com/what-is-a-break-even-analysis.htm 65. A Does the cost of the contract exceed the cost of possible repairs? The business should estimate the costs of the most expensive, possible repairs and calculate if these expenses would be more or less than the cost of the service or maintenance contract. If the cost of the repair would be less than the cost of the contract, it may be wise to forgo the contract. The business would consider the need for installation and the availability of training and technical assistance when purchasing equipment. A bus iness does not consider how much profit the seller will make on the contract. SOURCE: OP:027 SOURCE: Thakur, S. (2011, April 28). Negotiate software maintenance contracts: Tips & strategies. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.brighthubpm.com/monitoring-projects/115813-negotiate-software-maintenance-contracts-tips-and-strategies/Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 26 66. B Estimated sales exceed actual sales. Budgets are only useful if a business compares the budget estimates with actual operating conditions. Businesses use the budget information to make dec isions about how the business will operate and to make changes when necessary. A business knows that it must make operating changes if it compares the level of sales estimated in the budget wit h actual sales figures and finds that actual sales are not keeping up with the estimates. This information indicat es that the business might not make the expected profit or even have a loss if changes are not made. A business probably would not make operating changes if the budget information indicates that tota l revenues exceed projected costs, expected profits are increasing, and accounts receivable are on target. SOURCE: OP:030 SOURCE: Johnston, K. (2016, October 26). How does a budget help management make good decisions? Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/budget-management-make-good-decisions-57917.html 67. C Monitor the performance of all supply chain partners. To ensure the efficient production and distri bution of products, companies should monitor the performance of all supply chain partners on a consistent basis. Companies should not ignore underperforming vendors-they should work with them to resolve the problem(s) or else replace them. Companies must be careful when introducing new innovations or changes to the production process. Introducing change too quickly can overwhelm the supply cha in, resulting in failure to meet production quotas. Companies should stick with a single supplier when launching a new product in order to avoid overcomplicating the process. SOURCE: OP:303 SOURCE: Schiff, J. (2016, February 17). 13 ways to improve your supply chain management. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from http://www.enterpriseappstoday.com/supply-chain-management/slideshows/13-ways-to-improve-your-supply-chain-management.html 68. B Financial. Business analysis is the process of investigating and evaluating a business issue, problem, process, or approach. Analysis helps a business determine if it is achieving its goals or i f it needs to take corrective action, so it can achieve its goals. Financial analysis invol ves evaluating the business's financial health. Because the business needs to make a reasonable profit so it can thrive in mark etplace, it is important to continuously analyze the business's financial status. The operations bu siness function involves the day-to-day activities that the business performs-activities that are required for continued business functioning such as producing goods and services. Information management is the proc ess of coordinating the resources pertaining to business knowledge, facts, or data. Sales is a mark eting activity that involves responding to consumer needs and wants through planned, personalized communi cations intended to influence purchase decisions and ensure satisfaction. SOURCE: OP:327 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, July 9). Financial analysis. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/f/financial-analysis.asp 69. B Business process thinking. Business process thinking is a method of thinking that emphasizes th e importance of processes in business. Managers who use business process thinking would most lik ely establish the necessary steps to complete a project before assigning the project to staff. Human resource planning, agile project management, and change management are also important business practices, b ut they are not described in this example. SOURCE: OP:474 SOURCE: Pitagorsky, G. (2016, August 3). The importance of process thinking. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://www.projecttimes.com/george-pitagorsky/the-importance-of-process-thinking.html Test 1188 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 27 70. B Regulatory. Because the manufacturing company is required by local government to dispose of its waste safely, the company must design its waste disposal process to abide by the regulati ons. This is an example of regulatory factors affecting business process design. Human factors affecting process des ign include stress, employee morale, and fatigue. Technological factors that can affect process des ign include the c ost of any equipment or hardware that is necessary for the process. The term \"natural factors\" is not usually used to describe factors affecting process design. SOURCE: OP:475 SOURCE: Taylor, H. (2017, September 26). Factors that affect process design. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://bizfluent.com/list-7444011-factors-affect-process-design.html 71. A A manufacturing company purchases a new software program to run its machines. Technology can cause a business to change its processes, such as when a new technology becomes available or an old technology becomes obsolete. A small general store offering discounts to compete with a new shop ping mall is an example of how competition can cause business processes to change. A waste treatmen t plant changing its disposal method to align with environmental law is an example of how re gulations and governmental factors can cause business processes to change. A family-owned restaurant opening a second location in an effort to expand its brand is an example of how the desire for growth can caus e business processes to change. SOURCE: OP:476 SOURCE: Gleeson, P. (2018, June 30). Factors that may cause change in an organization. Retrieved September 17, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/factors-may-cause-change-organization-203.html 72. D Poor supply chain management can result in customer dissatisfaction. Poor supply chain managem ent would likely lead to many problems for all members of a supply chain, such as order fulfil lment delays and product quality issues. These issues would most likely result in customer dissatisfac tion, not customer satisfaction. Good supply chain management would lead to increased value for customers, since product issues would be less likely. Good supply chain management is likely to result in sustainable business practices, not unsustainable business practices. SOURCE: OP:477 SOURCE: Ingram,",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Patents, trademarks, and copyrights are all methods used to protect",
    "A": "houses and apartments. C. intellectual property.",
    "B": "physical inventions. D. government secrets. 3. What types of businesses can be owned by thousands of stockholders? A. General partnerships",
    "C": "Close corporations B. Open corporations",
    "D": "Sole proprietorships",
    "answer": "C: Close corporations B. Open corporations",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business owner who prefers to maintain complete control of all business activities might consider structuring the venture as a(n)",
    "A": "sole proprietorship. C. \"S\" corporation.",
    "B": "general partnership. D. limited liability company. 5. Channels of distribution benefit businesses by A. allowing them to avoid all channel tasks. B. lowering the prices of all industrial goods.",
    "C": "raising their profits each year.",
    "D": "getting their products to consumers more efficiently.",
    "answer": "A: sole proprietorship. C. \"S\" corporation.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A farmer with a produce stand in the yard is an example of a __________ distribution channel.",
    "A": "producer to consumer C. producer to retailer to consumer",
    "B": "producer to agent to consumer D. producer to wholesaler to consumer 7. The best way to evaluate the channel members in an international supply chain is often by using a(n) A. global distribution center.",
    "C": "global industry benchmarking system. B. intern ational monetary fund.",
    "D": "international trade center.",
    "answer": "A: producer to consumer C. producer to retailer to consumer",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The ultimate purpose of preparing a long, complex, business report is usually to",
    "A": "be well-organized. C. help with major decisions.",
    "B": "present all views. D. present accurate data. 9. Which of the following is an example of a brand promise: A. Low credit terms are available for qualified customers until January 2025. B. Leather sofas only $499 this weekend-buy now at Fred's Furniture Warehouse.",
    "C": "Henderson Photography...uniquely capturing your special moments is our priority.",
    "D": "For your convenience, four Cup O' Joe locations are open in the greater metro area.",
    "answer": "C: Henderson Photography...uniquely capturing your special moments is our priority.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true about a mixed economy:?",
    "A": "The government is the primary economic decision maker and also regulates individual and business behavior.",
    "B": "Individuals are the primary economic decision makers, and businesses control and regulate the system.",
    "C": "Businesses are the primary economic decision makers, and the government controls the system.",
    "D": "Individuals and businesses are the primary economic decision makers, and the government",
    "answer": "D: Individuals and businesses are the primary economic decision makers, and the government",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an operating expense for a business:?",
    "A": "Cost of goods C. Revenues",
    "B": "Employees' withholding D. Utilities Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 2 12. Economies of scale are highly dependent on average A. marginal cost.",
    "C": "revenue. B. total cost.",
    "D": "marginal revenue.",
    "answer": "D: marginal revenue.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following causes the greatest number of cultural sensitivity issues:?",
    "A": "Communication C. Globalization",
    "B": "Level of comfort with uncertainty D. Relationships to time and space 14. Porter said to the group, \"If we agree to proceed with this plan, the company's profitability will increase substantially. Because the company will be saving a lot of money, we are more likely to receive a higher pay increase next year.\" Porter is persuading the group members by A. expressing empathy.",
    "C": "exerting his authority. B. promoting benefits.",
    "D": "arguing on minor points.",
    "answer": "A: Communication C. Globalization",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When employees demonstrate adaptability, they are able to be?",
    "A": "aggressive. C. honest.",
    "B": "flexible. D. creative. 16. One reason that an excellent business vision is general rather than specific is that A. employees must be told exactly what to do. B. it mus t be short term.",
    "C": "everyone in the organization must be able to relate to it.",
    "D": "it must be compelling and energizing.",
    "answer": "B: flexible. D. creative. 16. One reason that an excellent business vision is general rather than specific is that A. employees must be told exactly what to do. B. it mus t be short term.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gianna is attempting to build a strategic relationship with Nico, who is an influential member of the local business community. What is one technique Gianna could use to build the relationship?",
    "A": "Establishing dominance and control C. Seeking a deal as quickly as possible",
    "B": "Finding a shared vision D. Focusing on Nico's shortcomings 18. Which of the following techniques is the best example of leveraging existing business relationships: A. Deleting negative client reviews",
    "C": "Calling clients just to say hello B. Avoiding meeting new people",
    "D": "Sending holiday cards to clients",
    "answer": "B: Finding a shared vision D. Focusing on Nico's shortcomings 18. Which of the following techniques is the best example of leveraging existing business relationships: A. Deleting negative client reviews",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following businesses is the best example of an entrepreneurial venture:?",
    "A": "A juice bar decides to purchase trucks to sell juice on location during special events.",
    "B": "A veterinarian invents and sells a device to prevent horse water troughs from freezing.",
    "C": "A pumpkin farm offers pumpkin carving and costume contests to create more interest.",
    "D": "A bakery creates a \"cretzel,\" a cross between a crescent and a pretzel, as a new product.",
    "answer": "B: A veterinarian invents and sells a device to prevent horse water troughs from freezing.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following attitudes should an entrepreneur have about new technological developments:?",
    "A": "New technologies should be applied to all business practices.",
    "B": "New technologies are overrated and should be avoided.",
    "C": "The impact of new technologies should always be evaluated.",
    "D": "The benefits of new technologies do not outweigh their high cost.",
    "answer": "C: The impact of new technologies should always be evaluated.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding international trade is true:?",
    "A": "Companies shipping internationally must use freight-forwarding services.",
    "B": "Only large companies typically benefit from conducting international trade.",
    "C": "Internet-based companies can easily become involved in international trade.",
    "D": "Foreign language skills are required to conduct international trade.",
    "answer": "C: Internet-based companies can easily become involved in international trade.",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One factor that an entrepreneur should consider when assessing a venture opportunity is whether it will",
    "A": "involve com plicated paperwork. C. lead to more opportunities.",
    "B": "require employee loyalty. D. satisfy vendors' needs. Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 3 23. Which of the following statements about feasibility studies is true: A. The feasibility study is essentially the written business model. B. A feasibility study is not necessary if similar businesses already exist.",
    "C": "Each feasibility study must focus on only one potential business model.",
    "D": "The feasibility study is completed before the business plan is developed.",
    "answer": "C: Each feasibility study must focus on only one potential business model.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One-time startup c osts often include __________ fees.",
    "A": "website maintenance C. trade association",
    "B": "shipping and postage D. incorporation 25. Which of the following situations is an example of a social risk that is associated with starting a new business: A. When Ni gel started his new business, he took out a bank loan and used his home as collateral. B. As a new business owner, Cassidy is so worried about failing that she develops an ulcer.",
    "C": "Adam is working 14 hours a day at his new company and is not spending ti me with friends.",
    "D": "Julie, a successful businessperson, is willing to quit her job to start a new business.",
    "answer": "D: Julie, a successful businessperson, is willing to quit her job to start a new business.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Evan does not want the legal obligation of repaying a loan and is willing to share profits with others. Which of the following options is E van most likely to select to fund a new venture:",
    "A": "Community bank C. Trade credit",
    "B": "Collateral savings D. Private equity 27. Which of the following questions would Allison ask herself when deciding if she should hire an assistant for her growing business: A. Can I trust this person to get the work done on time? B. How will I recruit applicants for the job?",
    "C": "Does the workload require a full-time or part-time employee?",
    "D": "Does this applicant meet my minimal educational requirements?",
    "answer": "D: Does this applicant meet my minimal educational requirements?",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Although hiring a highly skilled employee is an added expense, a business owner benefits because the employee's activities increase the firm's overall productivity based on his/her",
    "A": "attitude. C. expertise.",
    "B": "self-control. D. inability. 29. Because the MBC Company has one location that services the eastern part of the country and another location that services the western part of the country, the company's work flow is organized by A. territory.",
    "C": "authority. B. work teams.",
    "D": "relationship.",
    "answer": "C: authority. B. work teams.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Small-business owners often obtain ideas for new venture opportunities when they",
    "A": "analyze their companies' sales reports. C. apply for a commercial bank loan.",
    "B": "talk with their customers and vendors. D. revise their operating budgets. 31. When Deanna, a small-business owner, allocates 6% of her company's profit to product development, she is investing which type of resource: A. Financial",
    "C": "Strategic B. Fundamental",
    "D": "Structural",
    "answer": "B: talk with their customers and vendors. D. revise their operating budgets. 31. When Deanna, a small-business owner, allocates 6% of her company's profit to product development, she is investing which type of resource: A. Financial",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A car company has decided to invest less in its suc cessful pickup truck and to use those funds instead on the development of its new hybrid vehicle. This is an example of",
    "A": "risk mitigation. C. a harvest strategy.",
    "B": "a marketing plan. D. the discovery process. 33. Which of the following presents the first three steps in the accounting cycle in the correct order: A. Analyze, post, and journalize",
    "C": "Post, analyze and journalize B. Analyze, journalize, and post",
    "D": "Post, journalize, and analyze",
    "answer": "C: Post, analyze and journalize B. Analyze, journalize, and post",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Pete is preparing a cash flow statement for his new bu siness. If the startup costs are $27,645 and he has $36,200 cash, how much cash is available for Pete to operate the business?",
    "A": "$9,125 C. $8,555",
    "B": "$7,545 D. $8,265 35. Le' Grand Hotel experienced record profits and chose to reinvest those profits back into the hotel for a major remodeling project. Where would these retained earnings be represented on a balance sheet? A. Under revenue",
    "C": "Under contributed capital B. Under assets",
    "D": "Under stockholders' equity",
    "answer": "C: Under contributed capital B. Under assets",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason why creditors review a business's income statement is to decide if the business will be able to",
    "A": "develop new products. C. increase staff.",
    "B": "expand operations. D. repay a loan. 37. When a business seeks to establish a budget or make major business decisions, what type of accounting does it use? A. Financial accounting",
    "C": "Forensic accounting B. Managerial accounting",
    "D": "Internal auditing",
    "answer": "D: Internal auditing",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses that obtain credit from banks usually are required to provide acceptable",
    "A": "collateral. C. promotion.",
    "B": "technolog y. D. compensation. 39. A small restaurant wants to expand, but first it needs to raise funds. John wants to raise capital through debt financing, but his partner, Damien, isn't sure that's a good idea. What is one downside of debt financing that Damien could cite to prove his point to John? A. Shareholders will own part of their business. B. They will have to pay interest on the borrowed amount.",
    "C": "They will need to sell stock in their business.",
    "D": "They will be required to repay the money immediately.",
    "answer": "A: collateral. C. promotion.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an intangible benefit that might be included in a cost-benefit analysis:?",
    "A": "Increased profits C. Reduced employee turnover",
    "B": "Decreased expenses D. Increased convenience 41. The CEO of a medium-sized business asked the top five executives to each prepare a sales forecast for the upcoming year. The forecasts were then averaged together to get the composite forecast. What method of forecasting was used? A. Jury of executive opinion",
    "C": "The Delphi technique B. Sales force composite",
    "D": "Survey of buyer intentions",
    "answer": "D: Survey of buyer intentions",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following equations should employees know when they are verifying the accuracy of a business's balance sheet:?",
    "A": "Owner's Equity = Available Cash-Liabilities",
    "B": "Assets = Liabilities + Owner's Equity",
    "C": "Assets = Owner's Equity-Liabilities",
    "D": "Owner's Equity = Liabilities + Available Cash",
    "answer": "B: Assets = Liabilities + Owner's Equity",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following phrases is most likely to be listed in an official job description:?",
    "A": "\"Possess an associate's degree or higher\" C. \"Able to work closely with others\"",
    "B": "\"Have 10-15 years' experience\" D. \"Edit company newsletter\" 44. What is a factor that a growing business might consider when determining hiring needs? A. The business's sampling plan",
    "C": "Emplo yee to customer ratio B. Type of application required",
    "D": "Bonuses that customers demand",
    "answer": "D: Bonuses that customers demand",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the benefits to the business of an effective employee selection procedure is a(n)",
    "A": "reduction in the need for orientation. C. appropriate match of employees to jobs.",
    "B": "rapid rate of employee turnover. D. good supply of employees to train. 46. What type of information about employees do most businesses maintain in their personnel records? A. Family history",
    "C": "Past work exper ience B. Political affiliation",
    "D": "Country of origin",
    "answer": "C: Past work exper ience B. Political affiliation",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a supervisor must take disciplinary action, the supervisor should adopt a __________ attitude.?",
    "A": "stern C. wait-and-see",
    "B": "critical D. nonjudgmental 48. Why is it important for businesses to obtain marketing information about economic conditions, political systems, and technological changes throughout the world? A. To understand geography",
    "C": "To import products B. To remain competitive",
    "D": "To eliminate trade quotas",
    "answer": "D: To eliminate trade quotas",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses need a great deal of information to make effective decisions and solve specific problems. This information is usually obtained through",
    "A": "marketing research. C. observation.",
    "B": "financial management. D. data analysis. 50. The marketing function that includes creating strategies to attract the target customer to a business is A. market planning.",
    "C": "marketing-information management. B. pricing.",
    "D": "channel management.",
    "answer": "A: marketing research. C. observation.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For the strategy of conducting customer surveys, with tactics including contacting customers and tabulating survey results, which of the following is the goal:",
    "A": "Improving this year's customer satisfaction by 7% over last year's ratings",
    "B": "Improving this year's telemarketing skills by 7% over last year's skills",
    "C": "Improv ing this year's proposal writing by 7% over last year's writing",
    "D": "Improving this year's sales training results by 7% over last year's results",
    "answer": "A: Improving this year's customer satisfaction by 7% over last year's ratings",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A purpose of market identification is to focus the marketer's selling efforts on the __________ market.",
    "A": "retail C. target",
    "B": "consumer D. industrial 53. When analyzing market potential, businesses often look at consumer psychographic factors, such as personality characteristics and A. occupation.",
    "C": "income. B. gender.",
    "D": "lifestyles.",
    "answer": "C: income. B. gender.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a factor that new businesses consider when conducting an analysis of competitors in a specific market:?",
    "A": "Size and availability of space C. Cost of supplies and equipment",
    "B": "Product quality and price D. Industry research and training 55. One of the objectives in a business's marketing plan is to increase sales by 15% by reaching more customers. What dollar amount is 15% if the business currently has 250 customers who each spend $10,000 per year? A. $425,000",
    "C": "$375,000 B. $250,000",
    "D": "$515,000",
    "answer": "B: Product quality and price D. Industry research and training 55. One of the objectives in a business's marketing plan is to increase sales by 15% by reaching more customers. What dollar amount is 15% if the business currently has 250 customers who each spend $10,000 per year? A. $425,000",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about information:?",
    "A": "It is simple to manage. C. It is the same thing as data.",
    "B": "It is data put into a useful form. D. It has no value for an organization. Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 6 57. Which of the following is a specification that a business might establish for selecting spreadsheet software programs: A. Regularly organize customer information",
    "C": "Graphically display financial information B. Electronically communicate data",
    "D": "Digitally produce marketing data",
    "answer": "B: It is data put into a useful form. D. It has no value for an organization. Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 6 57. Which of the following is a specification that a business might establish for selecting spreadsheet software programs: A. Regularly organize customer information",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Trent was reviewing a business record that did not reflect updated information. The quality of the business record was compromised because it was",
    "A": "irrelevant. C. unorganized.",
    "B": "unavailable. D. inaccurate. 59. Company B's management has determined that it must downsize. Three persons in the customer service department will lose their jobs. Which of the following records can management use to help them determine which employees to keep: A. Human resources records",
    "C": "R&D records B. Production recor ds",
    "D": "Inventory records",
    "answer": "D: Inventory records",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Running out of inventory can result in",
    "A": "more satisfied customers. C. higher productivity.",
    "B": "higher taxes. D. lost sales. 61. Which of the following is an example of a safety procedure that a business might require i ts employees to follow: A. Review products to ensure quality standards are met. B. Place equipment in front of the business's emergency exits.",
    "C": "Wear protective headgear when working in hazardous areas.",
    "D": "Store supplies in the facility's offices, clos ets, and aisles.",
    "answer": "D: Store supplies in the facility's offices, clos ets, and aisles.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An important consideration when coordinating sequential tasks with team members is",
    "A": "timing. C. pricing.",
    "B": "durability. D. credibility. 63. Planning the quantities to produce is an important part of production planning because it helps A. prevent losses to the business.",
    "C": "increase consumer demand for the product. B. sequence the steps in production.",
    "D": "locate the resources needed for the product.",
    "answer": "A: timing. C. pricing.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding operating costs:?",
    "A": "Only some businesses have them. C. They occur once or twice a year.",
    "B": "They are fixed expenses. D. They are not directly related to production. 65. Service contract A costs $1,500 yearly and includes 12 service calls each year. Service cont ract B costs $600 yearly and charges $70 per call up to 12 calls each year. Which contract is less expensive and by what amount? A. Contract A by $80",
    "C": "Contract B by $60 B. Contract B by $50",
    "D": "Contract A by $70",
    "answer": "D: Contract A by $70",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One tool a business can use to cont rol expenses is a(n)",
    "A": "ratio. C. budget.",
    "B": "balance sheet. D. income statement. 67. Which of the following must occur for supply chain management to be successful: A. Few people should be involved in operations. B. Producers should be in contact wit h final customers.",
    "C": "Emphasis should be placed on internal activities.",
    "D": "Goods and communication should flow both ways.",
    "answer": "C: Emphasis should be placed on internal activities.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Luke is reviewing several internal and external reports to compare his company's sales and market share in relation to those of other companies in the industry. What type of business analysis is Luke conducting?",
    "A": "Promotional C. Financial",
    "B": "Competitive D. Productivity 69. Which of the following is an example of business process thinking: A. A company strives to fix its method of internal communications. B. The marketing department and finance department avoid interacting.",
    "C": "Whenever a customer complains about slow service, servers are fired.",
    "D": "A company prioritizes product promotions over product development.",
    "answer": "B: Competitive D. Productivity 69. Which of the following is an example of business process thinking: A. A company strives to fix its method of internal communications. B. The marketing department and finance department avoid interacting.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Stress and fatigue are __________ factors that can affect business process design.",
    "A": "technological C. regulatory",
    "B": "human D. government 71. A business process change would likely be required if a company A. plans a meet ing for Friday.",
    "C": "merges with another company. B. goes out of business.",
    "D": "has a profitable quarter.",
    "answer": "B: human D. government 71. A business process change would likely be required if a company A. plans a meet ing for Friday.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does supply chain management increase customer satisfaction?",
    "A": "Reduces the time it takes for goods to reach consumers",
    "B": "Integrates inform ation throughout an organization",
    "C": "Improves cash flow",
    "D": "Enhances data quality",
    "answer": "A: Reduces the time it takes for goods to reach consumers",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bernard's business is more successful than his competitors' because he is innovative, which gives him a(n) __________ advantage.",
    "A": "competitive C. absolute",
    "B": "creative D. administrative 74. Corporate governance is primarily concerned with __________ desires. A. CEO",
    "C": "vendor B. stakeholder",
    "D": "competitor",
    "answer": "A: competitive C. absolute",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A top-level executive is removed from his position on the Golden Ray Corporation's board of directors due to a personal scandal. The board then releases a detailed, professional statement to its stakeholders so they are aware of the situation. By doing this, Golden Ray Corporation is",
    "A": "lacking accountability. C. following regulatory guidelines.",
    "B": "demonstrating transparency. D. measuring internal performance. 76. Which of the following business activities is most likely to impact an organization's governance structures: A. Raising prices on consumer goods",
    "C": "Developing a marketing strategy B. Hiring a new sales representative",
    "D": "Borrowing money from a bank",
    "answer": "B: demonstrating transparency. D. measuring internal performance. 76. Which of the following business activities is most likely to impact an organization's governance structures: A. Raising prices on consumer goods",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Performance standards should be",
    "A": "extremely challenging. C. informally discussed.",
    "B": "subjective. D. measurable. 78. The determination of an exchange price acceptable to both the buyer and the seller of a product is called A. product decision.",
    "C": "place decision. B. promotion.",
    "D": "pricing.",
    "answer": "D: pricing.",
    "topic": "Pricing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is not a factor that affects selling price:?",
    "A": "Government regulation C. Competition",
    "B": "Supply and demand D. Profit control Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 8 80. Which of the following would be most useful to a business that is evaluating customer experience: A. Online customer reviews",
    "C": "Consumer trends B. Sales data",
    "D": "Kiosks",
    "answer": "D: Kiosks",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A fast-food company offers burgers, chicken nuggets, pizza, and french fries. Eventually, the company realizes that the pizzas are not profitable and decides to stop selling them. Which product-mix strategy is the company using?",
    "A": "Trading down C. Alteration",
    "B": "Trading up D. Contraction 82. Customer services that all retailers should provide include A. delivery service and play areas for children. B. convenient store hours and receipts for purchases.",
    "C": "merchandise repair and restaurants.",
    "D": "alterations and fashion shows.",
    "answer": "D: alterations and fashion shows.",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your target market is \"poor\" college students, so you base your unique selling proposition (USP) on value pricing. This is an example of a USP that is",
    "A": "meaningful to the customer. C. desirable and urgent.",
    "B": "difficult to communicate. D. fulfillable. 84. Pat's Pizza Place has introduced a new, low-fat pizza crust. In its advertising, management not only describes how tasty the crust is, but it also tells readers that the crust is low-fat and healthy. Pat's Pizza Place is using which of the following promotional communication characteristics: A. Relevance",
    "C": "Factual B. Repetitious",
    "D": "Persuasive",
    "answer": "A: meaningful to the customer. C. desirable and urgent.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following plans includes procedures for dealing with events that threaten to shut down business oper ations for an extended period of time:?",
    "A": "Safety plan C. Business plan",
    "B": "Continuity plan D. Asset security plan 86. What is an example of an amplified word-of-mouth strategy? A. A customer shares her opinion of a new product with a friend. B. Fans s hare the release date for a new product on Facebook.",
    "C": "Customers post comments about a company on Twitter.",
    "D": "A company asks customers to share product reviews on a website.",
    "answer": "B: Continuity plan D. Asset security plan 86. What is an example of an amplified word-of-mouth strategy? A. A customer shares her opinion of a new product with a friend. B. Fans s hare the release date for a new product on Facebook.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The primary cost factors that marketers must consider when developing a direct advertising campaign include list acquisition, delivery, and",
    "A": "research. C. production.",
    "B": "inventory. D. follow-up. 88. Ben recently purchased a cell phone. The manufacturer provided a form and a special code with the phone's packaging. Ben completed the form, copied his sales receipt, and mailed these items back to the manufacturer along with the part of the packaging that contained the special code. Within six weeks, Ben received a $50 check from the phone manufacturer. What type of sales-promotion technique was used? A. Sweepstakes",
    "C": "Rebate B. Coupon",
    "D": "Warranty",
    "answer": "C: Rebate B. Coupon",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An important activity performed by a business's public relations staff is",
    "A": "territory development. C. crisis management.",
    "B": "market segmentation. D. talent acquisition. Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 9 90. Which of the following is a situation indicating a problem with product durability: A. A customer complains that her/his new c ell phone battery quit working after one week. B. A customer returns a recently purchased sweater because it is the wrong size.",
    "C": "A customer complains to a restaurant server that his/her steak is too rare.",
    "D": "A customer returns a software package because it does not work with her/his computer.",
    "answer": "C: A customer complains to a restaurant server that his/her steak is too rare.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A risk management program helps __________ risk, which makes it easier to organize and handle them.",
    "A": "categorize C. prevent",
    "B": "encourage D. process 92. Why has enterprise risk management developed? A. The elimination of certain insurance plans",
    "C": "Reduced government regulation B. An increasingly diverse array of risks",
    "D": "Declining quality standards",
    "answer": "A: categorize C. prevent",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a tangible item that can be sold:?",
    "A": "Computer C. Haircut",
    "B": "Car wash D. Lawyer's advice 94. Who is usually responsible for developing and promoting an ethical atmosphere in a business? A. Consultants",
    "C": "Attorneys B. Employees",
    "D": "Managers",
    "answer": "A: Computer C. Haircut",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are components generally included in a company's business plan:?",
    "A": "Marketing plan, summary, and franchise agreement",
    "B": "Company description, financial plan, and marketing plan",
    "C": "Management plan, licensing contract, and annual report",
    "D": "Summary, operating plan, and sales report",
    "answer": "B: Company description, financial plan, and marketing plan",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A busines s should consider the impact that changes in the environment will have on the business's marketing mix because",
    "A": "government regulations can increase costs. C. the marketing mix is affected by technology.",
    "B": "most businesses want to be reactive. D. the business can change its marketing mix. 97. When an advertiser sends postage-paid sweepstakes entry forms to individuals, the advertiser is using __________ direct mail advertising. A. utility",
    "C": "reminder B. informative",
    "D": "persuasive",
    "answer": "D: persuasive",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does a bus iness's gross profit compare to the industry standard of 30% if it has annual sales of $400,000 and cost of goods sold is $260,000?",
    "A": "35% higher C. 35% lower",
    "B": "5% lower D. 5% higher 99. Which of the following factors is associated with innovative org anizations: A. Leadership gaps",
    "C": "Adaptability B. Change avoidance",
    "D": "Fear motivated",
    "answer": "D: Fear motivated",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Antonio has been tasked with helping the accounting staff at his company make the transition to a new recordkeeping software. He has been instructed to facilitat e training sessions, answer employee questions, and show the staff how the new software will help make their jobs easier. Antonio is performing __________ management.",
    "A": "change C. operations",
    "B": "inventory D. supply chain Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 10 1. C Defamation. Defamation is the publication of an untrue statement that subjects an entity to ridicule or contempt. Jack is publishing untrue information about his former employer out of spite, so he is committing defamation. Invasion of privacy occurs when a person's personal life is exposed unnecessarily. Battery is intentionally touching another in a harmful or offensive way without justification. Negligence includes situations i n which harm is caused accidentally. None of these three types of torts apply to Jack. SOURCE: BL:069 SOURCE: Miller, R.L. (2020). Business law today: The essentials (12th ed.) [p. 108]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc. 2. C Intellectual property. Int ellectual property refers to the ownership of ideas. Unlike tangible assets such as cars or computers, intellectual property is a collection of ideas and concepts. In many countries, there are three ways to protect intellectual property: patents, trademark s, and copyrights. Patents protect processes, methods, and inventions. Trademarks protect brand names-including words and symbols that are used to identify a product or company. A copyright will protect the following categories of work: literary works; mus ical works; dramatic works; choreographic works; pictorial, graphic, and sculptural works; motion pictures; sound recordings; architectural works; and computer programs and websites. Patents, trademarks, and copyrights do not protect physical inventions, h ouses and apartments, or government secrets. SOURCE: BL:051 SOURCE: Entrepreneur. (2017). Intellectual property. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from https://www.entrepreneur.com/encyclopedia/intellectual-property 3. B Open corporations. Individuals who invest their money in an open, or public, corporation are known as stockholders, or shareholders, because what they actually purchase are shares of stock in the corporation. This gives the investors the opportunity to share in the growth and possible profits of the corporation. General partnerships are owned by two or more partners. A close corporation is owned by a few people and does not offer its shares for sale to the general public. A sole proprietorship is owned by one person. SOURCE: BL:003 SOURCE: LAP-BL-001-Own It Your Way (Business Ownership) 4. A Sole proprietorship. Owners of sole proprietorships bear all the responsibility and decision-making for the business. Since there is one owner, the sole proprietor maintains control of every aspect of the business. General partnerships, \"S\" corporations, and LLCs have more owners; therefore, each owner generally has less control over business activities. SOURCE: BL:006 SOURCE: LAP-BL-006-Taking Care of Business (Selecting Forms of Business Ownership) 5. D Getting their products to consumers more efficiently. Channels of distribution benefit businesses by getting their products to consumers more efficiently. This may help raise profits, but it is not a guarantee. Channels may lower the prices of some but not all industrial goods. Channels allow businesses to share channel tasks, but they will not be able to avoid all channel tasks-every channel member contributes. SOURCE: CM:001 SOURCE: LAP-CM-002-Chart Your Channels (Channel Management) 6. A Producer to consumer. When goods are sold directly from the producer to the consumer, this is a direct channel of distribution. All of the other alternatives involve one or more intermediaries between the producer and the consumer. These are examples of indirect channels of distribution. SOURCE: CM:003 SOURCE: LAP-CM-003-Channel It (Channels of Distribution) Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 11 7. C Global industry benchmarking system. A global system provides a standard rating system with which to evaluate the effectiveness of international channel members. Because of the cultural, social, and political differences that exist outside of a company's national boundaries, the company's norm may not apply in these cases. A neutral third party familiar with international expectations may be a better judge of the channel member's effectiveness. The International Monetary Fund deals with exchange rates and differences in international currency. International trade centers and global distribution centers are examples of international channel members. SOURCE: CM:011 SOURCE: Wisner, J.D., Tan, K., & Leong, G.K. (2019). Principles of supply chain management (5th ed.) [Lesson 14-3]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc. 8. C Help with major decisions. A complex business report is a well-organized presentation of accurate information gathered to help with major business decisions. It summarizes the most important data, but it may not present all views on the subject. In most cases, it includes recommendations for action or suggested solutions for problems. SOURCE: CO:009 SOURCE: Guffey, M.E., & Loewy, D. (2019). Essentials of business communication (11th ed.) [Lesson 10-1a]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc. 9. C Henderson Photography...uniquely capturing your special moments is our priority. The brand promise is a company's agreement (spoken or unspoken) with customers that it will consistently meet their expectations and deliver on its brand characteristics and values. Henderson Photography tells you exactly what you can expect every time you purchase its services-unique photos to capture special moments. Fred's Furniture is offering sale prices for a limited time. The business offering credit terms to qualified customers has also placed time restrictions on its offer and has limited the offer to some rather than all customers. Rather than a brand promise, the businesses are using promotion. Cup O' Joe is communicating the convenience of having four locations. SOURCE: CR:001 SOURCE: Hinge. (2016, January 4). Elements of a successful brand 4: Brand promise. Retrieve d September 6, 2019, from http://hingemarketing.com/library/article/elements_of_a_successful_brand_4_brand_promise/?pivot/archive/2007-06/index.html 10. D Individuals and businesses are the primary economic decision makers, and the government helps regulate the system. A private enterprise system is an economic system in which individuals and groups, rather than the government, own or control the means of production. A private enterprise system is considered a mixed economy because individuals and businesses are the primary economic decision makers, while the government helps regulate and control the system. The government's activities serve to promote a fair competitive buying and selling environment. In a command economic system (communism), the government controls the economic system and does not allow private ownership of the means of production and distribution. SOURCE: EC:009 SOURCE: LAP-EC-015-People Power (The Private Enterprise System) 11. D Utilities. Operating expenses are those expenses nece ssary to keep the business running on a daily basis. They include utilities, rent, payroll, insurance, taxes, and supplies. Cost of goods is a separate category of expense, not part of operating expenses. Revenues are all categories of income that bring money into the business. Employees' withholding taxes are paid by the employees, not by the business. SOURCE: EC:010 SOURCE: LAP-EC-002-Risk Rewarded (Factors Affecting Profit) Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 12 12. B Total cost. The average total cost curve is what a manager should be looking at when s/he thinks about increasing or decreasing company size, because it shows the average total cost to the company per unit produced. The average marginal cost per unit produced would not give an accurate picture of the company's financial sit uation because it only shows the cost incurred per each additional unit produced. Analysis of the average revenue and average marginal revenue would only show how much the company is profiting on average, respectively, in terms of total average output and per each additional unit produced. This information by itself gives no insight into the cost incurred by the company in the production process. SOURCE: EC:077 SOURCE: Gottheil, F.M. (2013). Principles of economics (7th ed.) [pp. 190-193]. Mason, OH: South-Western Cengage Learning. 13. A Communication. Communication, both verbal and nonverbal, causes the greatest number of cultural sensitivity issues. Level of comfort with uncertainty and relationships to time and space also cause cultural sensitivity issues, but not as many as communication does. Globalization is a trend that is making the world seem a lot smaller-it offers proof that diversity is inevitable. SOURCE: EI:033 SOURCE: LAP-EI-033-Getting To Know You (Cultural Sensitiv ity) 14. B Promoting benefits. Persuasion is the ability to get people to see things your way, to do things your way, and to agree with you. Persuasion often involves appealing to others' wants and needs, and presenting information in such a way that it encourages them to support the idea or action. In the example, Porter discussed the benefit of a pay raise. Empathy is the ability to identify with another person's thoughts, feelings, values, and actions. There is no indication that Porter holds a positio n of authority or that he is arguing with someone on minor points. SOURCE: EI:012 SOURCE: LAP-QS-010-Win Them Over (Persuade Others) 15. B Flexible. Flexibility is the ability to adapt to changes as they occur. When employees are demonstrating adaptabili ty, they are able to be flexible and adjust to changing conditions. When employees demonstrate adaptability, they are not necessarily being aggressive, honest, or creative. SOURCE: EI:006 SOURCE: LAP-EI-023-Go With the Flow (Demonstrating Adaptability) 16. C Everyone in the organization must be able to relate to it. One reason that an excellent business vision is general rather than specific is that everyone in the organization must be able to relate to it. Team members should be able to relate the team v ision to their own personal visions for what they want to accomplish in their own careers and also for the organization. Excellent visions are meant for the long term. Employees don't always need to be told exactly what to do. Excellent visions are compell ing and energizing, but this does not relate to them being general or specific. SOURCE: EI:060 SOURCE: LAP-EI-060-Vision Quest (Enlisting Others in Vision) 17. B Finding a shared vision. Strategic relationships are successfully formed when both sides share a common vision that they can work toward together. Both parties will be equally motivated to succeed. Establishing dominance and control, seeking a deal as quickly as possible, and focusing on Nico's shortcomings will hinder Gianna from building a strategic relationship with Nico. SOURCE: EI:114 SOURCE: McKay, K. (2014, June 3). How to create strategic partnerships that are a win-win. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/234425 Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 13 18. D Sending holiday cards to clients. \"Leveraging\" means making the most out of something. In business, leveraging a relationship means maximizing the benefits of the relationship for your company. Leveraging business relationships is important for retaining current customers and continuing to obtain new customers. One example of leveraging an existing business relationship is sending holiday cards to clients. Sending a card is a thoughtful gesture that says to the client, \"We care about you.\" Avoiding meeting new people would not help an indiv idual leverage his/her existing relationships. Calling clients just to say hello would be unwise, since many customers are annoyed by unexpected and unimportant phone calls. Deleting negative client reviews is not only unethical, but would also not help leverage an existing relationship. SOURCE: EI:116 SOURCE: Wayshak, M. (2018). 7 ways to leverage existing customers for more sales. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/281492 19. B A veterinarian invents and sells a device to prevent horse water troughs from freezing. Creating a product to solve a problem and selling that product is a good example of an entrepreneurial venture because a need has been identified and met; the product s olves a problem for consumers, while the resulting sales benefit the veterinarian. A juice bar selling juice on location during special events expands its business but does not represent a new idea or problem solved. A pumpkin farm offering pumpkin carving and costume contests to create more interest is not creating something new or solving a problem. A \"cretzel\" might be a new creative pastry, but there is no indication that it meets an identified consumer need. SOURCE: EN:039 SOURCE: Allen, K.R. (2020). L aunching new ventures: An entrepreneurial approach (8th ed.) [p. 5]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc. 20. C The impact of new technologies should always be evaluated. An entrepreneur should always evaluate the potential impact that new technologies could have on business opportunities and competition. While the application of technology to business practices often has huge benefits, it is not always feasible or wise to apply them to every business practice. While the benefits of new technologies may be expensive or overrated sometimes, their impact and business potential should always be evaluated. SOURCE: EN:040 SOURCE: Kokemuller, N. (2019, July 29). Why is technology important in business? Retrieved September 6, 2019, from https://bizfluent.com/about-6320228-technology-important-business-.html 21. C Internet-based companies can easily become involved in international trade. A company that has a website can easily be found by people in foreign countries, and online services like eBay make international transactions easy to conduct. Small businesses represent a large majority of international trade. Freight-forwarding services are often used by companies, but they are not required. Foreign language skills may be helpful, but they are not required to conduct international trade since people in many countries speak more than one language and translation services exist. SOURCE: EN:041 SOURCE: Katz, J., & Green, R. (2011). Entrepreneurial small business (3rd ed.) [pp. 351-356]. New York, NY: McGraw-Hill/Irwin. Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 14 22. C Lead to more opportunities. A circumstance that presents itself as a favorable means to become a business is referred to as a venture opportunity. When an entrepreneur assesses the venture opportunity, s/he determines the chances of success. One factor the entrepreneur considers during the assessment is the potential for the venture opportunity to create more opportunities. These other opportunities might include the ability to develop additional products, appeal to different mark et segments, and expand via multi-units or franchising efforts. When an entrepreneur hires employees, s/he usually expects employee loyalty, regardless of the type of venture s/he is starting. The government requires all businesses to complete paperwork (e.g., tax forms), which is often complex. Therefore, paperwork is not a primary consideration, nor is satisfying its vendors' needs. SOURCE: EN:005 SOURCE: Ray, L. (2018, October 17). 5 steps to evaluating business opportunities. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/5-steps-evaluating-business-opportunities-44673.html 23. D The feasibility study is completed before the business plan is developed. A feasibility study can be used to determine the viability of several business alternatives, regardless of whether similar businesses already exist. The feasibility study pinpoints the strengths and weaknesses of each alternative so that the business idea that seems to have the best chance of success can be selected. After the most viabl e alternative is chosen, then a business plan, which is essentially the written business model for that alternative, can be developed. SOURCE: EN:038 SOURCE: Profitable Venture Magazine Ltd. (2009-2019). Feasibility study vs. Business plan-What's the dif ference. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from https://www.profitableventure.com/feasibility-study-business-plan/24. D Incorporation. Some of the expenses that an entrepreneur must pay during the startup phase are one-time costs, while other costs are ongoi ng. An example of a one-time cost is an incorporation fee, which an entrepreneur must pay if s/he chooses to incorporate the new business. Trade association membership fees, shipping and postage costs, and website maintenance are typically routine, ongoing expenses that the business must pay on a regular basis. SOURCE: EN:009 SOURCE: SmallBusiness.com. (2018, October 13). Starting a small business. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from http://wiki.smallbusiness.com/wiki/Starting_a_small_business 25. C Adam is working 14 hours a day at his new company and is not spending time with friends. There are many types of risks when starting a new business. Because many new business owners focus their attention on their businesses, they often neglect relationships with family and friends. This is social risk because there is a possibility of losing personal relationships when people do not spend time together in social situations. Another type of risk is physical risk. This occurs when a new business owner is under stres s and develops an illness or physical ailment, such as an ulcer. Obtaining a bank loan is a financial risk, while quitting a job may present a career risk. SOURCE: EN:010 SOURCE: Loesch, B. (2012, April 3). 6 commonly overlooked risks when starting a new business. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from http://www.business2community.com/startups/6-commonly-overlooked-risks-when-starting-a-new-business-0158188#acXl2uBTHM3aV2gM.97 Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 15 26. D Private equity. When a startup business owner obtains money in a way that s/he does not have debt, it is called private equity. This may include using personal savings, receiving money from friends and relatives, or soliciting support from private investor s. Private investors generally expect a financial return on their investment. Credit and banks are debt-based ways to finance a business because these options involve repaying a loan. Collateral savings is a fictitious term. SOURCE: EN:016 SOURCE: Riley, J. (2019). Sources of finance for a startup or small business. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from https://www.tutor2u.net/business/reference/sources-of-finance-for-a-startup-or-small-business 27. C Does the workload require a full-time or part-time employe e? A business owner considers many factors when determining if s/he should hire an employee. An important factor to consider is the nature of the work that the owner needs to have done-bookkeeping, purchasing, ad placement, etc. The owner must also consider how often certain tasks are performed (e.g., weekly, monthly). After determining what skills are needed, the owner must decide if there is enough work for a full-time employee or if a part-time employee could handle the workload. The business owner recruits applicants after determining the necessary skills and approximate workload. Therefore, the business owner cannot answer the remaining questions until s/he determines the type and amount of work s/he needs the employee to do. SOURCE: EN:018 SOURCE: Katz, J., & Green, R. (2011). Entrepreneurial small business (3rd ed.) [pp. 607-615]. New York, NY: McGraw-Hill/Irwin. 28. C Expertise. Resources are the items or people that a business uses to accomplish a goal or to make a product. Small-business owners must consider both the costs and the benefits in obtaining the resources they need to operate their companies. When a business needs special knowledge to operate or expand, the owner may need to hire someone with a specific set of skills or expertise, which can be a substantial payroll expense. Self-control and a good attitude are good traits to have, and the company may benefit from them; but the employee must have the knowledge and skills to have the ability to perform tasks that others in the company cannot. SOURCE: EN:021 SOURCE: Bamford,",
    "C": "E., & Bruton, G.D. (2011). Entrepreneurship: A small business approach. (pp. 34, 78). New York, NY: McGraw-Hill. 29. A Territory. Work flow is the order in which information is shared, tasks are performed, and decisi ons are made in relation to activities that keep a business running. A business organizes its work flow in a manner that best suits the nature of the business and its goals. One way to organize work flow is to divide work-related tasks by geographic locati on, such as territory or region. When a business organizes groups to do specific short-or long-term projects, work flow is organized in work teams. Authority and relationship are not widely used terms that businesses use to describe work flow organization methods. SOURCE: EN:027 SOURCE: Bamford, C.E., & Bruton, G.D. (2011). Entrepreneurship: A small business approach (pp. 159-161). New York, NY: The McGraw-Hill Companies, Inc. Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 16 30. B Talk with their customers and vendors. An opportunity is a circumstance that presents itself as a favorable means to meet an objective. Many small-business owners are entrepreneurs-individuals who look for opportunities to start businesses and then take action to make the opportunities actualize. There are many wa ys to look for business opportunities, such as watching trends; attending trade shows; and talking with friends, customers, vendors, and business associates. Although an opportunity can present itself at any time, it doesn't usually happen while doing task s such as analyzing sales reports or revising operating budgets. After deciding to start the business, a small-business owner might apply for a commercial bank loan to finance a new venture. SOURCE: EN:031 SOURCE: Longenecker, J.G., Petty, J.W., Palich, L. E., & Hoy, F. (2020). Small business management: Launching and growing entrepreneurial ventures (19th ed.) [pp. 59-63]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc. 31. A Financial. As a business grows, the owner often needs to invest in additional resources to ef ficiently operate. A resource is a person or item that is needed to accomplish an objective. A profit is the money left over after paying expenses, which is a financial resource. Fundamental, strategic, and structural are not common terms that business owners use to describe types of resources. SOURCE: EN:032 SOURCE: QuickBooks. (2019). 3 ways small businesses can re-invest profits. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from https://quickbooks.intuit.com/r/cash-flow/3-ways-small-businesses-can-re-invest-profits/32. C A harvest strategy. A harvest strategy is the way an entrepreneur or investor extracts money from a business or product after it has become successful in order to invest it in something else. For example, if a car company's pickup truck is already suc cessful, it does not need the same level of funding that it once did. Those funds can be extracted and put into a new product, such as hybrid vehicles. This is not an example of a marketing plan, risk mitigation, or the discovery process. SOURCE: EN:035 SOURCE: Kenton, W., & Abbott, B. (2019, April 20). Harvest strategy. Retrieved September 6, 2019, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/h/harvest-strategy.asp 33. B Analyze, journalize, and post. The major steps of the accounting cycle-in their proper order-are analyzing financial transactions, journalizing transactions, posting to ledgers, balancing the books, preparing financial statements, and closing the books. SOURCE: FI:085 SOURCE: LAP-FI-085-Show Me the Money (Nature of Accounting) 34. C $8,555. Businesspeople prepare cash flow statements to estimate when, where, and how much money will flow into and out of a business during a certain period of time. The information in the cash flow statement can help the business plan financially. To determine the amount of cash that is available to operate the business, subtract the expenses from the total amount of cash ($36,200-$27,645 = $8,555). SOURCE: FI:092 SOURCE: Warren, C.S., & Taylor, W.B. (2020). Managerial accounting (15th ed.) [Lesson 15-1]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc. Test 1209 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM-KEY 17 35. D Under stockholders' equity. Retained earnings are represented under stockholders' equity because they are monies reinvested back into the business by the stockholder(s). Assets are considered resources owned by the company, not monies invested or reinvested into the business. Contributed capital refers to monies invested into the company by the owner or other investors, rather than profits or earnings that are reinvested into the company. Revenue refers to earnings fro m the sales of goods or services and is dealt with on income statements, not balance sheets. SOURCE: FI:093 SOURCE: Bienias, C., Gilbertson, C.B., Lehman, M.W., & Gentene,",
    "D": "(2019). Century 21 accounting:",
    "answer": "A: change C. operations",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following prevents individuals other than the holder from making, selling, or using an invention:?",
    "A": "Trademark C. Copyright",
    "B": "Patent D. Trade secret 3. Allison just started her own photography business. She will be working alone, and she doesn't anticipate many business expenses or lawsuits. Whi ch type of business ownership is best for Allison? A. Sole proprietorship",
    "C": "Corporation B. Limited liability company (LLC)",
    "D": "Partnership",
    "answer": "B: Patent D. Trade secret 3. Allison just started her own photography business. She will be working alone, and she doesn't anticipate many business expenses or lawsuits. Whi ch type of business ownership is best for Allison? A. Sole proprietorship",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the type of tax that businesses are required to collect from customers when they purchase certain goods or services:?",
    "A": "Corporate C. Estate",
    "B": "Income D. Sales 5. Loggins Forestry and Mill Company sells wood to Henderson Wood Products. Henderson sells the wood to Franklin Construction Company, who uses the wood to build homes and office buildings. What is the channel of distribution for the wood products? A. Agent to industrial user to retailer to consumer B. Producer to industrial user to consumer",
    "C": "Agent to wholesaler to consumer",
    "D": "Producer to industrial distributor to industrial user",
    "answer": "D: Producer to industrial distributor to industrial user",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Wingo's sells the products it produces through its own catalog, which is a form of ___________ distribution.",
    "A": "direct C. middleman",
    "B": "indirect D. industrial 7. A business deciding to sell c ustom-made items directly to consumers is an example of selecting a distribution channel based on the A. product.",
    "C": "price. B. market.",
    "D": "location.",
    "answer": "A: direct C. middleman",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following helps the reader find specific elements of a formal report:?",
    "A": "Table of contents C. Executive summary",
    "B": "Title page D. Conclusion 9. What should a successful brand promise be able to do? A. Convey a high-quality image",
    "C": "Customize the product for each customer B. Clarify the company's processes",
    "D": "Communicate an appealing benefit",
    "answer": "A: Table of contents C. Executive summary",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an uninsurable risk:?",
    "A": "Fire C. Customer buying habits",
    "B": "Business interruption D. Personal injury 11. Which of the following is an example of a government regulation that affects a business's working conditions: A. Minimum wage",
    "C": "Zoning laws B. Food inspection",
    "D": "Price supports",
    "answer": "C: Zoning laws B. Food inspection",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You are the manager of a small-scale manufacturing company. You are faced with the decision to buy newer, more expensive equipment that is highly efficient, or t o continue using the older, less efficient equipment. Your company would need to increase _________ to make up the cost of the purchase of the new equipment.",
    "A": "workers C. managers",
    "B": "output D. advertising 13. Which of the following are secondary dimensions of diversity: A. Family status, ethnicity, and communication style B. Religion, work experience, and gender",
    "C": "Income, family status, and education level",
    "D": "Work experience, nationality, and age",
    "answer": "B: output D. advertising 13. Which of the following are secondary dimensions of diversity: A. Family status, ethnicity, and communication style B. Religion, work experience, and gender",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rob has a job interview this afternoon. In the morning, he goes over his other job offers to figure out which job he will accept (and what the salary and benefits are) if this employer doesn't offer him a position. Rob is developing his",
    "A": "role. C. walk-away point.",
    "B": "BATNA. D. style. 15. The first step toward becoming a leader is A. believing you can do it.",
    "C": "becoming a manager. B. being a role model.",
    "D": "demonstrating empathy.",
    "answer": "B: BATNA. D. style. 15. The first step toward becoming a leader is A. believing you can do it.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When determining venture-creation opportunities, entrepreneurs must first?",
    "A": "conduct research. C. identify staffing needs.",
    "B": "obtain financing. D. select a location. 17. Which of the following statements is true regarding stakeholder expectations: A. Each group of stakeholders has different needs and expectations. B. Stakeholder expectations are always financially driven.",
    "C": "All stakeholders want to exert authority over employees.",
    "D": "Stakeholder expectations always come second to customer needs.",
    "answer": "A: conduct research. C. identify staffing needs.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to share the best techniques for performing a job task with your coworkers?",
    "A": "It can reduce your work responsibilities. C. It will convince your boss to promote you.",
    "B": "Your coworkers will consider you an expert. D. It builds good working relationships. 19. Which of the following sets of characteristics best describes careers in entrepreneurship: A. Unpredictable, low-risk",
    "C": "Expensive, low-energy, relaxed B. Routine, predictable",
    "D": "Innovative, risky, time-intensive",
    "answer": "D: Innovative, risky, time-intensive",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The entrepreneurs best equipped to work long hours and overcome obstacles are ones who possess",
    "A": "passi on for their work. C. technological skills.",
    "B": "financial knowledge. D. confidence. 21. Ariana wants to promote her handcrafted jewelry in several different countries. Promoting her products in multiple countries is most likely to result in A. exposur e to new markets.",
    "C": "fewer cultural barriers. B. reduced financial risk.",
    "D": "fewer compliance challenges.",
    "answer": "A: passi on for their work. C. technological skills.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step in entrepreneurial discovery?",
    "A": "Determining the risks and rewards C. Analyzing the feasibility of an idea",
    "B": "Screen ing the product ideas D. Identifying an unmet want or need 23. A person who is a high achiever is often positively viewed by others as a A. follower.",
    "C": "leader. B. show-off.",
    "D": "risk-taker.",
    "answer": "D: risk-taker.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What questio n should an entrepreneur ask regarding the timing of a new product release?",
    "A": "Should I move the product through direct or indirect channels?",
    "B": "Is the market willing and able to pay for the product?",
    "C": "How much money should I allocate for next month's advertising?",
    "D": "What is the optimal break-even point for the product?",
    "answer": "B: Is the market willing and able to pay for the product?",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The technical or logistical section of the feasibility study includes information about",
    "A": "what the target market wants. C. chain of command.",
    "B": "potential profitability. D. where the work will happen. 26. Jacob, a new business owner, is developing an inventory list of items to sell to customers. What type of planning activity is Jacob focusing on? A. Human resources",
    "C": "Financial B. Operational",
    "D": "Knowledge management",
    "answer": "D: Knowledge management",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a business opportunity that requires a person to purchase the right to sell an established good or service under the parent company's name:?",
    "A": "Incorporation C. Foreign",
    "B": "Franchise D. Brokerage 28. A small-business owner might register for trademark protection for the company's A. computer software.",
    "C": "trade secret. B. invention.",
    "D": "logo.",
    "answer": "B: Franchise D. Brokerage 28. A small-business owner might register for trademark protection for the company's A. computer software.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a primary factor that small-business owners should consider when deciding to hire additional staff members?",
    "A": "Training methods C. Payroll expenses",
    "B": "Interview techniques D. Product standards 30. What is a possible downside of obtaining investment from venture capitalists? A. The increased chance of failure",
    "C": "The slow rate of growth B. Repaying the money",
    "D": "Sharing company ownership",
    "answer": "C: The slow rate of growth B. Repaying the money",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sally wants to incorporate her company and contracts a law firm to handle the legal aspects of the process. This is an example of",
    "A": "outsourcing. C. staffing.",
    "B": "exporting. D. designating. 32. Looking at problems from various points of view helps a small-business owner develop A. practical arguments.",
    "C": "unnecessary conflicts. B. creative solutions.",
    "D": "unpredictable results.",
    "answer": "A: outsourcing. C. staffing.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Finemart's bookkeeper journalizes the business's income and expenditures at the time they occur even if no money changes hands at that time. Finemart uses the __________ accounting method to record transactions.",
    "A": "cash C. managerial",
    "B": "accrual D. tax 34. Which of the following is a source of cash that businesses include in a cash fl ow statement: A. Payables",
    "C": "Loans B. Expenses",
    "D": "Assets",
    "answer": "B: accrual D. tax 34. Which of the following is a source of cash that businesses include in a cash fl ow statement: A. Payables",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are listed as long-term assets on a balance sheet:?",
    "A": "Land, cash, and mortgage C. Vehicles, insurance, and accounts payable",
    "B": "Buildings, vehicles, and capital equi pment D. Capital equipment, mortgage, and inventory 36. If you want to analyze your business's income statement, what basic calculation should you use? A. Expenses minus income",
    "C": "Profit minus income B. Income minus expenses",
    "D": "Income minus profit",
    "answer": "B: Buildings, vehicles, and capital equi pment D. Capital equipment, mortgage, and inventory 36. If you want to analyze your business's income statement, what basic calculation should you use? A. Expenses minus income",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a business obtaining funds through equity financing:?",
    "A": "Borrowing money from friends C. Selling stock to investors",
    "B": "Obtaining credit from vendors D. Negotiating loans with banks 38. An established company has achieved a steady, positive cash flow. Which of the following types of funding is it most likely to rely on for unexpected expenses: A. Collateral",
    "C": "Venture capital B. A business line of credit",
    "D": "The company's capital structure",
    "answer": "C: Venture capital B. A business line of credit",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a business gains ground on its competitors, which of the following benefits is it experiencing:",
    "A": "Increased expenses C. Increased market share",
    "B": "Increased profits D. Increased productivity 40. Which of the following is an example of a variable expense: A. Equipment leases",
    "C": "Packaging/Shipping costs B. Rent/Mortgage",
    "D": "Salaries",
    "answer": "C: Packaging/Shipping costs B. Rent/Mortgage",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following financial analysis methods is used to show the relationship of each component to the total within a single financial statement:?",
    "A": "Vertical analysis C. Industry analysis",
    "B": "Horizontal analysis D. Fundamental analysis 42. Which of the following is an example of an employee-assistance program: A. Compensation B. Career and education planning",
    "C": "Training on the use of dangerous power equipment",
    "D": "Corrective action",
    "answer": "A: Vertical analysis C. Industry analysis",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before selecting new employees, employers should take time to determine",
    "A": "retirement plans. C. job specifications.",
    "B": "advancement options. D. physical characteristics. 44. Why is it important to provide an overview of an initial training session with staff members before training begins? A. It gives staff members the opportunity to study before training begins. B. It lets staff members know what to expect during the training.",
    "C": "It enables staff members to succeed in the training sessions.",
    "D": "It helps staff members decide if they need the training.",
    "answer": "C: It enables staff members to succeed in the training sessions.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The last step in handling employee grievances should be to __________ the problem.",
    "A": "identify C. follow up",
    "B": "analyze D. consider 46. Which of the following guidelines would be the most appropriate for a supervisor to follow when administering remedial action: A. Take action in the presence of the employee's coworkers. B. Resume a normal attitude toward the employee as quickly as possible.",
    "C": "Let personnel handle minor problems with employees.",
    "D": "Delay taking action so that the connection between the infraction and the penalty becomes",
    "answer": "C: Let personnel handle minor problems with employees.",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a requirement for good decision-making:?",
    "A": "A college degree C. At least three options",
    "B": "Data D. Money Test 1230 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 5 48. Which of the following best describes the type of company that benefits most from marketing research: A. Large corporations with plans to change marketing strategies B. Any business wanting to improve its decision-making abilitie s",
    "C": "Small businesses who wish to expand their operations",
    "D": "Nonprofit organizations interested in their competition",
    "answer": "B: Data D. Money Test 1230 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 5 48. Which of the following best describes the type of company that benefits most from marketing research: A. Large corporations with plans to change marketing strategies B. Any business wanting to improve its decision-making abilitie s",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of communicating with customers:?",
    "A": "Sponsoring a charity event C. Choosing a store to distri bute products",
    "B": "Creating a new product D. Developing a marketing plan 50. Marketers plan where they need to go and how to get there efficiently in order to A. lay out their strategies.",
    "C": "measure their success. B. achieve satisfying connections.",
    "D": "agree upon a goal.",
    "answer": "A: Sponsoring a charity event C. Choosing a store to distri bute products",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "General Motors' attempt to meet the needs of specific groups of consumers by offering trucks, large cars, and compact cars is an example of __________ segmentation.",
    "A": "demographic C. geographic",
    "B": "educational D. market 52. What is the relationship between shareholders and the board of directors? A. The board of directors represents the sharehol ders. B. The shareholders pay dividends to the board of directors.",
    "C": "The shareholders make decisions for the board of directors.",
    "D": "The board of directors holds the shareholders accountable.",
    "answer": "D: The board of directors holds the shareholders accountable.",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason it is important for a business to develop a marketing plan is that the plan",
    "A": "increases the business's financial security in an unpredictable environment.",
    "B": "reduces the need to implement corrective action or contingency plans.",
    "C": "provides guidelines for personnel to meet the company's objectives.",
    "D": "allows the business to focus on short-term goals instead of long-term goals.",
    "answer": "C: provides guidelines for personnel to meet the company's objectives.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When translating performance measures for marketing activities into financ ial outcomes, which outcome usually is of most importance to management?",
    "A": "Tax level C. Net profit",
    "B": "Interest rate D. Unit price 55. What are important considerations in establishing hardware/software specifications for a business? A. User needs, m obility, delivery terms, and technical support B. Capabilities, compatibility, reliability, and cost",
    "C": "Security, social media policies, performance, and licensing",
    "D": "Strategic planning, training, upgrades, and cost",
    "answer": "C: Security, social media policies, performance, and licensing",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Reiki is searching the company 's extensive database for sales records of certain products to determine where, when, and how they were purchased. She hopes to find patterns that could help determine ways to increase sales. Reiki is currently using",
    "A": "sales strategy. C. data mining.",
    "B": "data cleansing. D. sales techniques. 57. What is the best way for David to protect his small company's business records from natural disasters such as fires and floods? A. Store copies of the records in another facility or site B. Keep the records in unlocked file cabinets in the facility's warehouse",
    "C": "Delegate an employee to ensure that the records are continually updated",
    "D": "Purchase insurance from a reputable source",
    "answer": "C: Delegate an employee to ensure that the records are continually updated",
    "topic": "Risk management & insurance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ashley owns a small hardware shop. Every month, she reviews her inventory lists to see which products are popular and which are not. Using this information, Ashley is able to order the appropriate amount of each product for her store. This is an example of the importance of",
    "A": "ignoring inventory when ordering. C. stocking a div erse array of products.",
    "B": "over-purchasing certain products. D. monitoring internal records. 59. When a business has too much inventory on hand for an extended period of time, what type of business cost increases? A. Holding",
    "C": "Production B. Mainten ance",
    "D": "Stockout",
    "answer": "D: Stockout",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Using a locked mailbox, implementing a \"last person out\" policy, and numbering building keys are all examples of policies and procedures designed to",
    "A": "determine which employees can and can't be trusted.",
    "B": "prevent employees from stealing from the workplace.",
    "C": "foster a positive workplace culture for employees.",
    "D": "maintain the physical security of a workplace.",
    "answer": "D: maintain the physical security of a workplace.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Molly purchases raw materials for a factory that changes the shape or appearance of those materials through a process known as",
    "A": "transformation. C. specification.",
    "B": "affirmation. D. negotiation. 62. Calculate the percentage of deliveries made on time if a business placed 160 orders within a six-month period, and 144 of the orders arrived within the desired time frame. A. 85%",
    "C": "75% B. 90%",
    "D": "80%",
    "answer": "A: transformation. C. specification.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When is it more economical for a business to lease rather than to buy a facility?",
    "A": "When mortgage money is plentiful C. When credit standing is high",
    "B": "When interest rates are low D. When available cash is limited 64. If a company's sales decrease steadily over time, it might decide to control spending by A. increasing stock.",
    "C": "monitoring investments. B. reducing payroll.",
    "D": "adjusting interest rates.",
    "answer": "D: adjusting interest rates.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To effectively manage a supply chain, companies should",
    "A": "ignore underperforming suppliers and distributors.",
    "B": "monitor the performance of all supply chain partners.",
    "C": "introduce frequent changes to the production process.",
    "D": "launch new products through multiple suppliers.",
    "answer": "B: monitor the performance of all supply chain partners.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Claire doing when she reviews a report that compares the purchase transactions of the company's four largest customers?",
    "A": "Conducting a sales analysis C. Organizing an inventory report",
    "B": "Preparing a purchasing forecast D. Analyzing servi ce performance 67. Every __________ is the result of a process. A. project",
    "C": "input B. activity",
    "D": "outcome",
    "answer": "A: Conducting a sales analysis C. Organizing an inventory report",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An Internet and cable provider is considering whether to implement a new process that would require its customer service agents to work the phone lines for 24 hours a day instead of the previous 12 hours a day. What type of factor will most likely impact the design of this new process?",
    "A": "Human C. Technological",
    "B": "Regulatory D. Environmental Test 1230 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 7 69. Improved performance, reduced costs, increased profitability, and competitive advantage are most likely to be reasons why a business may choose to engage in A. community outreach.",
    "C": "human resources management. B. anti-harassment training.",
    "D": "business process change.",
    "answer": "A: Human C. Technological",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fostering effic iency in the production process is a goal of",
    "A": "managerial accounting. C. human resources management.",
    "B": "supply chain management. D. information technology. 71. Which of the following statements regarding the relationship between a business and its s upply chain is true: A. A business's supply chain has very little impact on the business's overall success. B. If a business's supply chain is poorly managed, customer satisfaction is likely to suffer.",
    "C": "Effective supply chain management results in lower customer satisfaction.",
    "D": "Supply chains with organizational problems tend to boost members' overall success.",
    "answer": "B: supply chain management. D. information technology. 71. Which of the following statements regarding the relationship between a business and its s upply chain is true: A. A business's supply chain has very little impact on the business's overall success. B. If a business's supply chain is poorly managed, customer satisfaction is likely to suffer.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After Courtney finds the man's order, she lets him know it will arrive later that afternoon. He seems to be pleased, so Courtney knows she did the right thing. Which step of problem solving does this situation illustrate?",
    "A": "Determine possible solutions C. Define the problem",
    "B": "Evaluate the solution D. State and check assumptions 73. In a business, who is responsible for determining how much money a CEO should make? A. The vice president",
    "C": "All of the employees B. The previous CEO",
    "D": "The board of directors",
    "answer": "B: Evaluate the solution D. State and check assumptions 73. In a business, who is responsible for determining how much money a CEO should make? A. The vice president",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a business usually better able to do when it selects a certain target market?",
    "A": "Eliminate ethical dilemmas",
    "B": "Control expenses and increase profits",
    "C": "Focus marketing decisions on a specific group of people",
    "D": "Change the variable-cost margin to quickly achieve break-even point",
    "answer": "C: Focus marketing decisions on a specific group of people",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following factors differentiates the governance structure of a small business from a large business:?",
    "A": "The number of owners C. The impact of governance policies",
    "B": "The need for a board of directors D. The presence of investors 76. Which of the following statements regarding corporate governance is true: A. All companies need a board of directors to perform corporate governance. B. Small organizations do not need corporate governance.",
    "C": "Corporate governance can benefit organizations of any size.",
    "D": "Large companies are better at monit oring corporate governance.",
    "answer": "A: The number of owners C. The impact of governance policies",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "TRISM Co. sets an organizational goal to gain 100 new clients. To do so, each sales rep must contact five prospects per week. This is an example of",
    "A": "designing an organizational structure. C. establishing performance st andards.",
    "B": "aligning personal goals with company goals. D. generating new product ideas. 78. Which of the following markets is characterized by a large number of buyers and sellers, none of whom has a significant influence on price: A. Monopoly",
    "C": "Pure competition B. Oligopoly",
    "D": "Monopolistic competition",
    "answer": "C: Pure competition B. Oligopoly",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During periods when employment is high and the nation's outlook is optimistic, selling prices of products tend to increase. This is an example of selling prices affected by",
    "A": "supply and demand. C. competition.",
    "B": "economic conditions. D. government regulation. Test 1230 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 8 80. What do businesses usually consider during the process of determining the initial feasibility of a new product idea? A. Need for the product",
    "C": "Complexity of the product B. Value of promotion",
    "D": "Type of packaging",
    "answer": "B: economic conditions. D. government regulation. Test 1230 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM 8 80. What do businesses usually consider during the process of determining the initial feasibility of a new product idea? A. Need for the product",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a product line:?",
    "A": "A double cheeseburger C. An automobile tire",
    "B": "Notebooks, scratch pads, and stationery D. Candy, games, and shampoo 82. Marketing a lower priced version of an item in a product line under a different brand name than the higher priced version enables the business to A. contract the product mix. B. avoid damage to brand reputation and image.",
    "C": "confuse buyers resulting in negative net gain.",
    "D": "offset expenses of adding a new product line.",
    "answer": "B: Notebooks, scratch pads, and stationery D. Candy, games, and shampoo 82. Marketing a lower priced version of an item in a product line under a different brand name than the higher priced version enables the business to A. contract the product mix. B. avoid damage to brand reputation and image.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business should consider eliminating a specific customer service when the service",
    "A": "is being used by a majority of the business's customers.",
    "B": "becomes essential to completing the sale of some items.",
    "C": "is making a larger profit than ever before.",
    "D": "becomes too expensive, or no longer serves the intended purpose.",
    "answer": "D: becomes too expensive, or no longer serves the intended purpose.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Internal factors that affect a company's promotional decisions include the",
    "A": "product, technology, and market. C. product, its price, an d distribution.",
    "B": "environment and market demand. D. economy, distribution, and price. 85. Under which of the following circumstances is the response to direct email likely to be the highest: A. The postal mail service delivers the ad on time. B. The delivered ad is strictly informational in nature.",
    "C": "Recipients have given the advertiser permission to send the ad.",
    "D": "The advertiser sends out an unsolicited ad to thousands of recipients.",
    "answer": "C: Recipients have given the advertiser permission to send the ad.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a benefit to businesses of positive word-of-mouth communication?",
    "A": "Decreased operating expense C. Increased product mix",
    "B": "Decreased advertising costs D. Increased sales 87. What is an example of a company using a direct marketing channel? A. Creating an ad that is promoted on social media B. Hiring a research company to conduct marketing surveys",
    "C": "Advertising products in a popular magazine",
    "D": "Responding to customer ideas and requests via email",
    "answer": "D: Responding to customer ideas and requests via email",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a type of sales promotion that provides customers with immediate rewards:?",
    "A": "Product displays C. Loyalty programs",
    "B": "Mail-in rebates D. Price-off deals 89. Which of the following is a public relations activity that involves dealing with government officials: A. Advising",
    "C": "Counseling B. Lobbying",
    "D": "Writing",
    "answer": "D: Writing",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a process that weeds out defective products after they've been created:?",
    "A": "Quality control C. Quality improvement",
    "B": "Quality assurance D. Quality command 91. Risk should be managed A. through the purchase of insurance.",
    "C": "after an incident has occurred. B. on a case-by-case basis.",
    "D": "as a part of business strategy.",
    "answer": "A: Quality control C. Quality improvement",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Stimulating demand for goods is one of the responsibilities of which of the following marketing functions:",
    "A": "Selling C. Distribution",
    "B": "Financing D. Risk management 94. Which part of the business plan describes a company's pricing policies? A. Situational analysis",
    "C": "Marketing plan B. Financial plan",
    "D": "Segment analysis",
    "answer": "A: Selling C. Distribution",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The objectives that managers develop for a business to attain are also intended to serve as operating",
    "A": "requirements. C. regulations.",
    "B": "standards. D. guidelines. 96. Which of the following is a promotion-related question that a business m ight ask in order to adjust its marketing mix in response to environmental changes: A. Which channels of distribution will we use?",
    "C": "Is our product aimed at a specific market? B. To whom should we offer discounts?",
    "D": "What laws affect our advertising?",
    "answer": "D: What laws affect our advertising?",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business had a net profit of $76,000 last year on sales of $680,000 and this year had a net profit of $84,000 on sales of $700,000. What is the percent of increase in net profit?",
    "A": "1.5% C. 1%",
    "B": ".5% D. 2% 98. Key performance indicators used to assess business performance should align with the business's A. corporate culture.",
    "C": "goals and objectives. B. operating expenses.",
    "D": "payroll and benefits.",
    "answer": "C: goals and objectives. B. operating expenses.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tyrone, a new employee, had to attend daily training sessions for his first two weeks on the job. He learned a lot about the company and his new role, but he didn't retain much of it over time. This example demonstrates that",
    "A": "training sessions are useless for most employees.",
    "B": "knowledge is fleeting and hard to hold onto.",
    "C": "learning and knowledge are the same thing.",
    "D": "learning doesn't always lead to knowledge.",
    "answer": "D: learning doesn't always lead to knowledge.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Change management strategies often fail because",
    "A": "they don't include everyone in the change process.",
    "B": "employees dedicate too much time to the change process.",
    "C": "competitors have implemented the changes already.",
    "D": "low-level employees are given too much responsibility.",
    "answer": "A: they don't include everyone in the change process.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can you attempt to cancel a contract without facing legal action?",
    "A": "Breach the contract and refuse to pay the other party.",
    "B": "Bring a lawsuit against the other party.",
    "C": "Send a request to the other party asking for cancellation.",
    "D": "Cancel the contract within a year of signing it.",
    "answer": "C: Send a request to the other party asking for cancellation.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following forms of business ownership must obtain a charter from the state(s) in which it operates:?",
    "A": "Corporation C. Partnership",
    "B": "Sole proprietorship D. Consolidation 4. Which of the following is a personal factor that affects the choice of a form of business ownership: A. Market considerations",
    "C": "Area of the country B. Business experience",
    "D": "Economic conditions",
    "answer": "A: Corporation C. Partnership",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a condition that must exist for channels to be effective:?",
    "A": "Channel members must have varying goals. C. They must be properly managed.",
    "B": "They must have at least five members. D. Channel members must not share tasks. 6. Indirect channels of distribution are the only channels that involve A. industrial users.",
    "C": "producers. B. intermediaries.",
    "D": "ultimate consumers.",
    "answer": "C: producers. B. intermediaries.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Barker Company is determining which channel of distribution to use by considering the number of potential customers in various geographic regions. The company is focusing on",
    "A": "employees ' capabilities. C. product benefits.",
    "B": "branding issues. D. market factors. 8. What is one of the reasons why a supervisor might prepare a formal business report? A. To compile sales expenses",
    "C": "To analyze marketing trends B. To request pricing information",
    "D": "To schedule training sessions",
    "answer": "D: To schedule training sessions",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a customer sees a news story on TV about a certain company or brand, it's an example of a(n)?",
    "A": "brand promise. C. advertisement.",
    "B": "touchpoint. D. slogan. 10. One of the benefits of competition t o consumers is that competition encourages A. businesses to limit their product lines.",
    "C": "government to fix prices. B. businesses to develop new products.",
    "D": "government to finance business activity.",
    "answer": "B: touchpoint. D. slogan. 10. One of the benefits of competition t o consumers is that competition encourages A. businesses to limit their product lines.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following was one of government's or iginal roles in business:?",
    "A": "Acting as a referee C. Ensuring a business's profitability",
    "B": "Regulating technology D. Protecting the environment 12. Which of the following economic concepts influences the cost of the production process: A. Balance of payments",
    "C": "Distribution of income B. Economies of scale",
    "D": "Inelasticity of demand",
    "answer": "A: Acting as a referee C. Ensuring a business's profitability",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Changing parts of a game that is marketed in other countries so the game conforms to local customs and preferences is an example of",
    "A": "customization. C. globalization.",
    "B": "cultural sensitivity. D. nationalization. Test 1249 ENTRE PRENEURSHIP EXAM 2 14. In persuasion, what technique should you follow to be ready to answer questions and give proof? A. Attract attention.",
    "C": "Make it personal. B. Be reasonable.",
    "D": "Do your homework.",
    "answer": "B: cultural sensitivity. D. nationalization. Test 1249 ENTRE PRENEURSHIP EXAM 2 14. In persuasion, what technique should you follow to be ready to answer questions and give proof? A. Attract attention.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does a goal differ from a vision?",
    "A": "A goal is broad and far-reaching.",
    "B": "A goal is concrete and measurable.",
    "C": "A goal is abstract and indefinite.",
    "D": "There is no difference-the two are the same.",
    "answer": "B: A goal is concrete and measurable.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If an employee is content with the way things are currently done at work, they are more likely to __________ workplace changes.",
    "A": "understand C. accept",
    "B": "look forward to D. resist 17. Tory is a new business owner offering data management services for medical records to hospitals. How can she i dentify what hospital administrators will expect from her service? A. Entertain hospital administrators at a sporting event B. Read about trends impacting the hospital industry",
    "C": "Read patient reviews about each hospital",
    "D": "Research each hospital's financial information",
    "answer": "D: Research each hospital's financial information",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gianna is attempting to build a strategic relationship with Nico, who is an influential member of the local business community. What is one technique Gianna could use to build the relationship?",
    "A": "Establishing dominance and control C. Seeking a deal as quickly as possible",
    "B": "Finding a shared vision D. Focusing on Nico's shortcomings 19. Which of the following businesses best represents an innovative entrepreneurial endeavor: A. Starting a clothing business online B. Buying a small local coffee shop from its founder",
    "C": "Opening a new pizza franchise",
    "D": "Developing and selling a new wood-cutting device",
    "answer": "B: Finding a shared vision D. Focusing on Nico's shortcomings 19. Which of the following businesses best represents an innovative entrepreneurial endeavor: A. Starting a clothing business online B. Buying a small local coffee shop from its founder",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Arielle knows that she would be a good entrepreneur because she",
    "A": "can withstand ups and downs. C. is easily interested by many different ideas.",
    "B": "likes to see immediate results of her work. D. depends on others to get work done. 21. Which of the following statements regarding international trade is true: A. Businesses shipping internati onally must use freight forwarding services. B. Only large companies typically benefit from conducting international trade.",
    "C": "Online businesses can easily become involved in international trade.",
    "D": "Foreign language skills are required to conduct international trade.",
    "answer": "A: can withstand ups and downs. C. is easily interested by many different ideas.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Entrepreneurial discovery is an important process in a free enterprise economic system because an entrepreneur or small-business owner can",
    "A": "change legal requirements. C. improve economic sanctions.",
    "B": "form a technological monopoly. D. satisfy an unmet demand. 23. When generating product ideas as a group, who typically guides the discussion? A. Innovator",
    "C": "Mentor B. Negotiator",
    "D": "Facilitator",
    "answer": "D: Facilitator",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The financial section of a feasibility study must include sources of",
    "A": "funding. C. staffing.",
    "B": "materials. D. technology. Test 1249 ENTRE PRENEURSHIP EXAM 3 25. What financial tool do entrepreneurs use to plan, monitor, and manage their ventures' income and expenses? A. Inbound-call report",
    "C": "Environmental scan B. Request for proposal",
    "D": "Operating bud get",
    "answer": "A: funding. C. staffing.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An entrepreneur is most likely to discuss the concept for a new business with an industry expert when the entrepreneur",
    "A": "lacks knowledge or experience in the field.",
    "B": "needs to obtain a commercial bank loan.",
    "C": "wants to increase the business 's profit margins.",
    "D": "is ready to plan promotional activities.",
    "answer": "A: lacks knowledge or experience in the field.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Karla is obtaining a short-term simple interest loan to start her home-based business. If she borrows $3,000 at a 4.25% interest rate and pays the loan back two years after obtaining the loan, how much interest will Karla pay?",
    "A": "$255 C. $3,255",
    "B": "$127.50 D. $3,127.50 28. Which of the following is a sign that a company may need to hire more employees: A. Company revenue is below target. B. Employees are underworked.",
    "C": "The compan y is often unable to meet its deadlines.",
    "D": "Employees are happy with working conditions.",
    "answer": "A: $255 C. $3,255",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Al is thinking about moving his company's headquarters to another city, which would be expensive but would bring the company closer to the raw materials needed for manufacturing. The benefit of moving is",
    "A": "feasibility. C. proximity.",
    "B": "demand. D. independence. 30. Small-business owners develop and use operating procedures so that everyday tasks are performed in a(n) __________ way. A. diverse",
    "C": "standard B. imprecise",
    "D": "innovative",
    "answer": "C: standard B. imprecise",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which factor tends to reduce employee productivity and has a negative effect on the success of a new business?",
    "A": "Poor communication C. Clear quality standards",
    "B": "Narrow product lines D. Short-term goals 32. To stay competitive, business owners must adapt to changes in the business environment by monitoring external factors such as A. profit margins.",
    "C": "product development. B. economic conditions.",
    "D": "staffing needs.",
    "answer": "A: Poor communication C. Clear quality standards",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The profit a business earns can be determined from the business's",
    "A": "income statement. C. budget.",
    "B": "balance sheet. D. assets. 34. Calculate a business's cash receipts if it has $12,450 in sales, earns $78 in interest, collects $625 in sales tax, and owns $5,700 worth of equipment. A. $13,153",
    "C": "$18,853 B. $12,528",
    "D": "$17,150",
    "answer": "A: income statement. C. budget.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a current asset:?",
    "A": "Checking account C. Machinery",
    "B": "Building D. Land Test 1249 ENTRE PRENEURSHIP EXAM 4 36. Which of the following is an example of business process thinking: A. A company strives to fix its method of internal communications. B. The marketing department and finance department avoid interacting.",
    "C": "Whenever a customer complains about slow service, servers are fired.",
    "D": "A company prioritizes product promotions over product development.",
    "answer": "A: Checking account C. Machinery",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following types of credit might business owners obtain to purchase seasonal goods for resale:?",
    "A": "Mortgage debts C. Stocks and bonds",
    "B": "Short-term loans D. Accounts rec eivable 38. Which of the following is a benefit of debt financing when starting a business: A. You have control over how the money is spent. B. You don't need to pay interest on the money.",
    "C": "You have help from knowledgeable, experienced investors.",
    "D": "You don't have to pay back the money if the business fails.",
    "answer": "B: Short-term loans D. Accounts rec eivable 38. Which of the following is a benefit of debt financing when starting a business: A. You have control over how the money is spent. B. You don't need to pay interest on the money.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When businesses divide the change in total revenue by the marginal product, they are calculating the?",
    "A": "marginal revenue. C. earned income.",
    "B": "break-even point. D. cash-flow level. 40. Which of the following is an advantage of the jury of executive opinion method of sales forecasting: A. It is based on the opinion of outside experts. B. All opinions expressed carry equal weight.",
    "C": "It is a quick and easy method to use.",
    "D": "All opinions gathered are from sales executives.",
    "answer": "A: marginal revenue. C. earned income.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following financial analysis methods involves comparing the same items on a company's financial statements for two or more periods:?",
    "A": "Fundamental analysis C. Technical analysis",
    "B": "Vertical analysis D. Horizontal analysis 42. Which of the following is an onboarding activity: A. Grievances",
    "C": "Orientation B. Compliance",
    "D": "Exit interviews",
    "answer": "D: Exit interviews",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Job applications provide human resources personnel with information about an applicant's training, skills, education, and",
    "A": "intelligence levels. C. hobbies and interests.",
    "B": "employment history. D. insurability levels. 44. Which of the following is the primary stakeholder influencing corporate governance: A. Organizational em ployees",
    "C": "The board of directors B. Company shareholders",
    "D": "High-level company executives",
    "answer": "B: employment history. D. insurability levels. 44. Which of the following is the primary stakeholder influencing corporate governance: A. Organizational em ployees",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the main purpose of encouraging feedback during an employee training session?",
    "A": "To ensure employees understand the material",
    "B": "To identify employ ees with leadership skills",
    "C": "So employees can evaluate the training session",
    "D": "So employees can build better relationships",
    "answer": "A: To ensure employees understand the material",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What approach to managing people is intended to discourage further violations of company rules after infractions have alrea dy occurred?",
    "A": "Corrective C. Preventive",
    "B": "Termination-at-will D. Open-door management Test 1249 ENTRE PRENEURSHIP EXAM 5 47. Which of the following is a way that marketers can use data to follow up on any problems or issues with a product: A. Providing salespeople with additional tra ining B. Determining what new products to offer",
    "C": "Deciding which wholesalers to use for distribution",
    "D": "Budgeting for product development",
    "answer": "A: Corrective C. Preventive",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Marketing research can affect the business's marketing mix by providing information about various locations that will influence the business's __________ decision.",
    "A": "price C. place",
    "B": "promotion D. product 49. Identify the marketing function in the following situation: While shopping at the mall, Susan is asked her opinion of different brands of shampoo. A. Behavioral segmentation",
    "C": "Marketing-information management B. Promotion",
    "D": "Specialty advertising",
    "answer": "C: Marketing-information management B. Promotion",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following actions is most appropriate for a business to take when competitors introduce similar products to the marketplace:?",
    "A": "Increase its prices to improve its image C. Reduce its advertising efforts",
    "B": "Adjust its marketing strategies D. Focus on its working conditions 51. An overall purpose of market segmentation is to divide the market A. into well-defined groups of consumers.",
    "C": "into consumer or industrial markets. B. by distance from store or producer.",
    "D": "by consumer or industry income.",
    "answer": "B: Adjust its marketing strategies D. Focus on its working conditions 51. An overall purpose of market segmentation is to divide the market A. into well-defined groups of consumers.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following situations is an example of a business using niche marketing:?",
    "A": "A soft drink manufacturer advertises its product during a national television broadcast.",
    "B": "A national petroleum company offers credit cards for use at its gas and service stations.",
    "C": "A chemical manufacturer offers a hand soap that contains an antibacterial agent.",
    "D": "An athletic footwear company produces a line of shoes for children who play soccer.",
    "answer": "D: An athletic footwear company produces a line of shoes for children who play soccer.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason why it is important to accurately forecast sales for a marketing plan is because the forecast is the basis of other",
    "A": "pricing strategies. C. business reports.",
    "B": "operational activi ties. D. management techniques. 54. A controversial way for an organization to collect data on consumer purchasing habits and use the data to assess advertising objectives is by using A. detailed consumer questionnaires.",
    "C": "random phone surveys. B. online tracking methods.",
    "D": "indirect response techniques.",
    "answer": "B: operational activi ties. D. management techniques. 54. A controversial way for an organization to collect data on consumer purchasing habits and use the data to assess advertising objectives is by using A. detailed consumer questionnaires.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do businesses establish specifications for selecting hardware and software systems?",
    "A": "To obtain systems that perform required functions",
    "B": "To develop training programs for employees",
    "C": "To analyze the prices of various vendors",
    "D": "To keep up with the latest technological fads",
    "answer": "A: To obtain systems that perform required functions",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a primary purpose of data mining:?",
    "A": "To locate someone C. To spy on competitors",
    "B": "To identify patterns D. To attract customers 57. Which of the following is a reason why a small business might share its financial records: A. To convince a supplier to offer discounts on products purchased B. To persuade a customer of the business's excellent service",
    "C": "To show competitors why brand competition is useless",
    "D": "To prove the business's net worth to acquire a bank loan",
    "answer": "B: To identify patterns D. To attract customers 57. Which of the following is a reason why a small business might share its financial records: A. To convince a supplier to offer discounts on products purchased B. To persuade a customer of the business's excellent service",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of internal business record will help a firm determine the status of its supplies?",
    "A": "Credit report C. SWOT analysis",
    "B": "Income statement D. Inventor y report 59. Which of the following is an operations activity in business: A. Selecting media",
    "C": "Obtaining resources B. Contacting customers",
    "D": "Analyzing investments",
    "answer": "D: Analyzing investments",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Electrical hazards, slipping and tripping, and violence are all examples of potential __________ in the workplace.",
    "A": "non-negotiables C. safety issues",
    "B": "compromises D. success indicators 61. Why might a business decide to purchase goods for a price higher than the lowest possible price? A. To arrange flexible contracts",
    "C": "To satisfy a favorite vendor B. To spend additional funds",
    "D": "To obtain a needed delivery date",
    "answer": "C: To satisfy a favorite vendor B. To spend additional funds",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Three-way light bulbs are all made with the same size base. This is an example of a production process that uses __________ parts.",
    "A": "segmented C. branded",
    "B": "standardized D. graded 63. Businesses that develop and implement procedures for employees to follow to expedite task completion are trying to establish efficient A. production processes.",
    "C": "management techniques. B. workflows.",
    "D": "supervision.",
    "answer": "B: standardized D. graded 63. Businesses that develop and implement procedures for employees to follow to expedite task completion are trying to establish efficient A. production processes.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Abbra-Kadabra Company examined its expenses for electricity for the past six months and found the average electric bill to be $2,300 per month, with a high of $2,375 and a low of $2,250 during that period. This type of expense would be classified as a __________ cost.",
    "A": "variable C. semi-variable",
    "B": "fixed D. nonoperating 65. A business's budget estimated $165,500 in sales each month for the next four months, with 55% of that amount each month being for expenses. If actual sales for the four-month period were $690,000 and expenses were 55% of the actual sales, by what amount did the business's income increase? A. $14,500",
    "C": "$12,600 B. $13,900",
    "D": "$15,100",
    "answer": "C: $12,600 B. $13,900",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the primary goals of supply chain management is to",
    "A": "minimize overall value to the customer.",
    "B": "gain a competitive advantage in the marketplace.",
    "C": "set prices for products that maximize profits.",
    "D": "control customer perceptions of a business.",
    "answer": "B: gain a competitive advantage in the marketplace.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Wellston Industries wants to compare a current business situation with a target situation. Which of the following tools will help Wellston obtain the information that it wants:",
    "A": "Mind map C. Decision tree",
    "B": "Gap analysis D. Critical path 68. Income from sales, cost of goods sold, gross profit on sales, operating expenses, and net profit or loss are all part of a(n) A. sales budget.",
    "C": "income statement. B. balance sheet.",
    "D": "marketing plan.",
    "answer": "B: Gap analysis D. Critical path 68. Income from sales, cost of goods sold, gross profit on sales, operating expenses, and net profit or loss are all part of a(n) A. sales budget.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A manufacturing company is required by the local government to dispose of its waste in an environmentally safe way. This is an exampl e of how process design can be affected by __________ factors.",
    "A": "natural C. technological",
    "B": "human D. regulatory 70. One of the main external factors that may cause a firm to change its business processes is A. high operating costs.",
    "C": "low employee morale. B. desire for growth.",
    "D": "competition.",
    "answer": "D: competition.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does supply chain management increase customer satisfaction?",
    "A": "Enhances data quality",
    "B": "Integrates information throughout an organization",
    "C": "Improves cash flow",
    "D": "Reduces the time it takes for goods to reach consumers",
    "answer": "D: Reduces the time it takes for goods to reach consumers",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following should a person do first when facing the need to make a decision:?",
    "A": "Evaluate information C. Analyze results",
    "B": "Make a choice D. Define the objective 73. What is a benefit of corporate governance? A. Improved access to capital",
    "C": "Ability to bypass sustainability efforts B. Increased distance from investors",
    "D": "Freedom from stakeholder interference",
    "answer": "D: Freedom from stakeholder interference",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Members of a board of directors are",
    "A": "not able to make deci sions. C. a business's vendors.",
    "B": "required to be stockholders. D. elected by stockholders. 75. Which of the following is an example of an external mechanism of corporate governance: A. A company's business objectives",
    "C": "Government regulations B. Board of directors' policies",
    "D": "A company's code of conduct",
    "answer": "D: A company's code of conduct",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Most employers require applicants to complete",
    "A": "reference checks. C. resumes.",
    "B": "letters of intent. D. application forms. 77. Performance standards should be A. informally discussed.",
    "C": "measurable. B. subjective.",
    "D": "extremely challenging.",
    "answer": "D: extremely challenging.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What pricing strategy would be most effective for a business that wants to create an image of excellent quality and prestige?",
    "A": "High C. Moderate",
    "B": "Wholesale D. Discount 79. The Salty Pretzel Company, which has been doing very well in the market, shifts its pricing objectives to maximize profits. Most likely, The Salty Pretzel Company is A. obtaining market share.",
    "C": "trying to improve cash flow. B. creating an exclusive image.",
    "D": "stabili zing prices.",
    "answer": "A: High C. Moderate",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an internal method that a company uses to facilitate ongoing product and market opportunity recognition:?",
    "A": "Customer interviews C. Vendor surveys",
    "B": "Task force meetings D. Association membership 81. Reliability, courtesy, and competence are primary factors that a company should consider when it develops strategies to A. evaluate its customers' experiences.",
    "C": "improve the competition's market share. B. personalize its mass advertising messages.",
    "D": "comply with local ordinances.",
    "answer": "B: Task force meetings D. Association membership 81. Reliability, courtesy, and competence are primary factors that a company should consider when it develops strategies to A. evaluate its customers' experiences.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a good reason why a business would remove a product from its product mix and replace it with another:?",
    "A": "The company wants to expand its product line.",
    "B": "The product has become a fast seller.",
    "C": "The company wants to increase its market share.",
    "D": "The product has become a collectible.",
    "answer": "C: The company wants to increase its market share.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why has enterprise risk management developed?",
    "A": "Declining quality standards C. Reduced government regulation",
    "B": "The elimination of certain insurance plans D. An incr easingly diverse array of risks 84. External factors that affect a company's promotional decisions include A. competition and technology.",
    "C": "distribution and technology. B. environment, product, and price.",
    "D": "product, social trends, and demand.",
    "answer": "D: product, social trends, and demand.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The advertising medium that can best reach a targeted customer with a specific message is",
    "A": "TV. C. magazines.",
    "B": "email. D. billboard ads. 86. Jamie is a loyal customer of Glamor Girl cosmetics. She purchases every new product the company releases, writes glowing reviews online, and tells her friends and family to try the brand's cosmetics. Jamie could be described as a A. potential customer.",
    "C": "brand evangelist. B. late adopter.",
    "D": "discount customer.",
    "answer": "B: email. D. billboard ads. 86. Jamie is a loyal customer of Glamor Girl cosmetics. She purchases every new product the company releases, writes glowing reviews online, and tells her friends and family to try the brand's cosmetics. Jamie could be described as a A. potential customer.",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the most impor tant, fundamental keys to successful change management is",
    "A": "ensuring changes do not impact competitiveness.",
    "B": "focusing on processes over people.",
    "C": "minimizing use of resources.",
    "D": "involving everyone in the organization.",
    "answer": "D: involving everyone in the organization.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nelly recently purchase d a new toaster oven. The manufacturer of the toaster oven offered a special promotion where Nelly could receive $50 cash back if she mailed her proof of purchase to the company. This is known as a",
    "A": "coupon. C. rebate.",
    "B": "point-of-sale promotion. D. sweepstakes. 89. Why do some businesses sponsor local events? A. To generate revenue",
    "C": "To obtain publicity B. To create news",
    "D": "To sell products",
    "answer": "C: To obtain publicity B. To create news",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a task involved in quality assurance:?",
    "A": "Repairing defective goods to mai ntain quality",
    "B": "Inspecting products to ensure quality",
    "C": "Making changes for better quality",
    "D": "Training employees to strive for quality",
    "answer": "D: Training employees to strive for quality",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding the relationship between risk and business objectives:?",
    "A": "The more objectives a business has, the less risk it faces.",
    "B": "Objectives should never be modified because of risk.",
    "C": "Effective business objectives are not risky.",
    "D": "Risks help businesses determine objectives.",
    "answer": "D: Risks help businesses determine objectives.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following minimizes t he costs associated with maintaining a product mix:?",
    "A": "High breadth C. Economy image",
    "B": "Shallow depth D. Premium value Test 1249 ENTRE PRENEURSHIP EXAM 9 93. All goods or services sold to customers should A. be of the finest quality.",
    "C": "have many possible uses. B. be needed by the cust omers.",
    "D": "have the lowest possible price.",
    "answer": "B: Shallow depth D. Premium value Test 1249 ENTRE PRENEURSHIP EXAM 9 93. All goods or services sold to customers should A. be of the finest quality.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following parts of a business plan includes the history of the business:?",
    "A": "Strategy and implementation C. Company description",
    "B": "Market analysis D. Executive summary 95. The ski shop manager set an objective to increase sales by 10% over the previous year even though the forecast was for a mild and rainy winter. The manager's objective was A. unrealistic.",
    "C": "reasonable. B. practical.",
    "D": "scientific.",
    "answer": "C: reasonable. B. practical.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following identifies an upward economic trend:?",
    "A": "Businesses are using more computers.",
    "B": "Sales in the auto industry are increasing.",
    "C": "Businesses must meet stricter licensing requirements.",
    "D": "The number of firms accused of price fixing is increasing.",
    "answer": "B: Sales in the auto industry are increasing.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following technologies do many businesses use to monitor key performance indicators:?",
    "A": "Firewalls C. Extranets",
    "B": "Dashboards D. Terabytes 98. What company has the highest sales-to-receivables ratio based on the following information: Company A has sales of $250,000 and accounts receivable of $20,000; Company B has sales of $275,000 and accounts receivable of $25,000; Company C has sales of $300,000 and accounts receivable of $30,000; and Company D has sales of $290,000 and accounts receivable of $32,0 00. A. Company D",
    "C": "Company C B. Company B",
    "D": "Company A",
    "answer": "B: Dashboards D. Terabytes 98. What company has the highest sales-to-receivables ratio based on the following information: Company A has sales of $250,000 and accounts receivable of $20,000; Company B has sales of $275,000 and accounts receivable of $25,000; Company C has sales of $300,000 and accounts receivable of $30,000; and Company D has sales of $290,000 and accounts receivable of $32,0 00. A. Company D",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For successful innovation in the workplace, employees should have a desire to learn and be willing to",
    "A": "accept change. C. exhibit bias.",
    "B": "follow procedures. D. suppress ideas. 100. The advantage to a business that uses opt-in email to promote its products is that the business can A. customize offers.",
    "C": "predict trends. B. influence demographics.",
    "D": "control sales.",
    "answer": "A: accept change. C. exhibit bias.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "John would like to be a business owner, has money to invest, and wants to limit his liability. He does not have time to participate in the day-to-day operations of the business. What type of business ownership would you recommend?",
    "A": "Close corporation",
    "B": "Open corporation",
    "C": "Sole proprietorship",
    "D": "General partnership",
    "answer": "B: Open corporation",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why should partnerships develop a formal written agreement?",
    "A": "To meet the requirements of the law",
    "B": "To be able to sell stock",
    "C": "To prevent future problems",
    "D": "To pay less tax",
    "answer": "C: To prevent future problems",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Torts relating to misrepresented facts about a business's goods or services may be subject to a lawsuit on the basis of",
    "A": "intrusion.",
    "B": "assault.",
    "C": "defamation.",
    "D": "fraud.",
    "answer": "D: fraud.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Channel members add value to a product by",
    "A": "performing certain channel activities expertly.",
    "B": "making the product more costly.",
    "C": "making the product difficult for consumers to find.",
    "D": "pursuing individual goals.",
    "answer": "A: performing certain channel activities expertly.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an industrial user:?",
    "A": "A family buying weekly groceries",
    "B": "A construction company buying wood",
    "C": "A college student buying school supplies",
    "D": "An individual purchasing toothpaste",
    "answer": "B: A construction company buying wood",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A manufacturer of dishwashing soap has just invented a new type of soap that cleans better. The manufacturer should choose to distribute the soap through __________ distribution.",
    "A": "intensive",
    "B": "inclusive",
    "C": "selective",
    "D": "exclusive",
    "answer": "A: intensive",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an important aspect of fulfilling a company's brand promise?",
    "A": "To change the company's slogan on a regular basis",
    "B": "To use touchpoints to create positive customer experiences",
    "C": "To establish different policies for different types of customers",
    "D": "To develop different trade characters for different market segments",
    "answer": "B: To use touchpoints to create positive customer experiences",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Government protects consumers by establishing",
    "A": "requirements for product testing.",
    "B": "laws to monitor the growth of business.",
    "C": "a measure of effectiveness in government.",
    "D": "rules to generate competition.",
    "answer": "A: requirements for product testing.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In many places, trash pickup is legally controlled by just one company. This is known as",
    "A": "a regulated monopoly.",
    "B": "nonprice competition.",
    "C": "price competition.",
    "D": "price discrimination.",
    "answer": "A: a regulated monopoly.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To decrease its unit costs, Marti Mart has entered into long-term contracts with some of its vendors and has agreed to buy in bulk. This is an example of",
    "A": "marginal cost.",
    "B": "a tying agreement.",
    "C": "economies of scale.",
    "D": "the law of diminishing returns.",
    "answer": "C: economies of scale.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Collette wants to fill out at least five job applications this week. What standard has she set for her success?",
    "A": "Outperforming others",
    "B": "Improvement",
    "C": "Past performance",
    "D": "An objective measure",
    "answer": "D: An objective measure",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Associations with color are a cultural sensitivity issue that is most important for",
    "A": "individuals.",
    "B": "travelers.",
    "C": "families.",
    "D": "businesses.",
    "answer": "D: businesses.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Internal and external controls, policies, and guidelines for reaching goals while meeting stakeholders' needs are all common elements of",
    "A": "legal regulations for businesses.",
    "B": "corporate governance structures.",
    "C": "nondisclosure agreements.",
    "D": "public relations strategies.",
    "answer": "B: corporate governance structures.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to share the best techniques for performing a job task with your coworkers?",
    "A": "It builds good working relationships.",
    "B": "Your coworkers will consider you an expert.",
    "C": "It will convince your boss to promote you.",
    "D": "It can reduce your work responsibilities.",
    "answer": "A: It builds good working relationships.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Zoey isn't sure which decision to make, so she decides to follow her intuition when responding to an ethical dilemma. Which step of the ethical dilemma r esponse process is Zoey taking part in?",
    "A": "Consider all your potential actions.",
    "B": "Check your gut feeling.",
    "C": "Figure out who's affected.",
    "D": "Get the facts.",
    "answer": "B: Check your gut feeling.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step in entrepreneurial discovery?",
    "A": "Analyzing the feasibility of an idea",
    "B": "Determining the risks and rewards",
    "C": "Identifying an unmet want or need",
    "D": "Screening the product ideas",
    "answer": "C: Identifying an unmet want or need",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following activities is most likely to help entrepreneurs recognize opportunities for new product and business ideas?",
    "A": "Disagreeing",
    "B": "Observing",
    "C": "Informing",
    "D": "Persuading",
    "answer": "B: Observing",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a technological trend that impacts new business ventures:?",
    "A": "Cloud computing applications",
    "B": "Private enterprise movement",
    "C": "Liberal trade agreements",
    "D": "Environmental awareness initiatives",
    "answer": "A: Cloud computing applications",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Olivia is assessing the risks associated with starting a new business. She is considering how her professional reputation will be affected if her new business is not successful. What type of risk is Olivia considering?",
    "A": "Legal",
    "B": "Market",
    "C": "Career",
    "D": "Economic",
    "answer": "C: Career",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The founder of a startup should think about hiring employees when they are",
    "A": "willing to hire the first person interviewed.",
    "B": "not sure what a new employee will do.",
    "C": "turning down work due to limited capacity.",
    "D": "stressed about the amount of work to do.",
    "answer": "C: turning down work due to limited capacity.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following questions would Allison ask herself when deciding if she should hire an assistant for her growing business:?",
    "A": "Does this applicant meet my minimal educational requirements?",
    "B": "Does the workload require a full-time or part-time employee?",
    "C": "How will I recruit applicants for the job?",
    "D": "Can I trust this person to get the work done on time?",
    "answer": "B: Does the workload require a full-time or part-time employee?",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a capital resource:?",
    "A": "Credit card",
    "B": "Granite",
    "C": "Conveyer belt",
    "D": "Pencils",
    "answer": "C: Conveyer belt",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A small-business owner is trying to decide whether to rent or buy office furniture. The monthly rental is $275 per person, and there are six people who will need furniture. The cost of buying the furniture is $6,500 per person. What would you advise the sm all-business owner to do?",
    "A": "Buy the furniture because rental costs will be less than the purchase price in 2.2 years.",
    "B": "Buy the furniture because rental costs will exceed the purchase price in 1.97 years.",
    "C": "Rent the furniture because rental costs are much less a year than the purchase price on an annual basis.",
    "D": "Rent the furniture because rental costs will be less than the purchase price for 3.4 years.",
    "answer": "B: Buy the furniture because rental costs will exceed the purchase price in 1.97 years.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for new businesses to use resources productively?",
    "A": "It builds brand loyalty.",
    "B": "It improves marketing efforts.",
    "C": "Investors expect immediate returns.",
    "D": "Resources are often limited.",
    "answer": "D: Resources are often limited.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of entrepreneurship:?",
    "A": "Raul invests his money in the stock market.",
    "B": "Penelope asks her boss for a pay raise.",
    "C": "Elissa starts a company when she develops a new app.",
    "D": "Wesley starts working for his mo ther's accounting firm.",
    "answer": "C: Elissa starts a company when she develops a new app.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ariana wants to promote her handcrafted jewelry in several different countries. Promoting her products in multiple countries is most likely to result in",
    "A": "fewer cultural barriers.",
    "B": "fewer compliance challenges.",
    "C": "reduced financial risk.",
    "D": "exposure to new markets.",
    "answer": "D: exposure to new markets.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Employees who are paid fairly for a job well done are more likely to",
    "A": "experience job dissatisfaction.",
    "B": "stay engaged in their jobs and their company.",
    "C": "feel resentment toward management.",
    "D": "leave the company for another job.",
    "answer": "B: stay engaged in their jobs and their company.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When trying to raise capital, an existing business that is owed a large amount of money as accounts receivable may turn them into cash by selling them to a(n)?",
    "A": "investor.",
    "B": "creditor.",
    "C": "factor.",
    "D": "friend.",
    "answer": "C: factor.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business may review its accounting information to learn",
    "A": "the size of its competitors' debts.",
    "B": "how its products are being shipped.",
    "C": "what industry trends to expect for next year.",
    "D": "what its sales revenues are.",
    "answer": "D: what its sales revenues are.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A liability is",
    "A": "an item that adds value to the business.",
    "B": "a claim a creditor has against a business's assets.",
    "C": "a sign that a business is in financial trouble.",
    "D": "the portion of the business that belongs to its owners.",
    "answer": "B: a claim a creditor has against a business's assets.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rebuilding the budget for each new budgeting peri od is a strategy known as __________ budgeting.",
    "A": "zero-based",
    "B": "long-term",
    "C": "fixed",
    "D": "incremental",
    "answer": "A: zero-based",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a component of a profit-and-loss statement:?",
    "A": "Interest rate",
    "B": "Petty cash",
    "C": "Book value",
    "D": "Gross margin",
    "answer": "D: Gross margin",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following methods of financial analysis displays all information as percentages and is particularly useful for comparing companies within their industries:?",
    "A": "Common-sized statements",
    "B": "Vertical analysis",
    "C": "Horizontal analysis",
    "D": "Trend analysis",
    "answer": "A: Common-sized statements",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit that a business may include in a cost-benefit analysis:?",
    "A": "Decreased market share",
    "B": "Increased expenses",
    "C": "Decreased efficiency",
    "D": "Increased productivity",
    "answer": "D: Increased productivity",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following financial statements contains the company's \"bottom line,\" which represents net profit:?",
    "A": "Income statement",
    "B": "Balance sheet",
    "C": "Statement of cash flows",
    "D": "Statement of changes in equity",
    "answer": "A: Income statement",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following can legally be asked on a job application:?",
    "A": "Military experience",
    "B": "Number of children",
    "C": "Date of birth",
    "D": "Height and weight",
    "answer": "A: Military experience",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about the effects of remedial action:?",
    "A": "Behavior that is rewarded rarely g ets repeated by employees.",
    "B": "Studies indicate that remedial action causes great psychological damage.",
    "C": "The results of punishing undesirable behavior are unpredictable.",
    "D": "Once remedial action is taken, employees do not commit rule violations.",
    "answer": "C: The results of punishing undesirable behavior are unpredictable.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As the manager of Gray's Sporting-Goods Store, Jay makes an effort to communicate company information to employees on a regular basis, treat all employees respectfully, rewa rd good performance, and encourage a team-oriented attitude. This is an example of a manager",
    "A": "encouraging a competitive mindset.",
    "B": "supporting groupthink behavior.",
    "C": "creating a positive work environment.",
    "D": "implementing consensus strategies.",
    "answer": "C: creating a positive work environment.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "True or false: All employees make an impact on a business.",
    "A": "True; all employees make either a positive or negative impact on a business.",
    "B": "False; only executives and board members make an impact on a business.",
    "C": "False; only managers and supervisors make an impact on a business.",
    "D": "True; all employees make a positive impact on a business.",
    "answer": "A: True; all employees make either a positive or negative impact on a business.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A shoe company wants to keep up with changing trends in the shoe industry, so it conducts marketing research. The company wants to be sure its marketing research is as effective as possible, so the researchers try to keep their own opinions and biases hidd en so that their research will be",
    "A": "subjective.",
    "B": "objective.",
    "C": "timely.",
    "D": "invalid.",
    "answer": "B: objective.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of data that marketers could gather from the company's sales team:?",
    "A": "What products competitors are currently offering",
    "B": "The prices of raw materials",
    "C": "How actual sales compare to sales goals",
    "D": "The latest market research studies",
    "answer": "C: How actual sales compare to sales goals",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of how sales promotion tactics can impact marketing goals:?",
    "A": "Samuel purchases a new car after viewing a commercial.",
    "B": "Fatima convinces customers that her software is superior to competitors.",
    "C": "A soft drink company hosts a press conference to discuss its new flavor.",
    "D": "Erica goes to a coffee shop every day in hopes of winning a contest.",
    "answer": "D: Erica goes to a coffee shop every day in hopes of winning a contest.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Busy parents have been identified as frequent consumers of energy drinks. This is an example of behavioral market segmentation based on",
    "A": "economic status.",
    "B": "loyalty response.",
    "C": "rate of use.",
    "D": "occasion response.",
    "answer": "C: rate of use.",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a potential strength that a manager might identify in a SWOT analysis?",
    "A": "Large inventories",
    "B": "Market leadership",
    "C": "New foreign markets",
    "D": "Market saturation",
    "answer": "B: Market leadership",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business has a 30% share of an $845,500 market. What should it forecast in sales for next year's marketing plan if it expects to obtain an additional 5% of the market?",
    "A": "$270,560",
    "B": "$295,925",
    "C": "$253,650",
    "D": "$236,740",
    "answer": "B: $295,925",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do advertisers develop customer profiles?",
    "A": "They can become more profitable by selling customer profiles to other companies.",
    "B": "They want to understand more about their customers' interests, activities, and concerns.",
    "C": "They can recognize each individual's information once they have gathered profile information.",
    "D": "They want to make record keeping more efficient by condensing customer information.",
    "answer": "B: They want to understand more about their customers' interests, activities, and concerns.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the first question that a new business owner should ask when determining the venture's technology needs:?",
    "A": "Where should I purchase my supplies?",
    "B": "What software programs will help the business operate efficiently?",
    "C": "How will I legally structure my new business's technology department?",
    "D": "Is it necessary to maintain computer hardware?",
    "answer": "B: What software programs will help the business operate efficiently?",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about the term \"environment\":?",
    "A": "It applies to individuals, not businesses.",
    "B": "It consists of your surroundings.",
    "C": "It has no affect on your performance.",
    "D": "It refers only to the earth and its resources.",
    "answer": "B: It consists of your surroundings.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following methods of data mining, often used in market segmentation, involves placing observable data into naturally occurring groups:?",
    "A": "Cluster analysis",
    "B": "Forecasting",
    "C": "Prediction",
    "D": "Market basket analysis",
    "answer": "A: Cluster analysis",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An effective fire-prevention program requires that the business's employees know the exact location of all",
    "A": "fire extinguishers.",
    "B": "hazardous materials.",
    "C": "electrical outlets.",
    "D": "emergency services.",
    "answer": "A: fire extinguishers.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Coral owns a gymnastic studio that teaches children and young adults to do gymnastics. Coral's business produces",
    "A": "retail goods.",
    "B": "industrial services.",
    "C": "tangible outputs.",
    "D": "intangible outputs.",
    "answer": "D: intangible outputs.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When creating a quality assurance program, it is important that a manager first?",
    "A": "puts together a quality committee.",
    "B": "implements corrective action.",
    "C": "creates standards.",
    "D": "trains staff.",
    "answer": "C: creates standards.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can a business sell more goods to increase profit quickly but do so without increasing expenses?",
    "A": "Set lower prices",
    "B": "Plan special events",
    "C": "Hire additional staff",
    "D": "Purchase extra stock",
    "answer": "A: Set lower prices",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following provides the most economical way for a new business to obtain office space if it has limited cash flow:?",
    "A": "Make a $50,000 down payment on a 30-year mortgage",
    "B": "Pay a $2,000 security deposit to lease a facility",
    "C": "Negotiate a 9.5% interest rate to purchase a building",
    "D": "Obtain a 10% discount by paying a year's rent in advance",
    "answer": "B: Pay a $2,000 security deposit to lease a facility",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business often compares its similar financial information from different time periods to",
    "A": "influence buying behavior.",
    "B": "detect trends.",
    "C": "evaluate competitors.",
    "D": "control markets.",
    "answer": "B: detect trends.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the only true source of income for every member of a supply chain:?",
    "A": "Investments and loans used to finance the supply chain",
    "B": "Raw materials used in manufacturing at the beginning of the supply chain",
    "C": "Profit generated from one supply chain member selling to another",
    "D": "Final customers who buy the supply chain's end product",
    "answer": "D: Final customers who buy the supply chain's end product",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does process thinking help organizations?",
    "A": "Assists them in separating work between departments",
    "B": "Enables them to find out who to blame for issues",
    "C": "Lets them know why they succeeded or failed",
    "D": "Helps them avoid documenting workflow",
    "answer": "C: Lets them know why they succeeded or failed",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Human, regulatory, technological, and environmental factors are most likely to influence the design of",
    "A": "employee leave policies.",
    "B": "project due dates.",
    "C": "office visitation guidelines.",
    "D": "business processes.",
    "answer": "D: business processes.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Improved performance, reduced costs, increased profitability, and competitive advantage are most likely to be reasons why a business may choose to engage in",
    "A": "business process change.",
    "B": "human resources management.",
    "C": "community outreach.",
    "D": "anti-harassment training.",
    "answer": "A: business process change.",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bernard's business is more successful than his competitors' because he is innovative, which gives him a",
    "A": "competitive advantage.",
    "B": "creative advantage.",
    "C": "creative destruction.",
    "D": "competitive destruction.",
    "answer": "A: competitive advantage.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately describes the relationship between ethics and corporate governance:?",
    "A": "Organizations that consistently behave ethically have no need for corporate governance.",
    "B": "Corporate governance seeks to maximize p rofits at the expense of transparency and being ethical.",
    "C": "Corporate governance seeks to minimize unethical behavior, reduce risk, and avoid mismanagement.",
    "D": "Companies with effective corporate governance generally make more unethical decisions.",
    "answer": "C: Corporate governance seeks to minimize unethical behavior, reduce risk, and avoid mismanagement.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the relationship between shareholders and the board of directors?",
    "A": "The board of directors holds the shareholders accountable.",
    "B": "The board of directors represents the shareholders.",
    "C": "The shareholders pay dividends to the board of directors.",
    "D": "The shareholders make decisions for the board of directors.",
    "answer": "B: The board of directors represents the shareholders.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When monitoring progress in achieving organizational goals, it's important to evaluate objectives that are?",
    "A": "vague.",
    "B": "implied.",
    "C": "flexible.",
    "D": "measurable.",
    "answer": "D: measurable.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true regarding stakeholder expectations:?",
    "A": "Stakeholder expectations are always financially driven.",
    "B": "All stakeholders want to exert authority over employees.",
    "C": "Stakeholder expectations always come second to customer needs.",
    "D": "Each group of stakeholders has different needs and expectations.",
    "answer": "D: Each group of stakeholders has different needs and expectations.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who typically has the greatest influence on a company's corporate governance?",
    "A": "Board of directors",
    "B": "Shareholders",
    "C": "HR director",
    "D": "Chief financial officer",
    "answer": "A: Board of directors",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a profit-oriented pricing objective:?",
    "A": "Increasing market share",
    "B": "Creating an image for the business",
    "C": "Becoming more competitive",
    "D": "Earning return on investment",
    "answer": "D: Earning return on investment",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A company decides to stop manufacturing one of its products because the necessary raw materials have become too difficult to find and purchase. The company is using a(n) __________ product-mix strategy.",
    "A": "expansion",
    "B": "trading-up",
    "C": "contractio n",
    "D": "alteration",
    "answer": "C: contractio n",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A restaurant allows customers to order via its website and pay via tablet computers at each table. The restaurant is using __________ to provide excellent customer service.",
    "A": "competition",
    "B": "cross-training",
    "C": "internal service",
    "D": "technology",
    "answer": "D: technology",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "\"We are the most affordable gym in town!\" This unique selling proposition relates to the",
    "A": "sales copy.",
    "B": "placement.",
    "C": "pricing strategy.",
    "D": "guarantee.",
    "answer": "C: pricing strategy.",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Putnam Incorporated expects its employees to respond to its customers' phone requests within 24 hours. This is an example of a",
    "A": "customer-defined service goal.",
    "B": "company-defined service standard.",
    "C": "company-defined technical audit.",
    "D": "customer-defined technical expectation.",
    "answer": "B: company-defined service standard.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business's promotion can present facts in a creative way, but it must remain",
    "A": "literal.",
    "B": "honest.",
    "C": "positive.",
    "D": "competitive.",
    "answer": "B: honest.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A benefit to a business of using cable television for promotions is that it provides",
    "A": "a select group of stations that reach special markets.",
    "B": "the most requested programs in any television market.",
    "C": "24-hour programming on a minimum of 40 stations.",
    "D": "unique access to major international events.",
    "answer": "A: a select group of stations that reach special markets.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an advantage of using the internet for direct marketing:?",
    "A": "It is a relatively affordable form of marketing.",
    "B": "It eliminates the need for other types of marketing.",
    "C": "It is less flexible than other forms of marketing.",
    "D": "It involves face-to-face contact with customers.",
    "answer": "A: It is a relatively affordable form of marketing.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A company released a video game that depicts the game's characters using a certain brand of equipment. What type of sales promotion is the business using?",
    "A": "Bonus packaging",
    "B": "Cooperative selling",
    "C": "Advergaming",
    "D": "Bloggertainment",
    "answer": "C: Advergaming",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do many businesses often use to promote products and increase awareness?",
    "A": "Marketing research",
    "B": "Cause-related advertising",
    "C": "Public relations activities",
    "D": "Creative thinking",
    "answer": "C: Public relations activities",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a process that weeds out defective products after they've been created:?",
    "A": "Quality assurance",
    "B": "Quality improvement",
    "C": "Quality control",
    "D": "Quality command",
    "answer": "C: Quality control",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A risk management program helps __________ risk, which makes it easier to organize and handle.",
    "A": "encourage",
    "B": "prevent",
    "C": "process",
    "D": "categorize",
    "answer": "D: categorize",
    "topic": "Risk management & insurance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a tangible product:?",
    "A": "An insurance policy",
    "B": "A haircut",
    "C": "A pizza",
    "D": "Cooking lessons",
    "answer": "C: A pizza",
    "topic": "Risk management & insurance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ethical managers have the ability to make impartial judgments about employees and their actions without",
    "A": "being emotional.",
    "B": "showing favoritism.",
    "C": "expressing criticism.",
    "D": "feeling inferior.",
    "answer": "B: showing favoritism.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A new business owner can identify incorrect assumptions and faulty forecasts by comparing the business's performance against the company's",
    "A": "sales receipts.",
    "B": "mission statement.",
    "C": "business plan.",
    "D": "management plan.",
    "answer": "C: business plan.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an example of a broad goal that management might develop for a business?",
    "A": "Conduct training programs",
    "B": "Replace damaged equipment",
    "C": "Hire an advertising agency",
    "D": "Reduce operating expenses",
    "answer": "D: Reduce operating expenses",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a promotion-related question that a business might ask to adjust its marketing mix in response to environmental changes:?",
    "A": "To whom should we offer discounts?",
    "B": "Is our product aimed at a specific market?",
    "C": "What laws affect our advertising?",
    "D": "Which channels of distribution will we use?",
    "answer": "C: What laws affect our advertising?",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of William's business goals is to increase customer satisfaction by 15%. What is one measure that William could use to assess his progress toward that goal?",
    "A": "Number of product returns",
    "B": "Cost of marketing efforts",
    "C": "Level of employee tur nover",
    "D": "Number of touchpoints",
    "answer": "A: Number of product returns",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The ADKAR model, which stands for Awareness, Desire, Knowledge, Ability, and Reinforcement, is a strategy that businesses use for",
    "A": "change management.",
    "B": "project management.",
    "C": "project initiation.",
    "D": "programmed thinking.",
    "answer": "A: change management.",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "B Open corporation. Open corporations sell stock to the general public. By buying stock in an open corporation, John can become a business owner without daily involvement in the business. In addition, shareholders in an open corporation are only liable for t he amount they invest in the company. Sole proprietorship is a form of ownership that requires owner participation. General partnership combines the capital, experience, and abilities of two or more people. Sole proprietorships and general partnerships inv olve unlimited liability. A close (private) corporation does not offer stock for sale to the general public. In many cases, the shareholders manage and operate the business, which means the owners participate in the day-to-day activities of the business. SOURCE: BL:003 Explain types of business ownership SOURCE: LAP-BL-003-Own It Your Way (Types of Business Ownership) 3. C To prevent future problems. Individuals who are partners in a business should have a partnership agreement, even though it is not required by law, because it does help the partners prevent future problems. It should include such points as the rights, respo nsibilities, and contributions of each partner; the division of authority and profit for each partner; the length of the partnership agreement; and the actions to take if a partner dies or becomes unable to continue the business. Stock is sold for corporat ions, not for partnerships. The partnership agreement does not affect taxes. SOURCE: BL:006 Select form of business ownership SOURCE: LAP-BL-006-Taking Care of Business (Select Forms of Business Ownership) 4. D Fraud. A tort is a private wrongdoing against another person. Businesses can be held responsible in a variety of torts. For example, suppose a business's employee intentionally provides misleading product information to a customer to make a sale. Then, the customer purchases and is injured by the product based on the employee's misleading information. The customer may file a civil lawsuit against the business, and in some situations, the business's employee for fraudulent behavior. Assault and intrusion are criminal acts that are addressed in the criminal court system rather than the civil court system. Defamation is a tort that involves harm to an individual's or business's reputation. SOURCE: BL:069 Identify the basic torts relating to business ente rprises SOURCE: Laws.com. (2020, September 12). A brief overview of tort law. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://tort.laws.com/tort-law Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 2 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 5. A Performing certain channel activities expertly. Channel members add value to a product by performing certain channel activities expertly. Moving the product smoothly through the channel benefits all channel members. Channels are not meant to make products more costly or more difficult for consumers to find. Channels work best and deliver value-added products when channel members work together toward common goals. SOURCE: CM:001 Explain the nature and scope of channel management SOURCE: LAP-CM-001-Chart Your Channels (Channel Management) 6. B A construction company buying wood. An industrial user is a business that buys materials, services, or goods that will be used to make other goods or used in the operation of the company. A construction company, for instance, must buy lumber, steel, and ot her materials needed to build homes and offices. An ultimate consumer, on the other hand, is anyone who personally uses a good or service to satisfy their own needs or wants. We are all ultimate consumers of many different goods and services. Examples of u ltimate consumers include an individual buying toothpaste, a family buying groceries, and a student buying school supplies. SOURCE: CM:003 Explain the nature of channels of distribution SOURCE: LAP-CM-003-Channel It (Channels of Distribution) 7. A Intensive. Producers of consumer goods, such as dishwashing soap or candy, should use intensive distribution to make their product as available to consumers as possible. Exclusive distribution would make this product less available to the everyday consumer, as in the case of upscale cars or clothing, and is impractical for this type of product. Inclusive distribution is not a recognized distribution strategy. Selective distribution is a balance between intensive and exclusive distribution, such as the sale of certain power tools only through one or two retailers, and like exclusive distribution, it is impractical for dishwashing soap. SOURCE: CM:010 Select channels of distribution SOURCE: Indeed. (2022, April 2). What is intensive distribution? Defi nition and examples. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.indeed.com/career-advice/career-development/intensive-distribution 8. D Follow directions in the request for proposal document. A formally solicited project provides the writer with a request for proposal document (RFP) that provides directions on how to prepare and write the proposal. Since a formally solicited project is alr eady defined by the client, there is no need for the writer to provide any type of objectives to define a proposed project. Updates are provided for ongoing projects. Explanations for continuing a project are given for renewal project proposals. SOU RCE: CO:062 Write proposals SOURCE: Mulholland, B. (2021, September 17). 13 types of project proposals that get approved (and how to write them). Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.process.st/project-proposal/Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 3 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 9. B To use touchpoints to create positive customer experiences. The brand promise is a company's agreement (spoken or unspoken) with customers that it will consistently meet their expectations and deliver on its brand characteristics and values. To build and m aintain customer relationships, a company's brand promise should strive to create positive experiences for customers-experiences that will encourage them to return to the business again and again. Companies use various touchpoints to create these experien ces for their customers. Touchpoints are all of the opportunities that a company has to connect with its customers and reinforce its brand value. Touchpoints may include the company's employees, product attributes and packaging, and technological systems ( e.g., phone, website). A slogan (tag line) is a phrase that is easy to remember, such as \"Nationwide is on your side.\" A trade character is a symbol that is personified (e.g., Tony the Tiger). Businesses often use slogans and trade characters as elements o f their brands. Changing slogans frequently or developing different trade characters may confuse customers, which may reduce brand recognition. One reason that businesses establish certain types of policies (e.g., sales, service) is to ensure that customer s are treated fairly. Establishing different policies for different customers is not treating customers fairly, and in some circumstances, such actions are illegal. SOURCE: CR:001 Identify company's brand promise SOURCE: Patel, S. (2022, February 15). What are customer journey touch points? (and how to optimize them). Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.revechat.com/blog/customer-touchpoints 10. A Requirements for product testing. The government has passed many laws intended to protect consumers. In addition to requiring product testing, these laws prohibit false advertising and deceptive labeling, make food inspection mandatory, and set standards o f safety in building construction. None of these laws are intended to monitor business growth or to generate competition. Making government effective does not necessarily protect consumers. SOURCE: EC:008 Determine the relationship between governmen t and business SOURCE: LAP-EC-016-Regulate and Protect (Government and Business) 11. A A regulated monopoly. These companies are allowed to exist when legislators believe that one large company can more efficiently serve consumers than several small ones. Price discrimination is an illegal activity in which a business charges customers diffe rent prices for similar products. Price competition occurs when businesses use prices to attract scarce customer dollars. Nonprice competition occurs when businesses compete on a basis other than price. SOURCE: EC:012 Explain the concept of competit ion SOURCE: LAP-EC-912-Ready, Set, Compete! (Competition) 12. C Economies of scale. Economies of scale occur when unit costs are reduced as the scale of something in the business increases. In this case, buying in bulk is what has increased in scale. Marginal cost is the change in total cost that occurs when the quantity produced changes by one unit. The law of diminishing returns indicates that as more and more units of an input are added to production, the per person output decreases. With a t ying agreement, a vendor ties the sale of one good to a customer agreeing to buy a second good. No evidence is provided that a tying agreement has been set up. SOURCE: EC:077 Describe the concept of economies of scale SOURCE: Kenton, W. (2022, June 11). Economies of scale: What are they and how are they used? Retrieved August 30, 2022, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/e/economiesofscale.asp Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 4 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 13. D An objective measure. Collette has set an objective measure for her success-filling out five job applications this week. If she fills out fewer than five, she will not consider her goal t o have been achieved. In this case, she is not basing her success standard on past performance, improvement, or outperforming others. SOURCE: EI:027 Develop an achievement orientation SOURCE: LAP-EI-027-High Hopes (Developing an Achievement Orientation) 14. D Businesses. Associations with color are an especially important cultural sensitivity issue for businesses. When a company does international business, it must be careful to consi der the connotations of the colors it uses on packaging, labels, etc., in the cultures that will be affected. Associations with color tend to be a less important issue for individuals, families, and travelers. SOURCE: EI:033 Exhibit cultural sensitivity SOURCE: LAP-EI-033-Getting To Know You (Cultural Sensitivity) 15. D The audience is taking your idea seriously. After presenting an idea, it's normal to encounter some objections from the audience. Objections typically signify that the audience is listening and taking your idea seriously. Objections do not signify that you r audience is unengaged, that your idea won't be accepted, or that you haven't done enough research. If handled correctly, you can overcome objections and gain the acceptance of your audience. SOURCE: EI:108 \"Sell\" ideas to others SOURCE: LAP-EI-108-Do They Buy It? (\"Selling\" Ideas to Others) 16. B Corporate governance structures. An effective corporate governance strategy combines controls, policies, and guidelines to ensure that the organi zation is reaching its objectives while meeting its stakeholders' needs. Common examples of controls, policies, and guidelines include performance measurement systems, audits, separation of power within the governance structure, and clearly defined communi cation lines. Controls and policies can also be external, such as legal regulations for business. Policies and guidelines are also important for driving an organization toward its goals. Controls, policies, and guidelines are not necessarily the primary elements of public relations strategies, legal regulations for businesses, or nondisclosure agreements. SOURCE: PD:302 Identify the factors that impact governance structures SOURCE: Davoren, J. (2017, November 21). Three types of corporate governance mechanisms. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/three-types-corporate-governance-mechanis ms-66711.html 17. A It builds good working relationships. Helping your coworkers builds trust and teamwork, which improves your working relationships. Employees who share their knowledge build a stronger team and a positive work environment. Being helpful doesn't necessarily cause your coworkers to view you as an expert or convince your boss to promote you. When you teach your coworkers the best techniques, your team is likely to work more efficiently, but it doesn't reduce your work responsibiliti es. SOURCE: EI:115 Share best practices with key individuals and groups SOURCE: Indeed. (2022, August 5). How to build good working relationships at work. Retrieved August 30, 2022, from https://www.indeed.com/career-advice/starting-new-job/how-to-build-good-working-relationships Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 5 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 18. B Check your gut feeling. Using a logic al, step-by-step process is a great way to be sure you're responding correctly to an ethical dilemma. However, it's still important to check in with your gut feelings. If Zoey is following her intuition, she is checking in with her gut feeling to see what is right. Considering all your potential actions, figuring out who's affected, and getting the facts are other steps of the process. SOURCE: EI:125 Recognize and respond to ethical dilemmas SOURCE: LAP-EI-125-Make the Right Choice (Recognizing and Responding to Ethical Dilemmas) 19. C Identifying an unmet want or need. Entrepreneurial discovery is the process of detecting and matching product and market opportunities with one another in a m anner that satisfies the market and the business. This requires the entrepreneur or small-business owner to conduct research to discover what the market needs or wants. Screening ideas and analyzing the feasibility of an idea are steps that occur after ide ntifying a want or need. Determining risks and rewards are considerations when conducting a feasibility analysis. SOURCE: EN:001 Explain the need for entrepreneurial discovery SOURCE: Wood, U. (2016, December 23). How to grow your market by identifying unmet needs. Retrieved August 30, 2022, from https://www.bizjournals.com/bizjour nals/how-to/marketing/2016/12/how-to-grow-your-market-by-identifying-unmet-needs.html 20. B Observing. Entrepreneurial discovery is the process of detecting and matching product and market opportunities with one another in a way that satisfies bot h the market and the business. Many successful entrepreneurs discover product or business ideas by being observant. They make a point of watching people and situations to detect a problem or unfulfilled need. Then, the entrepreneurs work to develop a produ ct or process to solve the problem or fulfill the need. Persuading, disagreeing, and informing are not activities that typically help entrepreneurs recognize product and business ideas. SOURCE: EN:002 Discuss entrepreneurial discovery processes SOURCE: Cote, C. (2022, April 5). How to identify business & market opportunities. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://online.hbs.edu/blog/post/how-to-identify-business-opportunities 21. A Cloud computing applications. Entrepreneurs often find business opportunities by monitoring trends-the directions in which society is moving. Technological trends, such as the increased use of cloud computing, provide new business opportunities for aspiri ng entrepreneurs. Cloud computing applications allow businesses and individuals to prepare and store data on a hosted internet server rather than on a personal computer. The advantage of using cloud computing applications is that it often reduces a busines s's need to buy usage licenses from software developers for multiple employees. Trade agreements affect the importing and exporting of goods across national borders. Environmental awareness or \"going green\" is a societal trend. A movement to a private ente rprise system is an economic trend that is often spurred by political changes. SOURCE: EN:003 Assess global trends and opportunities for business ventures SOURCE: Sylvester, C. (2018, January 16). 8 important technology trends that will impact small businesses in 2018. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.networkdepot.com/8-important-technology-trends-will-impact-small-businesses-2018/Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 6 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 22. C Solve problems. An entrepreneur is a person who starts and assumes the risk for a business. Sometimes, entrepreneurs generate ideas for products that may solve a specific problem for a mar ket. Entrepreneurs do not usually look for ways to increase their liability, rationalize their spending, or control outcomes when they are generating business ideas. SOURCE: EN:006 Generate venture ideas SOURCE: Entrepreneur. (2017, October 30). Entrepreneurs solve problems differently than other professionals. Really! Here are the 6 ways. Retrieved August 30, 2022, from https://www.entrepreneur.com/artic le/303407 23. C Career. When starting a new business, there is always risk-the possibility of loss or failure. When an entrepreneur leaves a successful career with a reputable company to start a business, there is the risk that the entrepreneur m ay unintentionally do something to damage their reputation. A poor reputation may hinder the entrepreneur's ability to go back to the career if the new venture fails. Olivia is not considering market, economic, or legal risks. Market risks relate to the bu siness's customers or target market and may involve considerations such as product acceptance. Economic risks relate to factors that affect the business cycle (e.g., interest rates and unemployment rates). Legal risks relate to government regulations. SOURCE: EN:010 Assess risks associated with venture SOURCE: VanDeren, J. (2016, October 6). Career risks: What they are and why we have to take them. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2016/10/06/career-risks-what-they-are-and-why-we-have-to-take-them/24. C Turning d own work due to limited capacity. If a startup is turning down work because it doesn't have the capacity to take on new clients, then its leader should think about hiring new employees to help expand the startup's capacity. If the startup remains stagnant, it misses out on potential growth and profit opportunities. Hiring should be a strategic, well-planned decision and should not be done when the employer is stressed. Being willing to hire the first person interviewed or lacking an understanding of what th e new employee will do are not reasons to hire a new employee. SOURCE: EN:017 Explain factors to consider in determining a venture's human-resources needs SOURCE: Boitnott, J. (2018, April 24). 5 signs it's time to hire your first employee. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.inc.com/john-boitnott/5-signs-its-time-to-hire-your-first-employe e.html 25. B Does the workload require a full-time or part-time employee? A business owner considers many factors when determining if they should hire an employee. An important factor to consider is the nature of the work that the owner needs to h ave done-bookkeeping, purchasing, ad placement, etc. The owner must also consider how often certain tasks are performed (e.g., weekly, monthly). After determining what skills are needed, the owner must decide if there is enough work for a full-time employ ee or if a part-time employee could handle the workload. The business owner recruits applicants after determining the necessary skills and approximate workload. Therefore, the business owner cannot answer the remaining questions until they determine the ty pe and amount of work they need the employee to do. SOURCE: EN:018 Explain considerations in making the decision to hire staff SOURCE: Allegiance Staffing. (2020, August 18). When should I hire additional employees? Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.allegiancestaffing.com/blog/hire-additional-employees/Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 7 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 26. C Conveyer belt. A capital resource is anything of value that a business needs on an ongoing basis to operate. Trucks, office equipment, and machines such as conveyer belts are examples of capital resources. Pencils are office supplies. A credit card is a me thod of payment that allows a cardholder to purchase now and pay later. Granite is an igneous rock; therefore, it is a natural resource. SOURCE: EN:020 Identify capital resources needed for the venture SOURCE: Tatum, M. (2022, August 7). What is a capital resource? Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.wise-geek.com/wh at-is-a-capital-resource.htm 27. B Buy the furniture because rental costs will exceed the purchase price in 1.97 years. To determine whether to rent or buy office furniture, the small-business owner needs to first calculate the annual cost of renting the furniture. To do this, multiply the monthly rate of $275 by the number of employees needing furniture (6). This provides the total monthly rental expense: $275 X 6 = $1,650. Next, multiply the total monthly rental expense by 12, the number of months in a year: $1,650 X 12 = $19,800. Now, det ermine how much the small-business owner would pay if they bought the furniture. Multiply the furniture cost per person by the number of people needing furniture: $6,500 X 6 = $39,000. Finally, divide the furniture's total cost by the annual rental rate to determine how many years it would take for the cost of the rented furniture to exceed the cost of the purchased furniture: $39,000/$19,800 = 1.97 years. In a little less than two years, the cost of the rental furniture will exceed the cost of the purcha sed furniture. If the small-business owner has the money, it would be worthwhile for them to buy rather than rent the office furniture. SOURCE: EN:021 Assess the costs/benefits associated with resources SOURCE: Hanson, M. (2010). Business math (17th ed.) [p. 350]. Mason, OH: South-Western Cengage Learning. 28. D Resources are often limited. When a venture is first starting out, resources are usually limited because the company is not yet making a profit or generating revenue. Therefore, it's important to use resources productively to keep the venture going. Invest ors do not necessarily expect immediate returns. Using resources productively does not necessarily build brand loyalty or improve marketing efforts. SOURCE: EN:030 Explain the impact of resource productivity on venture success SOURCE: Glauser, M. (2017, February 15). How these 5 entrepreneurs used their limited resources to grow their business into a successful venture. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.entrepreneur.com/slideshow/281277#0 29. D When writing the business plan. Many experts agree that it's best to develop an exit strategy as soon as possible-even while writing the business plan. Having a plan for how you'll leave the company helps you have a more successful business. It should als o help you avoid waiting to sell the business until you start to lose money-ideally, you'll be able to exit your business while the company is still successful. Contacting a potential buyer and leaving the company are things that are done after developing an exit strategy. SOURCE: EN:037 Develop exit strategies SOURCE: Richards, D. (2020, January 3). How to write a business exit plan. Retrieved August 30, 2022, from https://www.thebalance.com/writing-a-business-plan-planning-your-exit-strategy-1200841 Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 8 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 30. C Elissa starts a company when she develops a new app. Elissa is an entrepreneur because she identifies an opportunity to create new value, develops and offers a unique product, assumes the risks of starting and building a business, focuses on the improvemen t and growth of that business, and receives personal and financial rewards for her efforts. Working for someone else's accounting firm, investing money, and asking for a raise are not examples of entrepreneurship. SOURCE: EN:039 Describe the nature of entrepreneurship SOURCE: AmosWEB. (2000-2022). Entrepreneurship. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from http://www.amosweb.com/cgi-bin/awb_nav.pl?s=wpd&c=dsp&k=entrepren eurship 31. D Exposure to new markets. When a business expands internationally, it often gains exposure to new markets for its products. When international customers discover and enjoy that new business's products, sales often increase. A business operating in several d ifferent countries will have more cultural barriers to deal with because customer preferences, traditions, and trends vary from country to country. When a business operates in many countries, it faces more compliance challenges since it must deal with a gr eater number of and more types of regulations imposed by different countries (e.g., ingredients and packaging used for products). Business expansion into international markets exposes a business to more financial risk since different currencies, tariffs, a nd shipping fees often reduce profits. SOURCE: EN:041 Describe small-business opportunities in international trade SOURCE: Arthur, L. (2019, January 28). The advantages & disadvantages of international franchises. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/advantages-disadvantages-international-franchises-22488.html 32. B Stay engaged in their jobs and their company. It may seem appealing to underpay workers while a new company gets on its feet-but it sure isn't ethical! Employees who are paid fairly for a job well done are more likely to stay engaged in their jobs and on board with their company's mission. Workers who aren't paid well, on the other hand, probably won't stick around for long-forcing the company to go through the expensive process of recruiting all over again. Underpaid workers are also likely to feel resen tment toward management and experience serious job dissatisfaction. SOURCE: EN:044 Describe the use of business ethics in entrepreneurship SOURCE: LAP-EN-044-Ethical Excellence (Ethics in Entrepreneurship) 33. C Factor. A factor is a finance company or bank that will pay cash for the accounts receivable of a firm for a charge of 0.5-2.75% of the outstanding accounts. The factor may also assume responsibility for collecting the accounts receivable. Businesses usual ly do not raise capital by selling accounts receivable to friends, creditors, or investors. SOURCE: FI:031 Explain sources of financial assistance SOURCE: Barone,",
    "A": "(2022, March 31). Factor. Retrieved August 30, 2022, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/f/factor.asp 34. D What its sales revenues are. A business may review its accounting information to learn what its sales revenues are. Internal accounting records will not reveal the size of competitors' debts or provide insights into industry trends. Accounting records do n ot typically include information about shipping. SOURCE: FI:085 Explain the concept of accounting SOURCE: LAP-FI-085-Show Me the Money (Nature of Accounting) Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 9 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 35. B A claim a creditor has against a business's assets. A liability is a debt the business must pay, or a claim a creditor has against the business's assets. Most businesses have liabilities-it is not necessarily a sign that a business is in financial trouble unless the business has more liabilities than it can reasonably pay. Liabilities do not add value to the business; rather, they subtract value. Owner's equity is the portion of the business that belongs to its owners or stockholders. SOURCE: FI:093 Explain the nature of balance sheets SOURCE: LAP-FI-093-The Right Balance (The Nature of Balance Sheets) 36. C They typically have at least five categories. Although some income statements include other categories as well, they should all have at least five basic categories. These categories include revenue, cost of goods sold/cost of sales, gross profit, operating expenses, and net income/profit. Income statements summarize a business's income and expenses over a period of time, and while this information can be used to make decisions about the future, it doesn't forecast a business's future. Income statements are analyzed primarily by a business's top executives and managers, creditors, and investors, but not customers. Ratio statement is not another name for income statements. Income statements are sometimes referred to as earnings statements, operating statements, and profit-and-loss statements. SOURCE: FI:094 Describe the nature of income statements SOURCE: LAP-FI-094-Watch Your Bottom Line (Income Statements) 37. A Zero-based. Rebuilding the budget for each new budgeting period is a strategy k nown as zero-based budgeting. It's the answer to traditional incremental budgeting, which only makes slight changes to the budget based on the results from the last budgeting period. Long-term and fixed are types of budget formats, not budgeting strategies. SOURCE: FI:099 Develop company's/department's budget SOURCE: LAP-FI-099-Build Your Game Plan (Developing a Company/Department Budget) 38. D Gross margin. Businesses calculate gross margin to prepare a profit-and-loss statement. Gross margin is the amount of money a business has left after subtracting the cost of merchandise sold from the net sales figure. Gross margin is the figure from which total operating expenses are subtracted to determine net income or net loss. Book value is the true value of a company's assets including its stock. Interest rate is the price rate for the use of money. Petty cash is a small amount of money kept on hand by a business for business purchases. SOURCE: FI:102 Interpret financial statements SOURCE: Anwah, S.G. (2022, August 30). How to interpret financial statements. Retrieved August 30, 2022, from https://www.thebalancesmb.com/interpreting-the-cash-flow-statement-1200760 Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 10 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 39. A Common-sized statements. Common-sized statements use percentages for the purposes of comparing one company to another within an industry or one company to overall industry averages. Percentages are used for comparison purposes because the relative sizes of companies can make it difficult to use dollar figures, for example. Horizontal analysis is also used for comparison, but it is most often used to compare the same pieces of information as they have changed from one period to another within a single compan y. Percentages are also often used in vertical analysis, but they are used to show what percentage of a general category is made up of a single item (e.g., what percentage of total assets are long-term assets). These percentages can then be compared across time but are not as often used to compare businesses to one another. Trend analysis is a method that uses data from the past to predict future data. This is often used in analyzing stock prices. SOURCE: FI:334 Describe types of financial statement analysis (e.g., ratio analysis, trend analysis, etc.) SOURCE: Warren, C.S., Jones, J.P., & Taylor, W.B. (2020). Financial and managerial accounting (15th ed.) [Lesson 14-2]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc. 40. D Increased productivity. A business may include many different benefits in a cost-benefit analysis, including increased productivity. Decreased market share, decreased efficiency, and increased expenses are disadvantages to a business, not be nefits. SOURCE: FI:357 Describe the nature of cost-benefit analysis SOURCE: LAP-FI-357-Running the Numbers (Cost-Benefit Analysis) 41. A Income statement. A company's net profit is presented on the final row of the income statement and is often referred to as the company's \"bottom line.\" While profitability analysis typically uses information from both the income statement and the balance s heet to calculate profitability ratios, the income statement displays the net profit for a given accounting period. The statement of cash flows, which is not helpful in calculating profitability ratios, is used by investors in evaluating investment risk. T he statement of changes in equity uses net profit in certain calculations but does not display this figure on its bottom line. SOURCE: FI:542 Monitor business's profitability SOURCE: Tuovila, A. (2021, April 18). Bottom line. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/b/bottomline.asp 42. A Military experience. The courts do not view asking for an applicant's military experien ce as discriminatory. Asking an applicant's date of birth may be considered age discrimination, while asking for number of children may discriminate against women. Height and weight can only be asked when they are bona fide occupational qualifications; oth erwise, they cannot legally be asked, because they can be used to discriminate against women and certain nationalities. SOURCE: HR:356 Select and hire new employees SOURCE: Williams, E. (2022, February 2). What is legal to ask in a job application? Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://work.chron.com/legal-ask-job-application-15948.html Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 11 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 43. A Employees may already have a s olution to the problem. Managers should try to obtain employee input when resolving a complaint because the employees may already have a solution to the problem, and they tend to support what they help create. Managers must keep in mind that employees may not be objective about a situation in which they are involved and that they have their own best interests at heart. Since many factors are usually involved in a problem, the employees may know the results, or effects, of the problem without knowing its tru e cause. Asking for employee input in resolving a problem is not always the easiest way to handle it and may create additional problems, rather than quickly resolving the initial problem. SOURCE: HR:366 Handle employee complaints and grievances SOURCE: Lucas, S. (2019, September 6). 6 tips for handling employee complaints. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.thebalancecareers.com/best-handle-employee-complaints-1917594 44. C The results of punishing undesirable behavior are unpredictable. Supervisors cannot predict how employees will react to remedial action. When properly administered, remed ial action should affect behavior without unintended complications. While some employees may, after discipline, be hostile toward the supervisor or continue to commit rule violations, disciplinary cases often end without incident. Psychological studies hav e shown that behavior that is rewarded is likely to be repeated. When discipline policies are communicated to employees when they begin working for the business, appropriate forms of discipline should not cause individuals great psychological damage if dis ciplinary action occurs. SOURCE: HR:369 Explain the nature of remedial action SOURCE: Assad, A. (n.d.). The effects of punishment on employee behavior. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/effects-punishment-employee-behavior-14302.html 45. C Creating a positive work environment. A business's overall work environment is affected by the work culture, which is the way the organization operates with regard to its treatment of employees and those outside the business. Owners and managers who treat employees respectfully, listen to their feedback, communicate openly, and reward good performance tend to foster a positive work culture. In a positive work culture, employees are more willing to work together to meet the business's goals. Competition is a rivalry. Consensus is a decision-making outcome that requires the substantial agreement of each group member. Groupthink is an extreme form of group cohesiveness that emphasizes the group's best interests and discourages independent thinking. In the situa tion described, Jay is not encouraging a competitive mindset, implementing consensus strategies, or supporting groupthink behavior. SOURCE: HR:403 Foster \u00e2\u20ac\u0153right\u00e2\u20ac \u009d environment for employees SOURCE: Huntington, S. (2019, December 11). Creating a positive work environment. Retrieved August 30, 2022, from https://articles.bplans.com/creating-positive-work-environment 46. A True; all employees make either a positive or negative impact on a business. A good employee in a certain job position can boost a company's productivity, help create profit, and contribute to a pleasant working environment. The wrong employee in th at same position may not only cause a company to miss out on these benefits, but can also create negative results in their place. Not all employees make a positive impact. Managers, supervisors, executives, and board members are not the only people who mak e an impact on a business. SOURCE: HR:410 Discuss the nature of human resources management SOURCE: LAP-HR-410-People Pusher (Nature of Human Resources Management) Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 12 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 47. B Objective. Researchers must keep their own opinions out of the way when they are gathering data. If a researcher's biases are obvious to research respondents, then the respondents may give answers that they think the researcher wants to hear rather than wh at they actually believe or know to be true. If marketing research is to be effective, researchers must be as objective (not subjective) as possible. Although marketing research does need to be timely, this isn't illustrated in this example. Effective mark eting research is valid research. SOURCE: IM:010 Explain the nature of marketing research SOURCE: LAP-IM-010-Seek and Find (Marketing Research) 48. C How actual sales compare to sales goals. The data in sales reports from a company's sales team can allow marketers to view how actual sales compare to sales goals. The latest market research studies would not come from the sales team, but from trade journa ls or market research firms. The prices of raw materials are data that come from a company's vendors. Data regarding competitors' products come from observing what competitors are doing. SOURCE: IM:012 Describe the need for marketing data SOURCE: LAP-IM-012-Data Do It (Need for Marketing Data) 49. D Erica goes to a coffee shop every day in hopes of winning a contest. Sales promotion includes promotional tactics such as contests like the one Erica is hoping to win. The contest is a n effective marketing strategy that helps boost sales and reach marketing goals. A commercial is an example of advertising, not sales promotion. A press conference is publicity rather than sales promotion. Fatima's interaction with customers is selling, no t sales promotion. SOURCE: MK:002 Describe marketing functions and related activities SOURCE: LAP-MK-001-Work the Big Seven (Marketing Functions) 50. A Increase sales by 5%. Marketing goals are objectives that marketers plan to fulfill. Increasing sales by 5% is what the company plans to achieve. Reducing prices is a strategy, or plan of action for achieving a goal or objective. Creating a new website and sending out an email newsletter could be considered tactics, or ways a company could carry out its strategy. SOURCE: MP:001 Explain the concept of marketing strategies SOURCE: LAP-MP-001-Pick the Mix (Nature of Marketing Strategies) 51. C Rate of use. Busy parents have been identified as frequent consumers or users of energy drinks; their rate of use is an example of shared behavior. Loyalty response refers to a consumer's preference for a particular brand. Occasion response refers to p urchases that occur at specific times (e.g., birthdays, holidays). Economic status refers to a person's wealth. SOURCE: MP:003 Explain the concept of market and market identification SOURCE: LAP-MP-003-Have We Met? (Market Identification) Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 13 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 52. B Market leadership. Market leadership is a potential strength that a manager might identify as a result of conducting a SWOT (strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, threats) analysis. New foreign markets are an example of a potential opportunity. La rge inventories is an example of a potential weakness. Market saturation is an example of a potential threat. SOURCE: MP:010 Conduct SWOT analysis for use in the marketing planning process SOURCE: LAP-MP-010-Analyze This! (SWOT Analysis) 53. B $295,925. Businesses often forecast sales in dollar amounts. In this example, the business currently has a 30% share of the market but expects to obtain an additional 5% next year. Therefore, next year's market share is expected to be 35% of an $8 45,500 market. To calculate that amount, multiply the dollar value of the market by the market share ($845,500 X 35% [or.35] = $295,925). SOURCE: MP:014 Forecast sales for marketing plan SOURCE: Indeed. (2021, May 25). Formula for a sales forecast and how to calculate it. Retrieved August 22, 2022, from https://www.indeed.com/career-advice/career-development/formula-for-sales-forecast 54. B They want to understand more about their customers' interests, activities, and concerns. The more advertisers know about their customers, the more they can effectively target their audiences. Advertisers go beyond demographic information and are continuall y trying to find ways to learn more behavioral information about their customers. Having increasingly large amounts of information about customers makes record keeping a greater challenge, necessitating the use of databases. Some advertisers sell customer information to other companies, but an increasing number recognize this practice as an invasion of their customers' privacy. Most companies of any size will not be able to recognize each and every one of their customers. The best they can do is to understa nd various groups of customers in terms of their behavior, interests, and preferences. SOURCE: MP:031 Develop customer profile SOURCE: Robinson, S. (2020, July 8). How to create customer profiles with examples. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.techtarget.com/searchcustomerexperience/tip/How-to-create-customer-profiles-with-examples 55. B What software programs will help the business operate efficiently? The type of business influences the venture's technological needs. The technology (e.g., computer software) the business selects should help the business run efficiently. For example, a med ical office needs different types of computer programs to maintain and store business information than a carpet-cleaning business. After the business owner determines the type of computer programs the venture needs, they can research vendors, costs, etc. R egardless of the type of business the owner is running, they will always need to maintain computer hardware to run the programs. The business doesn't legally structure the technology department differently from the rest of the business. SOURCE: NF:0 12 Determine venture's information technology needs SOURCE: Duggan, T. (n.d.). How to identify business IT needs. Retrieved August 19, 2022, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/identify-business-needs-351.html 56. B It consists of your surroundings. The term \"environment\" refers to your surroundings. This could mean anything-your living room, a classroom, the mall, etc. Although the term is often used to refer to the earth and its resources, its true meaning is much broader. Your environment has an e ffect on your performance and your decisions. Businesses exist within environments just as individuals do. SOURCE: NF:015 Conduct an environmental scan to obtain business information SOURCE: LAP-NF-015-Get the 4-1-1 (Conducting an Environmental S can) Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 14 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 57. D Predictive. Predictive analytics is used to analyze trends in past consumer behavior to predict future behavior. Descriptive analytics is used to condense big data into smaller, more useful pieces of information. Big data analytics refers to analyzing larg e amounts of data to discover patterns or trends and is not likely to describe specific holiday sales period data. Prescriptive analytics is used to go beyond descriptive and predictive models by recommending one or more courses of action and showing the l ikely business result of each decision. SOURCE: NF:139 Explain the principles of data analysis SOURCE: insightsoftware. (2021, February 17). Comparing descriptive, predictive, prescriptive, and diagnostic analytics. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://insightsoftware.com/blog/comparing-descriptive-predictive-prescriptive-and-diagnostic-analytics 58. A Cluster analysis. Cluster analysis is intended to group data points into groups or clusters. The goal here is to allow observable data to naturally collect into groups that are largely homogenous, share a set of characteristics, and are unlike the data in other groups or clusters. These clusters, when used to sort consumers, create market segments that can be targeted with marketing. Market basket analysis focuses on establishing links between data points that tend to occur together. This is often used in d etermining which items tend to be purchased together (placed in a \"market basket\" together). Prediction analysis, such as regression analysis, involves using independent or predictor variables to anticipate a response of a dependent variable. Forecasting a nalysis seeks to make predictions about specific time periods based on historical observations and other considerations. SOURCE: NF:148 Discuss the nature of data mining SOURCE: Camm, J.D., Cochran, J.J., Fry, M.J., Ohlmann, J.W., Anderson, D.R., Sweeney, D.J., & Williams, T.A. (2019). Business analytics (3rd ed.) [Lesson 4.1]. Boston, MA: Cengage Learning, Inc. 59. A Fire extinguishers. Businesses should keep fire extinguishers on the premises and make sure that all employees know where they are located. In the event that a fire breaks out, employees should be able to find the extinguishers quickly and attempt to put o ut the fire while another employee calls the fire department. Knowing where the fire extinguishers are and reacting quickly often prevents a fire from spreading and reduces the amount of damage. Fire-prevention programs do not require employees to know the location of all electrical outlets or hazardous materials. Employees should have easy access to the phone numbers of emergency services, rather than knowing the location of those services. SOURCE: OP:012 Establish safety policies and procedures SOURCE: Clark,",
    "B": ", Basteri,",
    "C": "G., Gassen, C., & Walker, M. (2014). Marketing dynamics (3rd ed.) [pp. 687-688]. Tinley Park, IL: Goodheart-Willcox. 60. D Intangible outputs. A service business produces an intangible output. Outputs are goods or services produced as the result of combining inputs. Coral's outputs are intangible because they have no physical presence. Coral does not produce tangible outputs, retail goods, or industrial services. SOURCE: OP:017 Explain the concept of production SOURCE: AmosWeb. (2000-2022). Production. Retrieved August 18, 2022, from https://www.amosweb.com/cgi-bin/awb_nav.pl?s=wpd&c=dsp&k=production Test 1268 ENTREPRENEURSHIP EXAM-KEY 15 Copyright \u00a9 20 23 by M BA Research and Curriculum Center\u00ae, Columbus, Ohio 61. C Creates standards. Management can help work toward the achievement of quality by implementing a quality assurance plan. The first step of putting together a quality assurance plan is to create quality standards. These standards help define quality and give the program a basis for functioning. Before a manager implements corrective action, trains staff, or puts together a quality committee, they need to create quality standards. SOURCE: OP:020 Describe the role of management in the achievement of qual ity SOURCE: Gartenstein,",
    "D": "(2019, March 27). How to build a quality assurance program. Retrieved August 30,",
    "answer": "B: , Basteri,",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit of establishing incident reporting procedures in the workplace:?",
    "A": "Employees use their judgment to determine if a report should be issued.",
    "B": "Managers who create these procedures are not required to follow up on incidents.",
    "C": "Managers who have information about incidents can investigate possible causes.",
    "D": "Employees cannot file official complaints if an incident is reported correctly.",
    "answer": "C: Managers who have information about incidents can investigate possible causes.",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For project managers, the most important part of managing stakeholder expectations is",
    "A": "justifying them.",
    "B": "understanding them.",
    "C": "competing against them.",
    "D": "delegating them.",
    "answer": "B: understanding them.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Nilesh started a new job, he trained alongside another employee for a few weeks so that he could get the hang of his job duties. The time that Nilesh spent training with the other employee is an example of a(n)?",
    "A": "emergency.",
    "B": "resource issue.",
    "C": "government regulation.",
    "D": "transition period.",
    "answer": "D: transition period.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The first step in an organizational risk assessment is",
    "A": "pinpointing who might be harmed.",
    "B": "evaluating the risks and making a plan.",
    "C": "recording and implementing your findings.",
    "D": "identifying the potential hazards.",
    "answer": "D: identifying the potential hazards.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A primary advantage for marketers who use direct mail to promote products is that",
    "A": "most marketers find that it is more effective than micro-marketing methods.",
    "B": "it is usually less expensive than personal selling methods.",
    "C": "it is more effective in creating brand awareness than television advertising.",
    "D": "marketers can deliver their messages to a broad audience.",
    "answer": "B: it is usually less expensive than personal selling methods.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kyra is a business owner who wants to calculate individual employee productivity. She knows that last month, her team of four workers generated $10,000 worth of goods by working 200 hours in an office space measuring 1,000 square feet. What is the labor productivity per employee for the whole month?",
    "A": "$40,000",
    "B": "$12.50",
    "C": "$800",
    "D": "$2,500",
    "answer": "D: $2,500",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an effective negotiation strategy:?",
    "A": "Using a \"give-and-take\" tactic to reach an agreement",
    "B": "Giving the other person as much time as they need to decide",
    "C": "Pushing the other person into making a decision",
    "D": "Insisting on your terms during the negotiation process",
    "answer": "A: Using a \"give-and-take\" tactic to reach an agreement",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determine the cost of goods sold for a business when the beginning inventory was $250,000, purchases were $600,000, and the ending inventory was $200,000.",
    "A": "$1,050,000",
    "B": "$650,000",
    "C": "$400,000",
    "D": "$150,000",
    "answer": "B: $650,000",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason it is important for a business to develop a marketing plan is that the plan",
    "A": "provides guidelines for personnel to meet the company's objectives.",
    "B": "allows the business to focus on short-term goals instead of long-term goals.",
    "C": "reduces the need to implement corrective action or contingency plans.",
    "D": "increases the business's financial security in an unpredictable environment.",
    "answer": "A: provides guidelines for personnel to meet the company's objectives.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A local veterinarian decides to add a surgical wing to their office, which will allow them to serve more patients over the coming years. The cost of building the new wing is an example of a(n)",
    "A": "operating expense.",
    "B": "expense control.",
    "C": "capital expenditure.",
    "D": "budget deficit.",
    "answer": "C: capital expenditure.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way that a business can learn about its competitors' activities is by",
    "A": "developing product specifications.",
    "B": "reviewing secondary data.",
    "C": "identifying communication barriers.",
    "D": "evaluating intranet efficiencies.",
    "answer": "B: reviewing secondary data.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Key performance indicators used to assess business performance should align with the business's",
    "A": "corporate culture.",
    "B": "payroll and benefits.",
    "C": "operating expenses.",
    "D": "goals and objectives.",
    "answer": "D: goals and objectives.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which form of business ownership makes up the minority of businesses in the U.S. yet makes up the majority of sales?",
    "A": "Sole proprietorships",
    "B": "Corporations",
    "C": "Partnerships",
    "D": "LLCs",
    "answer": "B: Corporations",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Dion works in the production planning department of a company that makes machinery. This machinery is then sold to companies that use it to create vehicles. Dion's company's output is considered",
    "A": "human resources.",
    "B": "consumer goods.",
    "C": "industrial goods.",
    "D": "intangible products.",
    "answer": "C: industrial goods.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Jackson, a manager at AMO Inc., uses the company car to run personal errands during working hours, he is acting unethically because he is?",
    "A": "misusing company resources.",
    "B": "violating government policies.",
    "C": "harassing other employees.",
    "D": "sharing confidential information.",
    "answer": "A: misusing company resources.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business has been running successfully for several years, what would be a probable next financial step?",
    "A": "Acquiring startup funds",
    "B": "Deciding on financial goals",
    "C": "Determining product prices",
    "D": "Purchasing a second location",
    "answer": "D: Purchasing a second location",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following decreases as production increases in a business that has economies of scale:?",
    "A": "Income taxes",
    "B": "Pay rates",
    "C": "Net profits",
    "D": "Fixed costs",
    "answer": "D: Fixed costs",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Intermediaries buy large quantities of goods from producers and sell smaller quantities to other intermediaries or to consumers. The result is that intermediaries __________ their per-unit cost for goods.",
    "A": "reduce",
    "B": "increase",
    "C": "stabilize",
    "D": "control",
    "answer": "A: reduce",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When employees are exposed to a variety of different ideas and perspectives, they are more likely to come up with their own new ideas and strategies. In other words, knowledge and learning lead to?",
    "A": "leadership.",
    "B": "innovation.",
    "C": "complacency.",
    "D": "curiosity.",
    "answer": "B: innovation.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Melissa has been assigned a unique task at work; her boss wants her to oversee her team's adoption of a new software. They explain that Melissa should make a plan for the integration of the new software, support her teammates in the transition, and ensure that the transition is successful. In other words, Melissa is responsible for",
    "A": "change management.",
    "B": "managerial control.",
    "C": "human resources management.",
    "D": "organizational goal setting.",
    "answer": "A: change management.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an important component of a business's press kit:?",
    "A": "Biographies of key company figures",
    "B": "Promotional messages",
    "C": "Customer testimonials",
    "D": "Interviews",
    "answer": "A: Biographies of key company figures",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a marketer is looking to gather data from a company's sales team, what information can they expect to find?",
    "A": "Updates on current trends in the marketing industry",
    "B": "Who the company's current and potential customers are",
    "C": "What products competitors are currently offering",
    "D": "The cost of goods, services, and raw materials",
    "answer": "B: Who the company's current and potential customers are",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After a good is produced, the price of that good should be set at a point at which",
    "A": "a large profit is made.",
    "B": "competition has sold the good.",
    "C": "the price is twice the cost.",
    "D": "the good will sell.",
    "answer": "D: the good will sell.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a way in which the government supports the growth of business:?",
    "A": "Surveys",
    "B": "Subsidies",
    "C": "Tax increases",
    "D": "Tariff reductions",
    "answer": "B: Subsidies",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following information about new employees are businesses required to report to the federal government:?",
    "A": "References",
    "B": "Compensation",
    "C": "Benefits",
    "D": "Address",
    "answer": "D: Address",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following would a business use to know how much money is available to hire more staff:?",
    "A": "Income statements",
    "B": "Profit-and-loss statements",
    "C": "Journals",
    "D": "Accounting information",
    "answer": "D: Accounting information",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An internet and cable provider is considering whether to implement a new process that would require its customer service agents to work the phone lines for 24 hours a day instead of the previous 12 hours a day. What type of factor will most likely impact t he design of this new process?",
    "A": "Regulatory",
    "B": "Environmental",
    "C": "Human",
    "D": "Technological",
    "answer": "C: Human",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ad-blocking software and spam filters help individuals avoid",
    "A": "direct print mail.",
    "B": "unsolicited publications.",
    "C": "unwanted digital advertising.",
    "D": "telemarketing calls.",
    "answer": "C: unwanted digital advertising.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A comprehensive report reveals that the Sabin Company can increase its data-entry outputs by 20% in a six-month period by installing the MMX software system. Sabin can use this type of business analysis to determine",
    "A": "why it should evaluate work schedules.",
    "B": "how to increase its efficiency.",
    "C": "how to detect a problem.",
    "D": "why it should obtain new markets.",
    "answer": "B: how to increase its efficiency.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When attempting to reduce costs, most businesses will first cut __________ costs.?",
    "A": "fixed",
    "B": "production",
    "C": "variable",
    "D": "operating",
    "answer": "D: operating",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is considered an external control mechanism impacting how a company functions:?",
    "A": "Industry standards",
    "B": "Payroll reviewed by leaders",
    "C": "Usernames and passwords",
    "D": "Segregation of duties",
    "answer": "A: Industry standards",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of two businesses that are indirect competitors:?",
    "A": "McDonald's and Burger King",
    "B": "Starbucks and American Eagle Outfitters",
    "C": "AT&T and Verizon",
    "D": "Apple and Microsoft",
    "answer": "B: Starbucks and American Eagle Outfitters",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following types of internal work teams do many businesses use to recognize product opportunities on a continuous basis:?",
    "A": "Cross-functional",
    "B": "Production",
    "C": "Homogenous",
    "D": "Independent-matrix",
    "answer": "A: Cross-functional",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an internal factor that impacts corporate governance structures:?",
    "A": "Regulation",
    "B": "Independent audits",
    "C": "Segregation of duties",
    "D": "Industry association guidelines",
    "answer": "C: Segregation of duties",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An applicant for a position as a checker-cashier was asked to ring a sale on the cash register and to balance the cash register based on specific figures and transactions. What management selection device is being used?",
    "A": "Written test",
    "B": "Background investigation",
    "C": "Performance simulation test",
    "D": "Interview",
    "answer": "C: Performance simulation test",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business owner who plans to exit their business venture by selling it to another company needs to develop the business in a way that",
    "A": "creates value for potential buyers.",
    "B": "appeals to a specific company.",
    "C": "allows them to maintain control after the purchase.",
    "D": "will generate regular income for them after the purchase.",
    "answer": "A: creates value for potential buyers.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business is successful in carrying out its brand promise, it provides its customers with?",
    "A": "a variety of messages.",
    "B": "above-average product quality.",
    "C": "consistent experiences.",
    "D": "a single touchpoint.",
    "answer": "C: consistent experiences.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an interactive public relations activity:?",
    "A": "Search engine optimization",
    "B": "Social media",
    "C": "Newsletter",
    "D": "Podcast",
    "answer": "B: Social media",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does a business's gross profit compare to the industry standard of 25% if it has annual sales of $500,000 and cost of goods sold is $400,000?",
    "A": "5% lower",
    "B": "10% lower",
    "C": "5% higher",
    "D": "10% higher",
    "answer": "A: 5% lower",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Supply chain management attempts to control which of the following business activities:",
    "A": "The buying and selling of stocks",
    "B": "Production, shipment, and distribution of products",
    "C": "Financial planning and managerial accounting",
    "D": "Human resources and communications",
    "answer": "B: Production, shipment, and distribution of products",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Yvonne wants her innovation to succeed, so she makes sure that there's a market for her innovation and that she has plenty of money and resources on hand. Which step of achieving innovation is Yvonne demonstrating?",
    "A": "Researching",
    "B": "Making connections",
    "C": "Reducing risk",
    "D": "Being open-minded and flexible",
    "answer": "C: Reducing risk",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can Tracy make sure that her marketing campaigns support her company's goals?",
    "A": "Engage in market planning",
    "B": "Select the right channels",
    "C": "Use pricing strategies",
    "D": "Speak with customers",
    "answer": "A: Engage in market planning",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "On a balance sheet, a business categorizes its inventory and accounts receivable as",
    "A": "long-term assets.",
    "B": "owner's equity.",
    "C": "current liabilities.",
    "D": "current assets.",
    "answer": "D: current assets.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses evaluate their relationships with banks to make sure the bank",
    "A": "likes the business.",
    "B": "understands the business.",
    "C": "operates worldwide.",
    "D": "will lower their interest rates.",
    "answer": "B: understands the business.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following roles of selling in our economy helps products be \"in the right place at the right time\":?",
    "A": "Affects employment",
    "B": "Promotes competition",
    "C": "Adds utility",
    "D": "Helps customers determine needs",
    "answer": "C: Adds utility",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The business's manager planned for only a small increase in sales over the next year because the largest local employer had laid off workers and was reducing production. What factor did the manager consider in setting this goal?",
    "A": "Customer service",
    "B": "Competition",
    "C": "Past sales",
    "D": "Economic conditions",
    "answer": "D: Economic conditions",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Arthur's boss asked him to study his company's sales data from the previous five years to see if there were any trends. After his research, Arthur presented his findings to his boss along with his predictions for the future. This is an example of the process of",
    "A": "customer retention.",
    "B": "data mining.",
    "C": "the selling process.",
    "D": "competitive analysis.",
    "answer": "B: data mining.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When an employee complaint results in a change in company policy, a manager should make sure employees are aware of the change by having the employees?",
    "A": "sign a statement that they know about the new policy.",
    "B": "copy the policy into their personal notebooks.",
    "C": "verbally repeat the policy to another employee.",
    "D": "explain their interpretation of the new policy to a supervisor.",
    "answer": "A: sign a statement that they know about the new policy.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a legally binding contract:?",
    "A": "A verbal expression of interest in an apartment",
    "B": "Terms and conditions associated with software",
    "C": "The purchase of an airline ticket",
    "D": "Making a doctor's appointment",
    "answer": "B: Terms and conditions associated with software",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When is it more economical for a business to lease rather than to buy a facility?",
    "A": "When credit standing is high",
    "B": "When interest rates are low",
    "C": "When available cash is limited",
    "D": "When mortgage money is plentiful",
    "answer": "C: When available cash is limited",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one reason why many people decide to become entrepreneurs?",
    "A": "Long hours",
    "B": "Less risk",
    "C": "Flexibility",
    "D": "Less responsibility",
    "answer": "C: Flexibility",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ada purchases jewelry and clothing from many different manufacturers and sells the items to customers in her boutique. What kind of buyer is Ada?",
    "A": "Business use",
    "B": "Transformational",
    "C": "Wholesale",
    "D": "Retail",
    "answer": "D: Retail",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Should a business develop permanent marketing strategies?",
    "A": "Yes, changing marketing strategies results in confusion for management.",
    "B": "No, businesses must be alert to changes in the marketplace.",
    "C": "Yes, the competition will know what to expect from the business.",
    "D": "No, marketing strategies change regardless of what the business wants.",
    "answer": "B: No, businesses must be alert to changes in the marketplace.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Yasir works for a company that manufactures glass bottles. His job is to inspect the bottles to make sure they were made correctly. He throws away any defective bottles. This examp le is best described as quality",
    "A": "assurance.",
    "B": "improvement.",
    "C": "circle.",
    "D": "control.",
    "answer": "D: control.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following words best describes enterprise risk management:?",
    "A": "Hazardous",
    "B": "Empathetic",
    "C": "Segmented",
    "D": "Comprehensive",
    "answer": "D: Comprehensive",
    "topic": "Risk management & insurance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an effect of monitoring your progress while working toward a goal?",
    "A": "It increases the likelihood that you will succeed.",
    "B": "It makes your goal more challenging and time-consuming.",
    "C": "It encourages communication throughout the process.",
    "D": "It adds external pressure to accomplish tasks.",
    "answer": "A: It increases the likelihood that you will succeed.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Macon Industries writes a purchase order for bolts, washers, and nails and sends the order to the Stanton Company to process. In this situation, the purchase order is a(n)",
    "A": "letter of intent.",
    "B": "open order.",
    "C": "accounts-receivable document.",
    "D": "sales contract.",
    "answer": "D: sales contract.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If one of your coworkers is treating another coworker unfairly, what is the ethical thing to do?",
    "A": "Ignore it.",
    "B": "Speak up.",
    "C": "Look for another job.",
    "D": "Be aggressive.",
    "answer": "B: Speak up.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an employee-assistance program:?",
    "A": "Corrective action",
    "B": "Compensation",
    "C": "Training on the use of dangerous power equipment",
    "D": "Career and education planning",
    "answer": "D: Career and education planning",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "While working as a server, Delia came up with an idea for an automated payment system for restaurants. This is an example of how",
    "A": "it is unethical to copy another business's model.",
    "B": "economic trends can help you identify opportunities.",
    "C": "work experience can lead to new business ventures.",
    "D": "entrepreneurs should focus on completely new industries.",
    "answer": "C: work experience can lead to new business ventures.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a product line:?",
    "A": "Philadelphia Cream Cheese",
    "B": "A1 Steak Sauce",
    "C": "Kraft meats",
    "D": "Capri Sun",
    "answer": "C: Kraft meats",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The observation method of collecting marketing research data involves",
    "A": "watching what customers do.",
    "B": "conducting online surveys.",
    "C": "test marketing new products.",
    "D": "calling customers on the phone.",
    "answer": "A: watching what customers do.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following guidelines would be the most appropriate for a supervisor to follow when administering remedial action:?",
    "A": "Take action in the presence of the employee's coworkers.",
    "B": "Let personnel handle minor problems with employees.",
    "C": "Delay taking action so that the connection between the infraction and the penalty becomes blurred.",
    "D": "Resume a normal attitude toward the employee as quickly as possible.",
    "answer": "D: Resume a normal attitude toward the employee as quickly as possible.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Evaluating an employee's performance by comparing it to the goals that were set for the job is part of a technique called",
    "A": "management by objectives.",
    "B": "positive reinforcement.",
    "C": "rank-order technique.",
    "D": "affirmative action.",
    "answer": "A: management by objectives.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A bakery has a vision to become the number one rated cupcake shop in town for the next six months. The most significant problem with this vision is that it is",
    "A": "unclear.",
    "B": "relatable.",
    "C": "short term.",
    "D": "realistic.",
    "answer": "C: short term.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Marketers should check on their markets periodically because markets can",
    "A": "advance.",
    "B": "lead.",
    "C": "fail.",
    "D": "change.",
    "answer": "D: change.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are important considerations in establishing hardware/software specifications for a business?",
    "A": "Capabilities, compatibility, reliability, and cost",
    "B": "Strategic planning, training, upgrades, and cost",
    "C": "User needs, mobility, delivery terms, and technical support",
    "D": "Security, social media policies, performance, and licensing",
    "answer": "A: Capabilities, compatibility, reliability, and cost",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hotel chains carefully analyze economic conditions and the competition before raising prices because the product the chains provide has",
    "A": "limited supply.",
    "B": "elastic demand.",
    "C": "unlimited supply.",
    "D": "inelastic demand.",
    "answer": "B: elastic demand.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the leading computer manufacturers has decided to produce software cases of high quality and high price. Who will ultimately decide if the price is too high?",
    "A": "Consumers",
    "B": "Government",
    "C": "Competition",
    "D": "Manufacturer",
    "answer": "A: Consumers",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before beginning a new project, a manager who uses business process thinking would most likely",
    "A": "examine the financial implications of the project to make sure it will be profitable.",
    "B": "create a list of things that employees should avoid doing during the project.",
    "C": "explain to employees the end result that the manager wants to achieve from the project.",
    "D": "determine the steps that employees need to follow to complete the project.",
    "answer": "D: determine the steps that employees need to follow to complete the project.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ben is hoping to start his own digital marketing business. Which of the following expenditures would fall under the category of \"professional fees\" when Ben is estimating the costs of starting his company:",
    "A": "Insurance and business permits",
    "B": "Computer hardware and software",
    "C": "A trademark for his company logo",
    "D": "Inventory and raw materials",
    "answer": "C: A trademark for his company logo",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An entrepreneurial business owner must",
    "A": "be independently wealthy.",
    "B": "dislike business planning.",
    "C": "desire regular 40-hour work weeks.",
    "D": "have an adventurous spirit.",
    "answer": "D: have an adventurous spirit.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Within a startup business or young company, the primary responsibility for acting ethically falls to",
    "A": "the company's customers.",
    "B": "the business's employees.",
    "C": "business investors.",
    "D": "the entrepreneur.",
    "answer": "D: the entrepreneur.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following helps the reader find specific elements of a formal report:?",
    "A": "Conclusion",
    "B": "Title page",
    "C": "Executive summary",
    "D": "Table of contents",
    "answer": "D: Table of contents",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Calculate a business's total cash available if it has a beginning cash balance of $2,300; total cash receipts of $4,900; and credit sales of $3,500.",
    "A": "$5,800",
    "B": "$7,200",
    "C": "$10,700",
    "D": "$3,700",
    "answer": "B: $7,200",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A small brick-and-mortar bookstore will benefit most from a supply chain that is designed to",
    "A": "purchase books to fulfill requested orders.",
    "B": "stock large quantities of best sellers.",
    "C": "ship books to customers' homes.",
    "D": "use an electronic commerce center to handle orders.",
    "answer": "A: purchase books to fulfill requested orders.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A primary reason that businesses identify market segments is because consumers",
    "A": "are not loyal to popular brands.",
    "B": "demand high-quality goods.",
    "C": "have different needs and wants.",
    "D": "desire the same level of service.",
    "answer": "C: have different needs and wants.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Charlie has a great idea for a new website, but he isn't sure if there is a demand for it. Charlie needs to",
    "A": "develop his business plan.",
    "B": "file for a patent.",
    "C": "consult external resources.",
    "D": "obtain funding.",
    "answer": "C: consult external resources.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A unique selling proposition answers which of the following customer questions:",
    "A": "\"Why is this good or service a great value for me?\"",
    "B": "\"What is the name of this product?\"",
    "C": "\"Why should I buy from you instead of someone else?\"",
    "D": "\"Who makes this product?\"",
    "answer": "C: \"Why should I buy from you instead of someone else?\"",
    "topic": "Product/service management & branding"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is one of the main components of an income statement:?",
    "A": "Assets",
    "B": "Taxes",
    "C": "Liabilities",
    "D": "Revenue",
    "answer": "D: Revenue",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an example of an external factor that affects promotion?",
    "A": "Increase in a product's price",
    "B": "Government regulation of ads",
    "C": "Reorganization of the business",
    "D": "A change in distribution methods",
    "answer": "B: Government regulation of ads",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following products would likely use an exclusive distribution pattern:?",
    "A": "A home-decorating magazine",
    "B": "A gallon of milk",
    "C": "A silk necktie",
    "D": "A large piece of farm machinery",
    "answer": "D: A large piece of farm machinery",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ben is conducting a feasibility study for a new venture idea. Which of the following questions should Ben ask\nand answer in terms of the venture's financial considerations:",
    "A": "Is there a real demand for the idea, good, or service?",
    "B": "How will the business communicate information about its products?",
    "C": "How will the business obtain the money it needs?",
    "D": "What regulations is the business likely to encounter?",
    "answer": "C: How will the business obtain the money it needs?",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a primary factor that small-business owners should consider when deciding to hire additional staff\nmembers?",
    "A": "Product standards",
    "B": "Payroll expenses",
    "C": "Training methods",
    "D": "Interview techniques",
    "answer": "B: Payroll expenses",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "At what stage of the entrepreneurial process does an entrepreneur determine the amount of capital needed t o\nlaunch the business?",
    "A": "Harvesting",
    "B": "Actualization",
    "C": "Development",
    "D": "Discovery",
    "answer": "C: Development",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about promotion:?",
    "A": "Promotional budgets should be at least $200,000.",
    "B": "Companies should utilize all types of media.",
    "C": "Successful promotional strategies should not be changed.",
    "D": "Promotion's ultimate goal is to increase sales.",
    "answer": "D: Promotion's ultimate goal is to increase sales.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kate is a consultant who specializes in helping companies discover and implement positive solutions to\nproblems in their business processes. Kate's work could best be described as",
    "A": "business analysis.",
    "B": "marketing research.",
    "C": "public relations.",
    "D": "financial counseling.",
    "answer": "A: business analysis.",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following employee-selection tools gives employers a chance to evaluate job applicants'\ncommunication skills:?",
    "A": "Personal interview",
    "B": "Physical examination",
    "C": "Reference check",
    "D": "Background screening",
    "answer": "A: Personal interview",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following questions should you ask to learn more about stakeholders' expectations for a project's\nlong-term impact:?",
    "A": "What are the specific deliverables for this project?",
    "B": "What worries you most about this project?",
    "C": "What problems will this project help to solve?",
    "D": "What obstacles will we face in completing this project?",
    "answer": "C: What problems will this project help to solve?",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Every month, a technology company has all-staff meetings in which employees team up and brainstorm new ideas together. Many of these ideas lead to innovative new products. This is an example of how __________ helps organizations innovate and change.",
    "A": "resilience",
    "B": "customer service",
    "C": "training",
    "D": "collaboration",
    "answer": "D: collaboration",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a company has achieved a maximum level of efficiency, the long-run average total costs of production have been?",
    "A": "ignored.",
    "B": "expanded.",
    "C": "minimized.",
    "D": "strengthened.",
    "answer": "C: minimized.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A furniture manufacturer has been receiving complaints about the safety of its Model BA2X baby crib. What is the first thing the manufacturer should do?",
    "A": "Ship the customers another crib",
    "B": "Offer refunds to the customers",
    "C": "Make style improvements to the crib",
    "D": "Initiate a product recall",
    "answer": "D: Initiate a product recall",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Evaluating risk is essential for any business that undertakes a new project or venture. Which of the following is the final step for a business when assessing risks:",
    "A": "Decide if the business can withstand a loss",
    "B": "Reduce or eliminate each identified risk",
    "C": "Estimate the likelihood of a loss occurring",
    "D": "Identify as many risks as possible",
    "answer": "B: Reduce or eliminate each identified risk",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A local business adds a specific item to its product line each spring. This is an example of the product-mix strategy called",
    "A": "contraction.",
    "B": "animation.",
    "C": "trading-up.",
    "D": "expansion.",
    "answer": "D: expansion.",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Anthony has worked as an IT professional at his company for three years. This year, he hopes to be moved to the social media department so that he can learn new skills and expand his professional network. After doing some research, he finds an employee within the department that he thinks he could learn a lot from. In return, he figures he can help the employee clean up their computer and teach them the new company software. He decides to contact the employee to set up a lunch meeting. In other words, Anthony is trying to initiate a",
    "A": "relational analysis.",
    "B": "strategic relationship.",
    "C": "private partnership.",
    "D": "mentorship program.",
    "answer": "B: strategic relationship.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Juan recently expanded his business into another country to reach more of his target market. He was thrill ed\nwith his company's profits following the expansion-until he converted the money back to his domestic\ncurrency. At that point, he realized that the company made much less than he originally thought. What risk\ninvolved with international business did Juan experience?",
    "A": "The cost of international unionized labor",
    "B": "Political unrest in foreign countries",
    "C": "Foreign exchange rate fluctuations",
    "D": "International trade agreement changes",
    "answer": "C: Foreign exchange rate fluctuations",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an impact of implementing an effective customer profile system into a marketing and\nsales campaign:?",
    "A": "It leads to better customer service.",
    "B": "It creates a broader customer base.",
    "C": "It increases the price of a campaign.",
    "D": "It increases the company's churn rate.",
    "answer": "A: It leads to better customer service.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following equations should employees know when they are verifying the accuracy of a business's\nbalance sheet:?",
    "A": "Owner's Equity = Available Cash-Liabilities",
    "B": "Assets = Owner's Equity-Liabilities",
    "C": "Owner's Equity = Liabilities + Available Cash",
    "D": "Assets = Liabilities + Owner's Equity",
    "answer": "D: Assets = Liabilities + Owner's Equity",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a judge determines that two individuals are not qualified to enter into a contract with one another, which basic\ncontractual element is missing?",
    "A": "Consideration",
    "B": "Capacity",
    "C": "Legality",
    "D": "Agreement",
    "answer": "B: Capacity",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An independent organization using part of its website to share comments from satisfied Publix grocery shoppers\nis an example of which element of the promotional mix?",
    "A": "Sales promotion",
    "B": "Publicity",
    "C": "Advertising",
    "D": "Personal selling",
    "answer": "B: Publicity",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are considered the owners of a corporation:?",
    "A": "Lower level employees",
    "B": "Managers",
    "C": "Stockholders",
    "D": "CEOs",
    "answer": "C: Stockholders",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do many businesses use dashboards?",
    "A": "To develop new software programs",
    "B": "To gather information for databases",
    "C": "To maintain security of the systems",
    "D": "To track key performance indicators",
    "answer": "D: To track key performance indicators",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason why a business might terminate an employee for cause is if the employee",
    "A": "refuses a promotion.",
    "B": "is a whistle-blower.",
    "C": "jeopardizes coworkers.",
    "D": "needs additional training.",
    "answer": "C: jeopardizes coworkers.",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A well-documented work process contributes to an efficient operating system because it",
    "A": "is easier to teach to new employees.",
    "B": "has been streamlined to limit waste.",
    "C": "can lead to extra paperwork.",
    "D": "creates the maximum amount of value.",
    "answer": "A: is easier to teach to new employees.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When customers buy on credit, the money owed to the business by the customers is part of the business's?",
    "A": "accounts payable.",
    "B": "cash receipts.",
    "C": "current liabilities.",
    "D": "accounts receivable.",
    "answer": "D: accounts receivable.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What approach to sales forecasting is being used by a business that starts the process by making forecasts for individual products or product lines?",
    "A": "Sales quota",
    "B": "Bottom-up",
    "C": "Trading area",
    "D": "Top-down",
    "answer": "B: Bottom-up",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Henry makes a mistake at work, he considers blaming one of his coworkers. His sense of __________ lets him know that he is facing an ethical dilemma.?",
    "A": "viability",
    "B": "rule of law",
    "C": "disrespect",
    "D": "accountability",
    "answer": "D: accountability",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An entrepreneur who acts with honesty and integrity in all their business relationships is likely to",
    "A": "experience more competition.",
    "B": "increase their expenses.",
    "C": "develop a positive reputation.",
    "D": "avoid ethical dilemmas.",
    "answer": "C: develop a positive reputation.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gross profit shows business owners the difference between what they've",
    "A": "spent and received.",
    "B": "received and billed.",
    "C": "estimated and invoiced.",
    "D": "paid and risked.",
    "answer": "A: spent and received.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a financial risk associated with new ventures:?",
    "A": "Unemployment",
    "B": "Inflation",
    "C": "Competition",
    "D": "Failing industry",
    "answer": "B: Inflation",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The costs required to register a new business are also known as",
    "A": "research expenses.",
    "B": "incorporation fees.",
    "C": "inventory expenses.",
    "D": "establishment fees.",
    "answer": "B: incorporation fees.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Obtaining a line of goods for use in a business is one of the functions of",
    "A": "organizing.",
    "B": "selling.",
    "C": "purchasing.",
    "D": "controlling.",
    "answer": "C: purchasing.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the exchange price of a product?",
    "A": "The price of goods that changes according to economic conditions",
    "B": "The price at which the seller is able to cover costs",
    "C": "The price to the buyer after the seller deducts discounts and allowances",
    "D": "The price that the buyer is willing to pay and the seller is willing to accept",
    "answer": "D: The price that the buyer is willing to pay and the seller is willing to accept",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An example of an operating expense that is included in a business's income statement is",
    "A": "purchases.",
    "B": "allowances.",
    "C": "commissions.",
    "D": "inventory.",
    "answer": "C: commissions.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kenneth owns a company that sells designer dog collars, harnesses, and leashes. He sends a weekly email to current and prospective customers that includes product information and general tips for animal safety. What type of public relations tool is Kenneth using to connect with his target market?",
    "A": "A newsletter",
    "B": "A press conference",
    "C": "A media tour",
    "D": "A press release",
    "answer": "A: A newsletter",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kwame runs an organic meal delivery service. He wants his customers to be able to depend on him to consistently deliver high-quality, healthy food that will simplify their busy lives. This is his company's",
    "A": "company promise.",
    "B": "brand promise.",
    "C": "brand point.",
    "D": "touchpoint.",
    "answer": "B: brand promise.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When analyzing market potential, a business must consider the market's interest level in the product and the market's?",
    "A": "profitability standards.",
    "B": "competence and reliability.",
    "C": "ability to buy.",
    "D": "personal goals.",
    "answer": "C: ability to buy.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In a business, who is typically responsible for determining how much money a CEO should make?",
    "A": "The previous CEO",
    "B": "The board of directors",
    "C": "The vice president",
    "D": "All the employees",
    "answer": "B: The board of directors",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following processes helps aspiring entrepreneurs generate venture ideas:?",
    "A": "Creative thinking",
    "B": "Financial planning",
    "C": "Decision-making",
    "D": "Goal setting",
    "answer": "A: Creative thinking",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Making sure a company follows laws and regulations describes the HR management activity of",
    "A": "compliance.",
    "B": "compensation and benefits.",
    "C": "employee relations.",
    "D": "staffing.",
    "answer": "A: compliance.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because people often change their negotiating styles and strategies, effective negotiators must be",
    "A": "flexible.",
    "B": "uneasy.",
    "C": "indifferent.",
    "D": "optimistic.",
    "answer": "A: flexible.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business that focuses its selling efforts on satisfying the needs and wants of its clientele is a __________ business.",
    "A": "customer-oriented",
    "B": "product-oriented",
    "C": "service-oriented",
    "D": "profit-oriented",
    "answer": "A: customer-oriented",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following characteristics best describe effective marketing research:?",
    "A": "Reliable, timely, subjective",
    "B": "Systematic, accurate, timely",
    "C": "Thorough, inopportune, valid",
    "D": "Objective, inexact, systematic",
    "answer": "B: Systematic, accurate, timely",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the goals of change management is to",
    "A": "limit the effects of a change.",
    "B": "reduce the time it takes to make a change.",
    "C": "keep the people involved to a minimum.",
    "D": "obtain buy-in from stakeholders.",
    "answer": "D: obtain buy-in from stakeholders.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where does a channel of distribution begin?",
    "A": "With the producer",
    "B": "With the intermediary",
    "C": "With the industrial user",
    "D": "With the ultimate consumer",
    "answer": "A: With the producer",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Larry's Dairy wants to team up with Rookie Cookie to develop one new ice cream flavor. How should Larry's Dairy accomplish this?",
    "A": "License Rookie Cookie name",
    "B": "Execute a joint venture",
    "C": "Create a partnership",
    "D": "Create a franchise under Rookie Cookie",
    "answer": "B: Execute a joint venture",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The manager of a gift shop has doubled the selling price of one type of small, stuffed animals because customers want more of the items than are available to buy. What factor affecting selling price is involved in this situation?",
    "A": "Cost and expense",
    "B": "Government regulation",
    "C": "Supply and demand",
    "D": "Competition",
    "answer": "C: Supply and demand",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of corporate growth is depicted in the following example: Company X combines with Company Y to form Company Z.?",
    "A": "Charter",
    "B": "Merger",
    "C": "Consolidation",
    "D": "Expansion",
    "answer": "C: Consolidation",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Charice creates a new kind of glue using a new chemical formula that she invented. She wants to make sure that none of her competitors use the formula for their products. To protect the formula, Charice should __________ it.",
    "A": "patent",
    "B": "trademark",
    "C": "copyright",
    "D": "prototype",
    "answer": "A: patent",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Commissions paid to salespeople increase as the amount of their sales increase. This is an example of __________ costs.",
    "A": "fixed",
    "B": "semi-variable",
    "C": "variable",
    "D": "operating",
    "answer": "C: variable",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business installs dead-bolt locks on all of its exterior doors, it reduces __________ risk.?",
    "A": "natural",
    "B": "economic",
    "C": "human",
    "D": "obsolescence",
    "answer": "C: human",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who typically has the greatest influence on a company's corporate governance?",
    "A": "Board of directors",
    "B": "Shareholders",
    "C": "Chief financial officer",
    "D": "HR director",
    "answer": "A: Board of directors",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "SWOT analysis is a technique for summarizing a company's",
    "A": "skills, workers, organizations, and teams.",
    "B": "strategy, wholesalers, objectives, and trademarks.",
    "C": "strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, and threats.",
    "D": "store, warranty, occupations, and tariffs.",
    "answer": "C: strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, and threats.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What section of a long, formal business report contains the author's opinions?",
    "A": "Appendix",
    "B": "Recommendations",
    "C": "Introduction",
    "D": "Summary",
    "answer": "B: Recommendations",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a scandal involving a large bank's CEO became public, the bank's public relations team went into immediate action. The team released public statements, provided an information hotline for the media, and apologized for the bank's involvement in the scandal. These public relations activities are forms o f?",
    "A": "philanthropy.",
    "B": "community relations.",
    "C": "media tours.",
    "D": "crisis management.",
    "answer": "D: crisis management.",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A business with limited cash flow might decide to lease rather than buy a facility because it wants to avoid making a",
    "A": "short-term commitment.",
    "B": "sizeable down payment.",
    "C": "monthly insurance disbursement.",
    "D": "required security deposit.",
    "answer": "B: sizeable down payment.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gloria, a screenwriter, has written a new script. To protect her artistic work from possible reproduction by other people, she needs a",
    "A": "trade secret.",
    "B": "patent.",
    "C": "trademark.",
    "D": "copyright.",
    "answer": "D: copyright.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A disruption in the supply chain can cause a business to",
    "A": "make more money.",
    "B": "create happy customers.",
    "C": "encourage employees.",
    "D": "stop production.",
    "answer": "D: stop production.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are two results of a company incorporating a business process design:?",
    "A": "Higher efficiency and decreased risk management",
    "B": "Increased structure and more consistency",
    "C": "Increased inefficiencies and more professionalism",
    "D": "More redundancies and improved problem solving",
    "answer": "B: Increased structure and more consistency",
    "topic": "Risk management & insurance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "April and Mark are making plans to open a fashion boutique in an expensive upscale mall in the suburbs. They plan to advertise their shop and put on fundraising fashion shows for charity. Which of the following would be the most appropriate product for them to offer:",
    "A": "$15 T-shirts",
    "B": "$200 silk dress",
    "C": "$20 basic jeans",
    "D": "$5 earrings",
    "answer": "B: $200 silk dress",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your job is to inform consumers about new services being offered by your business. You are involved in what marketing function?",
    "A": "Promotion",
    "B": "Pricing",
    "C": "Financing",
    "D": "Distribution",
    "answer": "A: Promotion",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an operations activity in business:?",
    "A": "Obtaining resources",
    "B": "Selecting media",
    "C": "Analyzing investments",
    "D": "Contacting customers",
    "answer": "A: Obtaining resources",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A realistic vision involves attaining __________ results.",
    "A": "complex",
    "B": "conditional",
    "C": "permanent",
    "D": "noble",
    "answer": "C: permanent",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the general intent of corrective counseling?",
    "A": "To be positive and fact-finding with regard to employee behavior",
    "B": "To manage people in such a way that infractions are prevented",
    "C": "To issue increasingly more severe penalties for each offense",
    "D": "To provide a mechanism for maintaining employee discipline on a day-to-day basis",
    "answer": "A: To be positive and fact-finding with regard to employee behavior",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Davis Company requires customers to provide their banking information each time they pay by phone to eliminate the financial and legal risks associated with storing banking information. However, customers strongly desire the ability to quickly pay by p hone and often do not have their banking information available. The current situation is causing late and missed payments, resulting in lost revenue for the company. Dissatisfied customers experiencing late fees, who often rant about the company's poor ser vice online, are creating a poor brand image for the company. Which of the following actions should the company take to best manage its legal, financial, IT, and brand risks:",
    "A": "Eliminate the pay-by-phone option and require customers to mail their payments to a P.O. Box",
    "B": "Encourage customers to set up automatic electronic payments, eliminating the need to store the information",
    "C": "Send letters explaining how the current payment policy protects customers' personal information",
    "D": "Develop a way to encrypt and store customers' bank information in the company database for future use",
    "answer": "D: Develop a way to encrypt and store customers' bank information in the company database for future use",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of information about equipment is important for businesses to keep in their records?",
    "A": "Country of origin",
    "B": "Inventory status",
    "C": "Production process",
    "D": "Serial numbers",
    "answer": "D: Serial numbers",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the main reasons why businesses need marketing information is to use it in",
    "A": "selling situations.",
    "B": "making decisions.",
    "C": "scheduling advertising.",
    "D": "monitoring distribution.",
    "answer": "B: making decisions.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an action that a business might take after comparing its operating results to the industry average:?",
    "A": "Improve relations with its advertising agency",
    "B": "Decrease collection time on accounts receivable",
    "C": "Increase participation in community activities",
    "D": "Decrease training and orientation for new employees",
    "answer": "B: Decrease collection time on accounts receivable",
    "topic": "Promotion & selling"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do coworkers who are involved in a dispute need to do before they can find a possible solution?",
    "A": "Contact an arbitrator.",
    "B": "Ignore the situation.",
    "C": "Negotiate a settlement.",
    "D": "Identify the problem.",
    "answer": "D: Identify the problem.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before Joe starts working on a new assignment, he thinks about the goals of the assignment, the resources he has available to him, and the activities that the project will entail. Joe is implementing",
    "A": "business process thinking.",
    "B": "inventory management.",
    "C": "personal accountability.",
    "D": "business objective planning.",
    "answer": "A: business process thinking.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is necessary for goods and services to exist?",
    "A": "Product standards",
    "B": "Raw materials",
    "C": "Entrepreneurial discovery",
    "D": "Demographic changes",
    "answer": "C: Entrepreneurial discovery",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following software is required for a computer system to be able to access online data:?",
    "A": "Antivirus",
    "B": "Filter",
    "C": "Browser",
    "D": "Modem",
    "answer": "C: Browser",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Entrepreneurs are often known for being __________, which sets them apart from other business owners.",
    "A": "educated",
    "B": "wealthy",
    "C": "empathetic",
    "D": "creative",
    "answer": "D: creative",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Zander owns a company that buys tea from other companies in China and sells it to grocery stores. Zander's company is a(n)",
    "A": "industrial user.",
    "B": "producer.",
    "C": "wholesaler.",
    "D": "retailer.",
    "answer": "C: wholesaler.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason why TV is popular with advertisers is because it is the",
    "A": "medium that delivers more memorable, believable ads.",
    "B": "only broadcast medium that offers local programming.",
    "C": "least influential type of advertising media.",
    "D": "least expensive type of advertising media.",
    "answer": "A: medium that delivers more memorable, believable ads.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Do businesses such as banks and dry cleaners engage in production?",
    "A": "No, the services provided by these businesses are intangible.",
    "B": "No, these businesses do not engage in production.",
    "C": "Yes, these businesses produce a line of tangible products.",
    "D": "Yes, the services provided by these businesses are their products.",
    "answer": "D: Yes, the services provided by these businesses are their products.",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Assembly, testing, and packaging fall under what stage of supply chain management?",
    "A": "Delivering",
    "B": "Manufacturing",
    "C": "Planning",
    "D": "Sourcing",
    "answer": "B: Manufacturing",
    "topic": "Operations, quality & supply chain"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When an employee is speaking with a customer about the customer's experience with the company, what\nshould the employee do?",
    "A": "Listen actively",
    "B": "Provide input",
    "C": "Anticipate responses",
    "D": "Agree with feedback",
    "answer": "A: Listen actively",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When monitoring progress in achieving organizational goals, it's important to evaluate objectives that are?",
    "A": "vague.",
    "B": "measurable.",
    "C": "implied.",
    "D": "flexible.",
    "answer": "B: measurable.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jolene's ice cream shop runs out of ice cream cones on a busy day. What type of situation requiring adaptability\nis Jolene's shop facing?",
    "A": "Transition period",
    "B": "Resource issue",
    "C": "Emergency",
    "D": "Personal interaction",
    "answer": "B: Resource issue",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of business managers dealing unethically with employees:?",
    "A": "Offering limited part-time options",
    "B": "Disciplining a whistle-blower",
    "C": "Monitoring use of supplies",
    "D": "Downsizing the workforce",
    "answer": "B: Disciplining a whistle-blower",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In what way can a startup business benefit from writing a business plan?",
    "A": "Define managers' roles",
    "B": "Assess a new product or promotion",
    "C": "Prepare for an expansion",
    "D": "Place a value on the business",
    "answer": "A: Define managers' roles",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Owners/Managers should avoid conducting a feasibility study if they are",
    "A": "unsure about the idea.",
    "B": "certain the idea is feasible.",
    "C": "considering a business expansion.",
    "D": "not ready to start the venture.",
    "answer": "B: certain the idea is feasible.",
    "topic": "Opportunity & venture discovery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sakiko wants to make sure she has a good understanding of the target customers for her new venture, so in her business plan, she should include a(n)",
    "A": "company description.",
    "B": "executive summary.",
    "C": "market analysis.",
    "D": "competitive analysis.",
    "answer": "C: market analysis.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ABC Inc. sells very expensive products that the average consumer cannot afford. Which form of demographic segmentation would be the most appropriate to use when directing promotional efforts to the target market?",
    "A": "Occupation",
    "B": "Age",
    "C": "Life stage",
    "D": "Income",
    "answer": "D: Income",
    "topic": "Market planning & strategy"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following ratios can help a business determine its overall profitability:?",
    "A": "Working capital ratio",
    "B": "Dividend yield",
    "C": "Return on equity",
    "D": "Liquidity ratio",
    "answer": "C: Return on equity",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A magazine has recently shifted to an all-digital product. This decision has most likely led to the need for",
    "A": "new employees.",
    "B": "business process changes.",
    "C": "a shift in the mission statement.",
    "D": "increased revenue.",
    "answer": "B: business process changes.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way for a business to control its expenses is to develop a plan to",
    "A": "purchase additional liability insurance.",
    "B": "obtain competitive bids from service providers.",
    "C": "offer flexible work hours to fulltime employees.",
    "D": "eliminate employees' healthcare benefits.",
    "answer": "B: obtain competitive bids from service providers.",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Internal and external audits are both necessary functions for a business, but they have several key differences. One of these differences is that",
    "A": "external auditors are responsible to management, while internal auditors are responsible to shareholders.",
    "B": "internal audits are conducted once a year, while external audits are ongoing and conducted throughout the year.",
    "C": "internal auditors are company employees, while external auditors are employed by an outside audit firm.",
    "D": "external audit reports examine company practices and risks, while internal reports examine financial",
    "answer": "C: internal auditors are company employees, while external auditors are employed by an outside audit firm.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship fundamentals & ethics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason why it is important for businesses to identify and respond to current business trends is to",
    "A": "control performance.",
    "B": "remain competitive.",
    "C": "encourage feedback.",
    "D": "improve motivation.",
    "answer": "B: remain competitive.",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a financial record that indicates an owner's equity in a business:?",
    "A": "Balance sheet",
    "B": "Profit report",
    "C": "Income statement",
    "D": "Operating budget",
    "answer": "A: Balance sheet",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sonny wants to run mail, email, social media, and texting campaigns, which are all forms of __________ marketing.",
    "A": "relationship",
    "B": "digital",
    "C": "print",
    "D": "direct",
    "answer": "D: direct",
    "topic": "Marketing foundations & customer behavior"
  },
  {
    "Question": "A local grocery store encourages its customers to sign up for its free loyalty cards. Based on the data it collects from the cards, the grocery store makes decisions about what items to put on sale and when. This is an example of a data __________ strategy.",
    "A": "encryption",
    "B": "breach",
    "C": "advertising",
    "D": "mining",
    "answer": "D: mining",
    "topic": "Information management & IT/security"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can an action plan help manage employees?",
    "A": "It details steps to achieve sales goals.",
    "B": "It plans for risk.",
    "C": "It explains how products will be created and delivered.",
    "D": "It allows the manager to delegate tasks and track progress.",
    "answer": "D: It allows the manager to delegate tasks and track progress.",
    "topic": "Venture planning & business plan"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What category of an income statement indicates total profit?",
    "A": "Cash flow",
    "B": "Bottom line",
    "C": "Net profit",
    "D": "Gross profit",
    "answer": "D: Gross profit",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An important aspect of providing excellent customer service is",
    "A": "using creative ads.",
    "B": "complimenting vendors.",
    "C": "training employees.",
    "D": "earning high profits.",
    "answer": "C: training employees.",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What important factors should a small business owner consider when deciding whether to hire an additional\nemployee?",
    "A": "Training needs and attitude",
    "B": "Property taxes and benefits",
    "C": "Screening process and skill set",
    "D": "Necessary skills and affordability",
    "answer": "D: Necessary skills and affordability",
    "topic": "Business law & compliance"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When concluding an interview with a job applicant, the interviewer should explain the?",
    "A": "next step in the process.",
    "B": "problems in the business.",
    "C": "performance evaluation system.",
    "D": "requirements of the position.",
    "answer": "A: next step in the process.",
    "topic": "Human resources management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses often buy goods to resell and do not pay for them immediately but receive __________ from the\nsupplier.",
    "A": "bank loans",
    "B": "commercial paper",
    "C": "trade credit",
    "D": "secured loans",
    "answer": "C: trade credit",
    "topic": "Financing, credit & banking"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The last step in the budgeting process is to",
    "A": "gather relevant data.",
    "B": "plug in the data.",
    "C": "evaluate and revise the budget as necessary.",
    "D": "use the budget for financial planning and control.",
    "answer": "C: evaluate and revise the budget as necessary.",
    "topic": "Financial statements & analysis"
  }
]